[{"value": {"id": 1877602, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110241", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of road safety policy on older people's (a) mobility and (b) independence.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["110240"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4029, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "In Great Britain, 17 to 24-year-olds remain one of the highest fatality risk groups, especially young men, both as car drivers and passengers. While drivers aged 17 to 24 represent a high proportion of collisions in Great Britain older car drivers are mor...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Roads: Safety", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "110240", "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877602", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877601, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110240", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what consideration has been given to the effects of her proposed road safety policies on people from both (a) younger and (b) older age demographics.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["110241"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4029, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "In Great Britain, 17 to 24-year-olds remain one of the highest fatality risk groups, especially young men, both as car drivers and passengers. While drivers aged 17 to 24 represent a high proportion of collisions in Great Britain older car drivers are mor...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Roads: Safety", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "110241", "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877601", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877441, "askingMemberId": 5125, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110169", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will make an assessment of the potential impact of the Schengen 90 days in any 180 rule on UK professional drivers and the businesses that depend on them.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["110167", "110168"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4993, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "Since 2021, UK nationals (including hauliers and coach drivers) have been bound to a limit of 90 days in any 180-day period (90/180 limit) for work and leisure journeys in the Schengen area. This limit is consistent with the approach taken by the EU to na...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Large Goods Vehicle Drivers: Immigration Controls", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "110167", "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "110168", "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877441", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877439, "askingMemberId": 5125, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110168", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she has had discussions with her EU counterparts on the potential impact of the Schengen 90 days in any 180 rule on UK professional drivers.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["110167", "110169"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4993, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "Since 2021, UK nationals (including hauliers and coach drivers) have been bound to a limit of 90 days in any 180-day period (90/180 limit) for work and leisure journeys in the Schengen area. This limit is consistent with the approach taken by the EU to na...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Large Goods Vehicle Drivers: Immigration Controls", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "110167", "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "110169", "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877439", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877438, "askingMemberId": 5125, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110167", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she is taking to secure an exemption for UK professional HGV and coach drivers from the Schengen 90 days in any 180 rule.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["110168", "110169"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4993, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "Since 2021, UK nationals (including hauliers and coach drivers) have been bound to a limit of 90 days in any 180-day period (90/180 limit) for work and leisure journeys in the Schengen area. This limit is consistent with the approach taken by the EU to na...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Large Goods Vehicle Drivers: Immigration Controls", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "110168", "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "110169", "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877438", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877597, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110195", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has has made of trends in the level of public awareness of updated Highway Code rules.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4029, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "Following updates to the Highway Code in 2022, the department ran large-scale THINK! advertising campaigns to raise awareness of the changes, with the percentage of road users reporting they knew a little or a lot about the changes going from 36% in Janua...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Highway Code: Publicity", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877597", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877715, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110047", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment she has made of the potential impact of the bird shooting industry on (a) native bird populations and (b) the natural environment.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1579, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "Defra has considered the potential impact of the bird shooting industry in a range of ways. In 2020, Defra considered the ecological impact of gamebird release and commissioned an assessment, as well as identifying evidence gaps for further work. In 2021,...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Birds: Gun Sports", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877715", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877614, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110136", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to help preserve hen harrier numbers.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1579, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "Hen harriers are monitored year-round by Natural England (NE) and the Royal Society for the Protection of Birds. NE staff engage closely with land managers of hen harrier habitat, and in the breeding season support the licenced use of Diversionary Feeding...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hen Harriers: Conservation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877614", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877503, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110291", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether all species of Zebra will be included in the proposed ban on hunting trophies.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["110111", "110119"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1579, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "Defra is continuing to engage with relevant stakeholders to help determine the most appropriate scope for a ban on the import of hunting trophies from species of conservation concern. Timeframes for introducing legislation and details of its scope will be...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hunting: Animal Products", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "110111", "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "110119", "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877503", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877553, "askingMemberId": 5040, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110119", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the proposed trophy hunting ban will include all species of zebra; and when her Department plans to publish what species its proposed ban will cover.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["110111", "110291"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1579, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "Defra is continuing to engage with relevant stakeholders to help determine the most appropriate scope for a ban on the import of hunting trophies from species of conservation concern. Timeframes for introducing legislation and details of its scope will be...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hunting: Animal Products", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "110111", "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "110291", "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877553", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877556, "askingMemberId": 4864, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110111", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether all species of Zebra will be included in the proposed ban on hunting trophies.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["110119", "110291"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1579, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "Defra is continuing to engage with relevant stakeholders to help determine the most appropriate scope for a ban on the import of hunting trophies from species of conservation concern. Timeframes for introducing legislation and details of its scope will be...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hunting: Animal Products", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "110119", "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "110291", "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877556", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877610, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110135", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of trends in the the numbers of hen harriers over the last 5 years.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1579, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "The number of breeding hen harriers is assessed annually by Natural England in partnership with the Royal Society for the Protection of Birds (RSPB). Summaries of these figures are published as blogs via Natural England\u2019s .gov blog page. Assessments of th...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hen Harriers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877610", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877421, "askingMemberId": 5104, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110164", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, if she will take steps to help ensure that official child right\u2019s impact assessments are undertaken to inform the evaluation of different policy options during the consultation, Driving", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5039, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "We will assess a range of impacts when deciding how we will act on social media, including children\u2019s rights and their wellbeing. To inform those assessments, we will consult children and young people directly through the national conversation and consult...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mobile Phones and Social Media: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877421", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877685, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110060", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, with reference to SOPS 1.1. in the Department's 2024/5 Annual Report, if she will publish (a) a breakdown of resource spending on G) Modernising and reforming the work of the Government", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 3966, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "The net resource spending on \u2018Modernising and reforming the work of the Government functions\u2019 for 2024-25 was \u00a3204.375m. The breakdown of gross expenditure is split between Admin and Programme spend is shown below.The \u00a346.366m Admin spent in gross adminis...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology: Public Expenditure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877685", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877568, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110079", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps the Government is taking to incentivise UK-based companies to retain and create skilled jobs in the UK rather than offshore them.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5076, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "Our modern Industrial Strategy is a 10-year plan to back our strengths and create a highly skilled, economically prosperous country, with key objectives to drive up business investment and create high-quality jobs across the UK. We are focused on capturin...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Skilled Workers: Job Creation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877568", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877882, "askingMemberId": 5212, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110578", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps she is taking with international counterparts to ensure Doctors Without Borders are able to access Gaza to provide aid to Palestinians.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5148, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "I refer the Hon Member to the statement to the House I made on 5 January, and to the joint statement issued by the Foreign Secretary and several of her counterparts on 30 December, available on GOV.UK here: https://www.gov.uk/government/news/jointstatemen...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gaza: M\u00e9decins Sans Fronti\u00e8res", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877882", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877433, "askingMemberId": 4623, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110038", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her policies of the Taliban's decision to permanently ban women and girls from education.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5148, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "I refer the Hon Member to the answer provided on 12 January in response to Question 103187.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Afghanistan: Women", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877433", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877590, "askingMemberId": 5112, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110165", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the answer to Question 104985, whether the Government is aware of which independent audit firm the Palestinian Authority has contracted to complete the review of ", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5148, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "I currently have nothing further to add to the previous answer to which the Hon Member refers in his question. As and when there is further information to report on this matter, I will update him and other Members accordingly.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Palestine: Curriculum", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877590", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877716, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "109969", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when she expects a decision from the Office of Road and Rail on the prospect of approving a Newcastle to Brighton rail link.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4993, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "Grand Central submitted an application to the Office of Rail and Road (ORR) on 19 December 2025 for rights to operate Open Access rail services between Newcastle and Brighton. The application has not been agreed by the infrastructure manager, Network Rail...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Newcastle upon Tyne", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877716", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877447, "askingMemberId": 5000, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110117", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he has taken to develop a national diagnostic and treatment pathway for craniocervical instability.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4981, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "Craniocervical instability (CCI) is a complex condition managed through existing specialised neurology and spinal pathways. There is currently no single national diagnostic or treatment pathway for CCI and no plan to change that at this time. Instead, car...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Craniocervical Instability: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877447", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877615, "askingMemberId": 5137, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110177", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his Department's policies of the report by Marie Curie, entitled Dying in Poverty, published in 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 163, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government acknowledges the findings of Marie Curie\u2019s Dying in Poverty report (2025), which highlights the financial insecurity experienced by individuals at the end of life. This Government is committed to providing a financial safety net for those w...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Poverty: Terminal Illnesses", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877615", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878009, "askingMemberId": 5354, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110674", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential implications for its policies of the preliminary findings of the ELSA Study that screens children for Type 1 diabetes.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4981, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government is guided by the UK National Screening Committee (UK NSC), an independent scientific advisory committee which makes its recommendations based on internationally recognised criteria and a rigorous evidence review and consultation process. It...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Diabetes: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878009", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877707, "askingMemberId": 5140, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110180", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish the (a) eligibility criteria for interest-free hardship loans and (b) process for applying for them for retired civil servants that are unable to access their civil service pension payments on", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4449, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Cabinet Office awarded the contract to administer the Civil Service Pension Scheme to Capita in November 2023 under the previous government. The Civil Service Pension Scheme transferred to Capita on 1 December.Transitional Help Loans are available to ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Civil Servants: Workplace Pensions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877707", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877460, "askingMemberId": 5340, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110285", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of vaping devices that (a) contain and (b) can be configured to contain more than the standard 2ml tank capacity through (i) intercha", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4981, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Tobacco and Vapes Bill will stop vapes and nicotine products from being deliberately branded, promoted, and advertised to children and provides the Government with new powers to restrict the packaging, device appearance, and display of vapes and other...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electronic Cigarettes: Public Health", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877460", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878158, "askingMemberId": 5234, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110591", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Answer of 15 January to Question 101203, on Latex: Allergies, if he will place a copy of the Expert Advisory Group on Allergy's December 2025 minutes in the House of Commons L", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4981, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Terms of Reference for the Expert Advisory Group on Allergy, which is overseen and supported by external stakeholders, states that the meetings are confidential. Therefore, the meeting minutes are not shared publicly.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Latex: Allergies", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878158", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877572, "askingMemberId": 5030, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110118", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to support orchestras.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 3966, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government is proud to champion our world-class orchestras and musicians, and help them to thrive. Through Arts Council England\u2019s (ACE) 2023\u201326 National Portfolio Investment Programme, more money is going to more orchestral organisations in more parts...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Orchestras: Government Assistance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877572", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877616, "askingMemberId": 5137, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110178", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has had recent discussions with Marie Curie on funding for the hospice sector.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "Last year, I met key palliative care and end-of-life care stakeholders, including Marie Curie, in a roundtable format with a focus on long-term sector sustainability within the context of our 10-Year Health Plan.The Government is developing a Palliative C...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hospices: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877616", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877540, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110194", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase the level of funding in hospice care in Yeovil constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "Palliative care services are included in the list of services an integrated care board (ICB) must commission, including the Somerset ICB, which covers the Yeovil constituency. To support ICBs in this duty, NHS England has published statutory guidance and ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hospices: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877540", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878150, "askingMemberId": 4811, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110476", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February 2026 to Question 108291 on IVF: Greater Manchester, if he will have discussions with the NHS Greater Manchester Integrated Care Board on the potential impact of", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4444, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "There are no current plans to discuss with the Greater Manchester Integrated Care Board (ICB) any changes to its provision of National Health Service funded in vitro fertilisation treatment or the current National Institute for Health and Care Excellence ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "IVF: Greater Manchester", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878150", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877692, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110068", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what his planned timetable is for issuing Pension Savings Statements to doctors.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": true, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4444, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Department of Health and Social Care has indicated that it will not be possible to answer this question within the usual time period. An answer is being prepared and will be provided as soon as it is available.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Doctors: Workplace Pensions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877692", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877691, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110067", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many doctors have had to file an estimate for their tax returns as a result of not receiving the appropriate Pension Savings Statements before 31 January 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": true, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4444, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Department of Health and Social Care has indicated that it will not be possible to answer this question within the usual time period. An answer is being prepared and will be provided as soon as it is available.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Doctors: Workplace Pensions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877691", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877560, "askingMemberId": 5228, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110220", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment has been made of the performance, environmental impact, and scalability of peat-free alternatives within horticulture.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1579, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "Using the Responsible Sourcing Scheme for Growing Media methodology to assess the environmental impact of different types of growing media, it has been shown that all materials have an environmental impact, but for the most part, peat-alternatives have a ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Horticulture: Peat", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877560", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877424, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110198", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to help ensure the 30 by 30 on land in England nature recovery target is met.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1579, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The UK Government is committed to protecting 30% of land and sea in the UK by 2030 (30by30). Progressing this target on land in England means ensuring that our most important and wildlife-rich habitats are benefiting from effective, long-term conservation...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Land: Environment Protection", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877424", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877491, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110182", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether Natural England has enacted byelaws under Section 28R of the Wildlife and Countryside Act 1981 for the (a) protection and (b) management of Sites of Special Scientific Interest", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1579, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "Natural England has not enacted any byelaws under section 28R since the provision\u2019s introduction in 2001. A set of Model SSSI Byelaws for this purpose was agreed with Defra in 2020 and was published by Natural England at https://consult.defra.gov.uk/natur...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sites of Special Scientific Interest: Nature Conservation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877491", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877401, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110004", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department plans to bring forward legislative proposals to set a target for the reduction of the use of single-use plastic.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1579, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "Defra does not currently have plans to bring forward legislative proposals to set a target for the reduction of the use of single-use plastic. This Government is committed to moving to a circular economy and will publish a Circular Economy Growth Plan tha...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Plastics: Recycling", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877401", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877457, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110126", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, is he will publish the list of companies who have had (a) their license to sponsor skilled and temporary workers revoked and b) their license since reinstated in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5266, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The register of licensed sponsors can be found on the Home Office website at: Register of licensed sponsors: workers - GOV.UKThis is a live document that shows which sponsors are currently fully active and the absence of a sponsor from the list signals th...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Migrant Workers: Sponsorship", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877457", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877620, "askingMemberId": 5283, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110239", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if her Department will provide a guarantee that any changes to settlement rules will not have an adverse impact on families that are on the five-year pathway to remain.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5266, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The earned settlement model, proposed in\u202fA Fairer Pathway to Settlement, is currently subject to a public consultation, running until 12 February 2026.The consultation seeks views on whether there should be transitional arrangements for those already on a...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Immigration", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877620", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877431, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110204", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department plans to publish an equalities impact assessment of the Child Poverty Strategy, including its impact on groups at highest risk of poverty.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1533, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "A full summary Equalities Analysis was published alongside the Strategy and is available at: Child Poverty Strategy: Summary Equalities Analysis - GOV.UK.The impacts of policies contributing to the Child Poverty Strategy will be kept under review and moni...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Poverty: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877431", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877576, "askingMemberId": 4742, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110061", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to help restrict the sale of illegal prescription drugs online.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5213, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Medicines and Healthcare products Regulatory Agency (MHRA) is responsible for the regulation of medicines for human use, medical devices, and blood products for transfusion in the United Kingdom. This includes applying the legal controls on the retail...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prescription Drugs: Sales", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877576", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877612, "askingMemberId": 5186, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110190", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to free up hospital beds and\u00a0support individuals whose families delay hospital discharges to avoid paying for health care costs.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5213, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "Enabling people to be discharged from hospital promptly with the right care and support contributes to better outcomes and a speedier recovery for patients, as well as preventing the loss of independence.As set out in the statutory guidance on hospital di...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hospital Beds", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877612", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877694, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110041", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the post of Chief of Defence People remains part of his plans for Defence Reform.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4682, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "I refer the hon. Member to the answer given by my hon. Friend the Minister for Veterans and People on 26 November 2025 to Question 92316 to the hon. Member for South Suffolk. The full answer can be found below: Significant reforms are being implemented wi...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chiefs of Staff", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877694", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877585, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110130", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to reduce the average time taken for transfers of care of patients being discharged from hospitals to home care provision.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5213, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "It is important that people are discharged promptly from hospital with the right support in place. This winter, local systems have been asked to place a particular focus on reducing bed occupancy and improving patient flow, whilst from 2025/26, National H...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Home Care Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877585", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877686, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110066", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of IT issues on pharmacies claiming payment for Pharmacy First Services that they have carried out.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "Payments made to pharmacy contractors in England are set out in the Drug Tariff. Within the Drug Tarif there are discretionary provisions for advanced services, including Pharmacy First, that allow contractors to receive payment if the submission of claim...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pharmacy: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877686", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877656, "askingMemberId": 4513, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110033", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when will the Copthorne Hotel Gatwick Airport cease to provide asylum accommodation.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["110030", "110031", "110032"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4641, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "This Government inherited a broken asylum system, with tens of thousands stuck in a backlog and claims not being processed, wasting millions in taxpayer money. We will empty asylum hotels as soon as possible, and by the end of this Parliament. That is a c...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Hotels", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "110030", "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "110031", "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "110032", "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877656", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877654, "askingMemberId": 4513, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110032", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers have absconded from the Copthorne Hotel Gatwick Airport to date.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["110030", "110031", "110033"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4641, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "This Government inherited a broken asylum system, with tens of thousands stuck in a backlog and claims not being processed, wasting millions in taxpayer money. We will empty asylum hotels as soon as possible, and by the end of this Parliament. That is a c...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Hotels", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "110030", "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "110031", "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "110033", "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877654", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877653, "askingMemberId": 4513, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110031", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers at the Copthorne Hotel London Gatwick are (a) single males and (b) family groups for which the latest data is available.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["110030", "110032", "110033"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4641, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "This Government inherited a broken asylum system, with tens of thousands stuck in a backlog and claims not being processed, wasting millions in taxpayer money. We will empty asylum hotels as soon as possible, and by the end of this Parliament. That is a c...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Hotels", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "110030", "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "110032", "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "110033", "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877653", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877621, "askingMemberId": 4513, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110030", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers have been (a) moved from the Copthorne Hotel since 22 January and (b) are still located at the site.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["110031", "110032", "110033"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4641, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "This Government inherited a broken asylum system, with tens of thousands stuck in a backlog and claims not being processed, wasting millions in taxpayer money. We will empty asylum hotels as soon as possible, and by the end of this Parliament. That is a c...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Hotels", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "110031", "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "110032", "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "110033", "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877621", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877652, "askingMemberId": 429, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "109966", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to respond to Question 101725 tabled by the hon. Member for Widnes and Halewood on 2 January 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4641, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Hon Member received a response to PQ 101725 on 4th February 2026.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Home Office: Written Questions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877652", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877718, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "109971", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will hold discussions with the (a) Science Museum and (b) Victoria and Albert Museum on making items available online for residents in Northern Ireland.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 3966, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "DCMS officials are in touch with the Science Museum Group and the Victoria and Albert Museum to discuss the ongoing steps they are taking to resume online sales to Northern Ireland. ", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Science Museum and Victoria and Albert Museum: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877718", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877435, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110076", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether she has made an assessment of the security of prisons holding ISIS members following gains by the Syrian army against the Syrian Democratic Forces.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5148, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "I refer the Hon Member to the written ministerial statement published on 28 January. Any further updates on the issues addressed in that statement will be made in the normal way in due course.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Syria: Islamic State", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877435", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877534, "askingMemberId": 55, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "109957", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her policies of reports of attacks on places of worship for Christian communities in Ethiopia.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4572, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "We remain concerned about attacks on places of worship in Ethiopia, and their impact on civilians. We note the 4 November statement of the Catholic Bishops' Conference of Ethiopia condemning recent attacks on Orthodox, Roman Catholic and Muslim communitie...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ethiopia: Christianity", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877534", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877384, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "109996", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to help improve respite services for carers.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government recognises the vital role of unpaid carers and is committed to ensuring they have the support they need.In England, the Care Act 2014 requires local authorities to deliver a wide range of sustainable, high-quality care and support services,...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Respite Care", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877384", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877506, "askingMemberId": 4874, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110113", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, how many secondary legislation (a) laid and (b) planned under the Employment Rights Act 2025 have been submitted to the Regulatory Policy Committee.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5224, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Regulatory Policy Committee (RPC) does not review secondary legislation. Where applicable under Better Regulation guidance, the RPC produces opinions of Option Assessments and Impact Assessments to help Government ensure that the evidence and analysis...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employment Rights Act 2025: Delegated Legislation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877506", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877697, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110242", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what consideration the Department has given to end-of-life decision-making in cases involving progressive loss of capacity, including advanced dementia.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "We recognise that high-quality palliative care and end-of-life care should include the opportunity for individuals to discuss their wishes and preferences so that these can be taken fully into account in the provision of their future care, also known as a...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Palliative Care", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877697", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877712, "askingMemberId": 4787, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110074", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many emergency dental appointments have been delivered under the Urgent Dental Care Incentive Scheme in (a) Norfolk and Waveney and (b) North West Norfolk; and (b) what progress his Department ", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "We have asked integrated care boards (ICBs) to commission extra urgent dental appointments to make sure that patients with urgent dental needs can get the treatment they require. ICBs have been making extra appointments available from April 2025.These app...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dental Services: North West Norfolk", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877712", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877407, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110100", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps NHS England is taking to encourage integrated care boards to commission prioritised oral health pathways for patients undergoing cancer treatment; and whether practices that participate ", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["110099"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government is working to ensure that patients who have a diagnosis of cancer receive timely, safe, and effective dental care.NHS England has produced guidelines which aim to ensure that patients across England with a diagnosis of cancer, including ora...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cancer: Dental Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "110099", "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877407", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877406, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110099", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has identified general dental practices participating in locally commissioned schemes to provide prioritised oral healthcare for patients undergoing cancer treatment.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["110100"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government is working to ensure that patients who have a diagnosis of cancer receive timely, safe, and effective dental care.NHS England has produced guidelines which aim to ensure that patients across England with a diagnosis of cancer, including ora...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cancer: Dental Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "110100", "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877406", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877504, "askingMemberId": 4595, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110036", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Stoke-on-Trent Central of 24 November 2025 with case reference GS06761.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4631, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Home Office responded to the hon. Member on 3 December 2025. This reply has been resent on 3 February 2026.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Members: Correspondence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877504", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877633, "askingMemberId": 3935, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "109981", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to answer Question 107979 on Defence: Expenditure tabled by the Rt hon. Member for Central Devon on 23 January 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4682, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "I will respond to the right hon. Member shortly.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Defence: Written Questions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877633", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877658, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110146", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to improve the Royal Navy\u2019s targeting decision cycle, including through the Navy AI Cell.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4682, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "Subject to the Defence Investment Plan, the Royal Navy intends to use digital systems, data tools, and structures that allow maritime forces to contribute to a Digital Targeting Web that is effective across different domains and integrates with NATO allie...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Navy: Artificial Intelligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877658", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877665, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110151", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of integration between Project Asgard and Project Boyd.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4682, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Strategic Defence Review outlined how the Armed Forces must complete the journey from a joint force to an Integrated Force underpinned by a common digital foundation and shared data. Project BOYD and Project ASGARD represent the Royal Air Force (RAF) ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Military Intelligence: Artificial Intelligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877665", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877661, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110148", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what is the scope of the Royal Navy\u2019s Develop Directorate.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4682, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Royal Navy\u2019s Develop Directorate leads the development of future warfighting capability and acts as the Design Authority for naval capabilities of the future. It seeks to achieve the optimum mix of present and future warfighting technologies required ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Navy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877661", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877660, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110147", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what is the remit of the Royal Navy\u2019s Disruptive Capabilities and Technologies Office.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4682, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "I refer the hon. Member to the response given to Question 105587 on 21 January 2026.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Navy: ICT", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877660", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877635, "askingMemberId": 5280, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110237", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of State Pension age changes on 1950s born women in Aberdeenshire North and Moray East constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["110203", "110225"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5069, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "All women born since 6 April 1950 have been affected by changes to State Pension age. Estimates can be made with ONS 2022 Census Data of how many women born in the 1950s were resident in each constituency in that year.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "State Retirement Pensions: Women", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "110203", "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "110225", "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877635", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877655, "askingMemberId": 5277, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110225", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of State Pension age changes for 1950s-born women living in Moray West, Nairn and Strathspey constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": ["110203", "110237"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5069, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "All women born since 6 April 1950 have been affected by changes to State Pension age. Estimates can be made with ONS 2022 Census Data of how many women born in the 1950s were resident in each constituency in that year.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "State Retirement Pensions: Women", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "110203", "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "110237", "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877655", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877430, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110203", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of State Pension age changes for 1950s-born women living in Harpenden and Berkhamsted constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["110225", "110237"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5069, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "All women born since 6 April 1950 have been affected by changes to State Pension age. Estimates can be made with ONS 2022 Census Data of how many women born in the 1950s were resident in each constituency in that year.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "State Retirement Pensions: Women", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "110225", "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "110237", "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877430", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877501, "askingMemberId": 1482, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "109972", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of excluding soft play centres and other family focused venues from the 15 per cent business rates discount for pubs and music venues on those businesses; and whe", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5282, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "Pubs rents in business rates valuations are analysed differently to some other sectors. While most hospitality and leisure properties are valued by comparing the size of the property, pubs are valued by comparing their turnover potential. Industry bodies ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Leisure: Business Rates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877501", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878170, "askingMemberId": 5125, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110555", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of postal deliveries across Northern Ireland.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["110554"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5076, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "Ministers and officials have discussions with Royal Mail on a regular basis in its capacity as the universal service provider. Earlier this month, I met the CEO of Royal Mail, Alistair Cochrane, to press him on Royal Mail\u2019s progress in improving quality o...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Delivery Services: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "110554", "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878170", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878169, "askingMemberId": 5125, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110554", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will have discussions with Royal Mail to encourage timely deliveries in Lagan Valley.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["110555"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5076, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "Ministers and officials have discussions with Royal Mail on a regular basis in its capacity as the universal service provider. Earlier this month, I met the CEO of Royal Mail, Alistair Cochrane, to press him on Royal Mail\u2019s progress in improving quality o...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Royal Mail: Lagan Valley", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "110555", "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878169", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877511, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110077", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will publish a break down of the billions in investment secured on his visit to China in January 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1446, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "As set out in the 30 January press release, hundreds of millions worth of new investment was secured as part of the visit, alongside \u00a32.2 billion in export deals. This includes investment from HiTHIUM, Chery Commercial Vehicle, Asymchem, and POP MART.Furt...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Foreign Investment in UK: China", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877511", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877505, "askingMemberId": 4874, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110112", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of regulatory divergence from the EU on UK exporters since July 2024, broken down by sector and by firm size.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1446, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "No, we will not be making such a precise assessment, but the EU is our closest partner and biggest trading market and we are committed to making trade easier by removing unnecessary barriers to trade. To date, many UK regulations continue to align in the ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Export Controls", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877505", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877507, "askingMemberId": 4874, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110114", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assumptions his Department uses regarding cost pass-through to consumers when assessing the impact of new trade-related regulatory requirements on businesses, and whether those assumptions have be", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5076, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "Addressing regulatory barriers to trade can help reduce costs for UK businesses trading internationally and support economic growth. Cost pass\u2011through to consumers is subject to uncertainty and may differ significantly depending on market conditions, prod...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Overseas Trade: Regulation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877507", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877456, "askingMemberId": 1491, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "109973", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, when he will publish the results of the Department's consultation on the Voluntary Carbon and Nature Markets: raising integrity.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5260, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government welcomes the many responses to the Voluntary Carbon and Nature Markets consultation. Officials are undertaking analysis of the responses received and the Government intends to publish its response in the first half of this year.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Carbon Emissions: Public Consultation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877456", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877709, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110044", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions she has had with app-based private hire companies regarding Transport for London issuing licences for private hire drivers.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4029, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Secretary of State has not recently discussed the issuing of private hire vehicle driver licences by Transport for London with private hire vehicle operators.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Taxis: Licensing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877709", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877700, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110043", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to paragraph 84 of the UK Government Resilience Action Plan, when the Lead Government Department Expectations will be published.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4243, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "We plan to publish the Lead Government Department Expectations in Spring 2026. ", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Emergencies", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877700", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877587, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110132", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidance his Department has issued to local authorities on setting adult social care fee uplifts in financial year 2026-27.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "Under the Care Act 2014, local authorities are tasked with the duty to shape their care markets to meet the diverse needs of all local people. This includes negotiating fees individually with care providers to achieve a sustainable balance of quality, eff...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Services: Fees and Charges", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877587", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877393, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110095", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, a) what estimate his Department has made of the average additional cost per passenger ticket on domestic ferry services arising from the inclusion of domestic maritime within the UK Emissions", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5116, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government has not produced estimates of the additional cost per passenger ticket arising from the inclusion of domestic maritime within the UK Emissions Trading Scheme. The Impact Assessment considers costs at sector-level rather than by route or far...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "UK Emissions Trading Scheme: Ferries", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877393", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877423, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110224", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether he has made a recent assessment of the eligibility of tenants who purchase electricity via landlord-supplied prepayment card systems for support under the Warm Home Discount Scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5129, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "In 2025, the Government consulted on whether to expand the Park Homes Warm Home Discount Scheme to other households without a direct relationship with their energy supplier (including those pay their landlord for energy). Given the cost of the scheme fall...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electricity: Rented Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877423", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877427, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110075", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether the \u00a3530,000 community compensation payment listed in the Community funds for transmission infrastructure guidance for the installation of a substation applies to substations installe", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4998, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The \u00a3530,000 figure is not compensation. It is a community benefit recognising, transparently, the vital role that host communities play in delivering nationally important clean energy infrastructure. The guidance applies only to onshore electricity trans...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Solar Power: Community Development", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877427", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877618, "askingMemberId": 4657, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110053", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to assess the need for the provision of the vaccination against Covid for (a) children and (b) adults who are suffers of Long-Covid.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4981, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "I refer the Hon. Member to the answer I gave on 2 February 2026 to Question 108759.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Coronavirus: Vaccination", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877618", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877588, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110133", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the impact of increases in employer National Insurance contributions on the financial sustainability of domiciliary care providers.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5282, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government\u202fhas protected the smallest\u202fbusinesses and charities\u202ffrom the impact of the increase to employer National Insurance\u202fby increasing the\u202fEmployment Allowance\u202ffrom \u00a35,000\u202fto \u00a310,500.\u202fThat means\u202fmore than half of businesses with\u202fNICs\u202fliabilities ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Home Care Services: Employers' Contributions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877588", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877689, "askingMemberId": 5301, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110260", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether he has had discussions with Companies House on recent increases to their fees.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5076, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The recent adjustments to the fees, which came into effect on 1 February 2026, were determined following detailed modelling of budgetary requirements by Companies House to support the delivery of priorities set by this government. There was extensive dial...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Companies House: Fees and Charges", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877689", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877717, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "109970", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate her Department has made of the change in the number of people who will be tax payers as a result of the freezing of personal allowances between 2024 and 2029.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5069, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The number of people forecast to pay Income Tax by marginal rate can be found in Table 3.19 of the Office for Budget Responsibility\u2019s November 2025 Economic and fiscal outlook \u2013 detailed forecast tables: receipts, linked below: https://obr.uk/download/nov...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Income Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877717", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877608, "askingMemberId": 4630, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110039", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she has made and assessment of the potential merits of completing an updated assessment of the potential savings to the Exchequer from withdrawing the postponed VAT accounting process, taking into account (a", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5282, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "Postponed VAT accounting provides significant support for businesses, helping to manage cash flow and facilitate imports. HMRC undertakes regular operational work to ensure compliance with the rules around postponed VAT accounting. The VAT gap has reduced...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "VAT", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877608", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877535, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110236", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the proposed pay-per-mile tax on electric vehicles will take into account rural drivers.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5282, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "As announced at Budget 2025, the Government is introducing Electric Vehicle Excise Duty (eVED) from April 2028, a new mileage charge for electric and plug-in hybrid cars, recognising that electric vehicles (EVs) contribute to congestion and wear and tear ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electric Vehicles: Excise Duties", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877535", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877589, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110134", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the Government plans to publish proposals for a long-term funding settlement for adult social care during this Parliament.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4083, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The provisional Local Government Finance Settlement for 2026-27 to 2028-29 sets out multi-yearsettlements for local authorities, including upper tier authorities that have social care responsibilities. As part of this, the government have set out the fund...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Services: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877589", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877563, "askingMemberId": 5283, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110238", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to implement the legislative changes proposed in the 'Strengthening the standards and conduct framework for local authorities in England' cons", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4083, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The government published its response to the consultation \u201cStrengthening the standards and conduct framework for local authorities in England\u201d in November 2025. We intend to legislate on local government standards reforms when parliamentary time allows.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877563", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877428, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110201", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the cost of changes in the levels of funding to hospices on the wider healthcare system.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["110200"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "answerText": "Integrated care boards (ICBs) are responsible for commissioning palliative care services to meet the reasonable needs of their population, which can include hospice services available within the ICB catchment. To support ICBs in this duty, NHS England has...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hospices: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "110200", "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877428", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877426, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110200", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of funding the full cost of specialist palliative care delivered by hospices.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["110201"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "answerText": "Integrated care boards (ICBs) are responsible for commissioning palliative care services to meet the reasonable needs of their population, which can include hospice services available within the ICB catchment. To support ICBs in this duty, NHS England has...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hospices: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "110201", "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877426", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877586, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110131", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of proposed local authority care fee uplifts below the minimum price for homecare on the sustainability of the domiciliary care market.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "answerText": "Under the Care Act 2014, local authorities are tasked with the duty to shape their care markets to meet the diverse needs of all local people. This includes negotiating fees individually with care providers, including in the domiciliary market, to achieve...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Home Care Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877586", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877593, "askingMemberId": 1576, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "109978", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to (a) increase the availability of aspirin and (b) normalise aspirin supply chains.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5213, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Department is aware of a recent disruption to the supply of aspirin dispersible tablets and are working with suppliers to understand the causes and aid a return to normal supply as soon as possible. Supply issues have been addressed, and stock is regu...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Aspirin: Supply Chains", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877593", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879406, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111604", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to her Department\u2019s press release entitled Act now: 864,000 sole traders and landlords face new tax rules in two months, published on 5 February 2026, what assessment she has made of the potential imp", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879406", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879405, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111603", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to her Department\u2019s press release entitled Act now: 864,000 sole traders and landlords face new tax rules in two months, published on 5 February 2026, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of a", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879405", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879404, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111602", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to her Department\u2019s press release entitled Act now: 864,000 sole traders and landlords face new tax rules in two months, published on 5 February 2026, what steps HM Revenue and Customs is taking to en", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879404", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879360, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111601", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to Answer of 2 February 2026 to Question 108145 on Graduates: Employment, how many higher education providers are currently at risk of regulatory intervention.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879360", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879358, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111600", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the long-term career progression of graduates who are not in high-skilled employment 15 months after graduation.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879358", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879354, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111599", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential impact of the tax treatment of the State Pension and Pension Credit on the relative incomes of pensioners.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879354", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879353, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111598", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps is he taking to help improve price transparency for veterinary services.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879353", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879352, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111597", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of the Competition and Market Authority\u2019s report entitled The Competition and Markets Authority (CMA) is conducting a market i", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879352", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879299, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111596", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of student loan repayments on recruitment and retention in NHS roles where a degree is mandatory.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879299", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879298, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111595", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the proportion of the total value of Plan 2 student loans issued since 2012 that will be written off.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879298", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879297, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111594", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of the student loan interest rate on costs to the public purse.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879297", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879296, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111593", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the cost to the public purse of funding undergraduate courses that do not lead to sustained graduate-level employment.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879296", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879295, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111592", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many undergraduate courses eligible for student loans have median graduate earnings below the repayment threshold five years after graduation.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879295", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879291, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111591", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of student loan repayments on graduates\u2019 ability to meet basic living costs in South Basildon and East Thurrock constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879291", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879290, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111590", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on the number of people in the South Basildon and East Thurrock constituency who have fully repaid their Plan 2 student loan.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879290", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879289, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111589", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on the number of people who have outstanding Plan 2 student loans in South Basildon and East Thurrock constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879289", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879288, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111588", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on the number of Plan 2 student loan borrowers who have seen their outstanding balance increase despite making regular repayments in South Basildon and East Thurrock consti", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879288", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879287, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111587", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, with reference to his Department\u2019s press release entitled Clean energy funding to be tied to stronger workers\u2019 rights, published on 4 February 2026, what assessment he has made of the potenti", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879287", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879286, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111586", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, with reference to his Department\u2019s press release entitled Clean energy funding to be tied to stronger workers\u2019 rights, published on 4 February 2026, what mechanisms his Department will use to", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879286", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879285, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111585", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, with reference to his Department\u2019s press release entitled Clean energy funding to be tied to stronger workers\u2019 rights, published on 4 February 2026, what assessment his Department has made of", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879285", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879312, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111584", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she plans to end the sale of written-off consumer debts to third-party debt purchasers.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879312", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879308, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111583", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department has taken to respond to breaches of the Supplier Code of Conduct v3.0 Ethical Behaviour provisions.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879308", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879307, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111582", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department is taking to help protect the interests of UK subcontractors that are engaged by Government suppliers.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879307", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879306, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111581", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department is taking to help ensure that subcontractors supplying Government departments have high standards.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879306", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879305, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111580", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information she holds on when the Animal Welfare Committee plans to publish its report on the responsible sourcing of fur.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879305", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879304, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111579", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether she plans to publish a response to the call for evidence on the fur trade, published on 31 May 2021.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879304", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879303, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111578", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the (a) objectives and (b) workplan will be for the working group on fur.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879303", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879302, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111577", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when the working group on fur will be established; and whether animal welfare organisations will be asked to participate.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879302", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879399, "askingMemberId": 5352, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111576", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether he plans to meet small pub landlords to discuss potential closures and job losses within the hospitality sector.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879399", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879396, "askingMemberId": 5352, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111575", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps he is taking to support small pub landlords.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879396", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879393, "askingMemberId": 5352, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111574", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of Government policies on rural economies and high streets on the social and community value of pubs.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879393", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879392, "askingMemberId": 5352, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111573", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of business rates revaluation on village pubs and hospitality venues in rural areas.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879392", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879391, "askingMemberId": 5352, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111572", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what comparative assessment she has made of the potential impact of alcohol duty policy on on-trade venues such as pubs, with off-trade alcohol sales in supermarkets.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879391", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879390, "askingMemberId": 5352, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111571", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she has conducted a comparative assessment of the potential impact of (a) VAT rates on food and drink served in pubs compared with (b) VAT rates applied in comparable European countries.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879390", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879389, "askingMemberId": 5352, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111570", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of introducing additional business rates relief for community pubs that operate as the sole hospitality venue in rural villages.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879389", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879388, "askingMemberId": 5352, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111569", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential cumulative impact of business rates, minimum wage increases, VAT, energy costs and alcohol duty on the viability of small and independently owned pubs.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879388", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879387, "askingMemberId": 5352, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111568", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to review early years funding policy to help ensure it is fit for purpose for rural and shared-setting providers.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879387", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879386, "askingMemberId": 5352, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111567", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has had discussions with the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government on supporting early years provision delivered through village halls and other community assets.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879386", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879385, "askingMemberId": 5352, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111566", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential implications of rural early years provision in sustaining village communities and preventing rural depopulation on her Department's funding policy for early years.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879385", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879384, "askingMemberId": 5352, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111565", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of rural early years setting closures on (a) low-income, (b) part-time and (c) any other parental workers.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879384", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879383, "askingMemberId": 5352, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111564", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to help support recruitment and retention of early years staff in rural areas, including consideration of travel costs, wage supplements, and shared staffing models.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879383", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879382, "askingMemberId": 5352, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111563", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if her Department will issue guidance to Ofsted and local authorities on recognising the operational challenges faced by early years providers operating from shared community buildings.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879382", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879381, "askingMemberId": 5352, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111562", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance her Department provides to local authorities on the use of (a) sustainability and (b) contingency funding to prevent the closure of sole early years providers in rural villages.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879381", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879380, "askingMemberId": 5352, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111561", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many rural early years settings have closed in each of the last five years; and what proportion of those were operating from shared or temporary premises.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879380", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879379, "askingMemberId": 5352, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111560", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to introduce a (a) rurality and (b) sparsity weighting within the Early Years National Funding Formula.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879379", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879378, "askingMemberId": 5352, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111559", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the financial viability of rural early years providers operating from (a) village halls and (b) any other shared community premises where daily set-up and pack-down co", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879378", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879441, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111558", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what progress his Department has made on setting out plans to seek further evidence from the park homes sector on the rationale for the maximum 10 per cent commission payable on ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879441", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879425, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111557", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of a respiratory modern service framework on winter pressures on the NHS.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879425", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879367, "askingMemberId": 5343, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111556", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with park home resident groups on the sales commission rate in the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879367", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879355, "askingMemberId": 5343, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111555", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the 10% sales commission on park home residents.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879355", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879342, "askingMemberId": 5334, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111554", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential implications for her policies of trends in the level of importation of synthetic cathinones through mail; and what progress her Department has made in t", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879342", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879341, "askingMemberId": 5334, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111553", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her policies of the Advisory Council on the Misuse of Drugs' recommendations on synthetic cathinones in its report entitled Synthetic Cat", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879341", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879340, "askingMemberId": 5334, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111552", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of updating the Home Office Approved Field Testing guidance in relation to synthetic cathinones.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879340", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879339, "askingMemberId": 5334, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111551", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of expanding drug testing on arrest powers to synthetic cathinones.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879339", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879323, "askingMemberId": 5320, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111550", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government following the internal review of the upper limit for Disabled Facilities Grants.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879323", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879322, "askingMemberId": 5320, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111549", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he plans to take following the internal review of the upper limit for Disabled Facilities Grants; and what his planned timetable is for further action.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879322", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879435, "askingMemberId": 5313, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111548", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of trends in the level of use of Community Protection Warnings in cases involving people experiencing a mental health crisis; and what gu", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879435", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879401, "askingMemberId": 5310, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111547", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps her Department is taking to reduce speeding on rural roads in Newbury constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879401", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879400, "askingMemberId": 5310, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111546", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether her Department plans to review diversion routes for M4 closures to ensure that country lanes are not used.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879400", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879398, "askingMemberId": 5310, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111545", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the performance of AJM Healthcare in delivering wheelchair services to the NHS.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879398", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879397, "askingMemberId": 5310, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111544", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she has made an estimate of the proportion of automotive technicians qualified to work on electric vehicles.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879397", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879395, "askingMemberId": 5310, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111543", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that refrigeration, air conditioning and heat pump engineers receive training in handling flammable and toxic alternative refrigerants bef", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879395", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879394, "askingMemberId": 5310, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111542", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the proposed hydrofluorocarbon phasedown reforms will include mandatory training requirements for the refrigeration, air conditioning and heat pump workforce.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879394", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879343, "askingMemberId": 5303, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111541", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of imported agricultural produce on farm-gate prices for British farmers.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879343", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879422, "askingMemberId": 5301, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "111540", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department has made a recent evaluation of the effectiveness of the under-occupation deduction policy for social rented housing.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879422", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879420, "askingMemberId": 5301, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "111539", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department will publish (a) national and (b) regional breakdowns of under-occupied social rented housing.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879420", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879419, "askingMemberId": 5301, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "111538", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 18 December 2025 to Question 101647 on Anti-social Behaviour: Children, whether she will provide a forum for volunteer groups to ask questions that may arise as a result of t", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879419", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879418, "askingMemberId": 5301, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "111537", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 18 December 2025 to Question 101646 on Offences against Children, whether guidance will explicitly address the concerns outlined in the Casey Review that Child Sexual Exploit", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879418", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879417, "askingMemberId": 5301, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "111536", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 18 December 2025 to Question 101646 on Offences against Children, whether guidance to volunteer groups will explicitly state that child sexual abuse must not be tolerated und", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879417", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879338, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111535", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of rail services that have been returned to state ownership on the level of service in Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879338", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879337, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111534", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of funding for road maintenance in Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879337", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879336, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111533", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps his Department is taking to help ensure the accuracy of small businesses' energy bills in Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879336", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879335, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111532", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what plans his Department has to help improve GP access to decarbonisation schemes in Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879335", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879334, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111531", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps he is taking to support the green energy sector in Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879334", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879333, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111530", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the resilience of the electricity distribution network in Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879333", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879332, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111529", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to help increase levels of (a) recruitment and (b) retention of neighbourhood police officers in Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879332", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879331, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111528", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to help ensure in-person access to police services in Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879331", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879427, "askingMemberId": 5268, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111527", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to make water social tariff (a) eligibility, (b) discount levels and (c) application processes (i) transparent and (ii) subject to government oversi", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879427", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879426, "askingMemberId": 5268, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111526", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of trends in the level of support for water social tariff across different regions; and what steps she is taking to ensure households in similar", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879426", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879450, "askingMemberId": 5265, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111525", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel received a pre-discharge mental health assessment in each year since 2015.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879450", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879449, "askingMemberId": 5265, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111524", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, following discharge, how quickly do veterans receive their medical records.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879449", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879448, "askingMemberId": 5265, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111523", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reason were urgent repairs requested for Service Family Accommodation from 20/12/25 to 1/1/26.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879448", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879447, "askingMemberId": 5265, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111522", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many urgent repairs were requested for Service Family Accommodation from 20/12/25 to 1/1/26.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879447", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879446, "askingMemberId": 5265, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111521", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many dedicated mental health professionals there are per capita across the military; and how many have there been each year since 2015.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879446", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879445, "askingMemberId": 5265, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111520", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on internal human resources services each year since 2015.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879445", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879444, "askingMemberId": 5265, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111519", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on military police services each year since 2015.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879444", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879361, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "111518", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many GP practices have closed in the last 12 months; and and GPs have (a) resigned and (b) retired in the same period of time.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879361", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879359, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "111517", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of changes to employer National Insurance contributions to (a) GP practices, (b) the number of FTE GPs in work and (c) locum GPs.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879359", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879357, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "111516", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to (a) improve access to GPs and (b) increase the number of FTE GPs (i) in work and (ii) on permanent contracts.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879357", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879375, "askingMemberId": 5251, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111515", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether consenting determinations for critical energy transmission infrastructure in Scotland will be made in line with the 52 week process needed to support the delivery of Clean Power 2030.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879375", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879350, "askingMemberId": 5227, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111514", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to increase standards in and ensure effective regulation of the cosmetic surgery sector.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879350", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879436, "askingMemberId": 5225, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111513", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what consideration the Government has given to making dynamo power lights compulsory on e-scooters and bikes.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879436", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879424, "askingMemberId": 5211, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-23T00:00:00", "uin": "111512", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many applications to open Sixth Forms and Post 16 offers the Department has granted in (a) England, (b) London and (c) West Ham and Beckton constituency in each of the last three years.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879424", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879443, "askingMemberId": 5208, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111511", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what criteria her Department will apply when deciding which organisations are invited to participate in the forthcoming consultation on banning trail hunting; and whether bodies which ", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879443", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879442, "askingMemberId": 5208, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111510", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment has she made of the potential impact of the changes to the sovereignty of the Chagos Islands on the protection of the marine environment of the Chagos Archipe", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879442", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879439, "askingMemberId": 5208, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111509", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of compound interest on the long-term balances of student loan borrowers including those with intermittent or low earnings.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879439", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879438, "askingMemberId": 5208, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111508", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what hardship protections are available to student loan borrowers experiencing financial pressure, and what assessment the Department has made of the potential impact of the absence of interest freezes or repay", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879438", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879434, "askingMemberId": 5208, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111507", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the UK Port Waste Reception Facilities regime in supporting the disposal of fishing gear; and whether he plans to strengthen or stan", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879434", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879433, "askingMemberId": 5208, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111506", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department is taking steps to (a) define and regulate the classification of ocean plastic and related environmental claims and (b) tackle marketing practices where products", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879433", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879430, "askingMemberId": 5208, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111505", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of requirements relating to safe and suitable flooring within the reformed Decent Homes Standard for social and privately ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879430", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879428, "askingMemberId": 5208, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111504", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether additional support will be made available to schools to help meet staffing costs as a result of the launch of the new free breakfast club programme in April 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879428", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879328, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111503", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to ensure that NHS organisations and contracted wheelchair service providers are subject to more rigorous, mandatory regulation.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879328", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879327, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111502", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to make the recently developed service specification guidelines for wheelchair services mandatory across England.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879327", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879326, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111501", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what statistics he has on the demand for and use of wheelchairs; and how that data informs NHS England\u2019s commissioning of appropriate services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879326", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879325, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111500", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that funding for wheelchair users is adequate to meet essential needs, including equipment and specialist support.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879325", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879437, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111499", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of business rates on soft play centres in Harpenden and Berkhamsted constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879437", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879324, "askingMemberId": 5199, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111498", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of support available to low-income families whose children require prolonged inpatient neonatal and paediatric care.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879324", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879416, "askingMemberId": 5198, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "111497", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent steps she has taken to close asylum hotels, particularly the Four Points Hotel in Horley.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879416", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879301, "askingMemberId": 5193, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111496", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has assessed the adequacy of financial investment in (a) weekend, (b) short-break fostering and (c) supported lodgings.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879301", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879432, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111495", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many responses her Department received to the consultation entitled Amending the hydrofluorocarbon phasedown schedule.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879432", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879431, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111494", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will meet with manufacturers from the heating, refrigeration and air conditioning industries to discuss mandatory training regarding flammable refrigerants as part of the GB F G", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879431", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879429, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111493", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to her Department's press release entitled Game changer for the nation, published on 19 June 2025, how much and what proportion of the funding for new and upgraded grassroots sport", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879429", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879263, "askingMemberId": 5154, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111492", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure that the Child Maintenance Service is able to identify hidden earnings.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879263", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879262, "askingMemberId": 5154, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111491", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to (a) improve the Child Maintenance Service and (b) ensure that payments are made.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879262", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879440, "askingMemberId": 5138, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111490", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her department is taking to strengthen flood resiliency around major transport routes in the South West.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879440", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879373, "askingMemberId": 5138, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111489", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department has taken to help ensure the timely implementation of Wave 0, Wave 1 and Wave 2 hospital schemes planned under the New Hospital Programme impacting Wave 3 schemes.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879373", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879369, "askingMemberId": 5138, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111488", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will publish the detailed scoring of MCDA analysis conducted under the New Hospital Programme Review for individual schemes once those schemes have been completed.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879369", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879363, "askingMemberId": 5138, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111487", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the capacity within the construction industry to build schemes planned under the New Hospital Programme on schedule.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879363", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879362, "askingMemberId": 5138, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111486", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what operational savings his Department has identified from the Royal Liverpool University Hospital that may be applicable to schemes planned under the New Hospital Programme.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879362", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879351, "askingMemberId": 5138, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111485", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that (a) the Programme Team of New Hospital Programme has adequate levels of staff and (b) staffing vacancies do not delay the implementation of that p", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879351", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879349, "askingMemberId": 5138, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111484", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether operational savings secured from hospitals built to Hospital 2.0 standard under the New Hospital Programme: Plan for Implementation will be redirected to support the increased maintenance c", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879349", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879347, "askingMemberId": 5138, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111483", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to his Department's policy paper entitled New Hospital Programme; Plan for Implementation, published on 20 January 2025, what the evidential basis is for the estimated cost for the r", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879347", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879346, "askingMemberId": 5138, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111482", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will conduct a detailed assessment of the progress of individual schemes delivered under the New Hospital Programme.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879346", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879348, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "111481", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 11 November 2025 to Question 84973 on Car-Hill formula, when he plans to publish the conclusions of that review.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879348", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879318, "askingMemberId": 5105, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111480", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if will he publish a list of all (a) current and (b) former Parliamentarians that have been named in the Epstein files.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879318", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879317, "askingMemberId": 5105, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111479", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information her Department holds on whether the Crown Estate sought legal advice on the potential liability of their properties being used for the procurement of prostitution.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879317", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879316, "askingMemberId": 5105, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111478", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information her Department holds on the number of times that Jeffrey Epstein (a) visited and (b) stayed at a Crown Estate owned property.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879316", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879315, "askingMemberId": 5105, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111477", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what information his Department holds on the number of times Peter Mandelson visited 11 Downing Street between June 2010 and March 2020 for each year.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879315", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879314, "askingMemberId": 5105, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111476", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what information his Department holds on the number of times Peter Mandelson visited 10 Downing Street in each year since 6 May 2010 before he was appointed as the UK Ambassador to the United States of America.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879314", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879313, "askingMemberId": 5105, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111475", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what information his Department holds on the number of times that George Osborne (a) visited the British Ambassador to the United States of America and (b) met with officials from the British Embassy in the Unit", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879313", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879300, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "111474", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what information her Department holds on role that the Rt hon. Member for Tottenham had in the appointment of Lord Mandelson as the UK Ambassador to the United States of Amer", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879300", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879415, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111473", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his department is taking to help ensure that the Pupil Premium is spent on supporting the needs of the eligible children\u2019s needs.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879415", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879414, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111472", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his department has made of the efficacy of schools\u2019 use of the Pupil Premium to support eligible children.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879414", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879413, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111471", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what consideration his department has given to the potential benefits of changing Pupil Premium rules so that funding goes directly towards supporting the eligible child\u2019s care.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879413", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879412, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111470", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment has his department made of the potential benefits to allowing parents of previously looked after children to make financial contributions to the Pupil Premium for therapy.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879412", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879411, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111469", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment has his department made of the potential benefits of introducing mandatory regular building surveys and maintenance plans in support of vulnerable adults under the court of protection.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879411", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879410, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111468", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of financial abuse by negligent Financial Deputies on vulnerable adults under the court of protection.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879410", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879409, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111467", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress the MRS has made in delivering mechanistic research into ME/CFS.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879409", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879408, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111466", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether her Department plans to promote the new road safety strategy to the public.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879408", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879407, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111465", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he plans to reassess compensation amounts under the Infected Blood Compensation Scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879407", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879421, "askingMemberId": 4874, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "111464", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when the Minister of State for Social Security and Disability plans to respond to the correspondence of (a) 19 December and (b) 20 January from the hon. Member for Arundel and South Downs.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879421", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879374, "askingMemberId": 4846, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "111463", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if she will review the decision to withhold documents relating to Andrew Mountbatten Windsor\u2019s role as UK Special Representative for Trade and Industry until 2065.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879374", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879294, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111462", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what the cost to UK Export Finance was in 2024\u201325 of expanding its climate stress testing models and scenarios using Network for Greening the Financial System scenarios; what the estimated cost of this", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879294", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879293, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "111461", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the Government Property Agency\u2019s total expenditure was in 2024\u201325 on measuring, collecting, reporting or validating greenhouse gas emissions across the Government estate; and what the Agency\u2019s projected ann", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879293", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879292, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111460", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what staffing or system costs are associated with monitoring, reporting and compliance activity relating to official travel emissions in his Department.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879292", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879284, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111459", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the provision of central reservation barriers on the National Highways motorway and trunk road network, how many crossover accidents, where vehicles have breached the central reservation, occu", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879284", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879283, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111458", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answers of 1 December 2025 to Questions 93461 and 93459, if she will publish the locations, route sections and lengths for a) the 52.6 km of rigid concrete barrier installed in each of the perio", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879283", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879282, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111457", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 18 November 2025 to Question 87860, what HOPS Change Budget refers to; and whether the figures provided relate solely to spending on electric vehicle charging infrastructure ", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879282", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879281, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111456", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of airport surface access planning conditions and sustainability requirements on the level of car parking and drop-off charges paid by passengers.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879281", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879280, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "111455", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January 2026 to Question 105302 on Dartford-Thurrock Crossing: Privatisation, what steps she is taking to mitigate for the loss of revenue to her Department from the privatisation o", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879280", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879279, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111454", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether estimates of net Government support per passenger journey are used internally by her Department for (a) budgeting, (b) business planning and (c) performance monitoring purposes; and in which internal do", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879279", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879278, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111453", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when her Department plans to publish the updated Traffic Advisory Leaflet 1/24; and what assessment she has made of the potential merits of recommending that local authorities permit motorcycles to use bus lane", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879278", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879277, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111452", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps her Department is tacking to help tackle anti-social behaviour on the bus network.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879277", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879276, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111451", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether her Department has conducted a comparative assessment of Air Passenger Duty rates in the UK with aviation passenger taxes and equivalent charges in other European countries; and whether such analysis is used", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879276", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879270, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "111450", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average grant-supported cost per bus was under each bus procurement scheme in each of the last five years; and what assessment she has made of the potential impact of social value weightings on tendere", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879270", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879269, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "111449", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when she plans to publish the final National Policy Statement for Ports..", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879269", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879268, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111448", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she intends to make changes to the existing Airports National Policy Statement in the context of the potential of a third runway at Heathrow; and what assessment she has made of the likelihood of securi", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879268", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879267, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111447", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January 2026 to Question 105288 on Railways: Repairs and Maintenance, what criteria is used to determine which rail infrastructure schemes are included in the Department\u2019s longer-te", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879267", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879266, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111446", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assurances she has had from Network Rail on steps being taken to minimise unnecessary barrier down-time at level crossings, while maintaining safety; and how such assurances will be monitored.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879266", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879265, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "111445", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 4.3.2 of the draft National Policy Statement for Ports, what guidance will be available to decision-makers to support their interpretation of the terms compensation for as a last res", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879265", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879264, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111444", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 4.5.12 of the draft amended National Policy Statement for Ports, published on 4 June 2025, what guidance will be available to decision-makers to support them interpreting the term ec", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879264", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879356, "askingMemberId": 4799, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111443", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to help ensure that women can access toothpaste that is appropriate for their saliva's ph level.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879356", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879311, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111442", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what powers does she have to help ensure schools comply with (a) paragraph 6.81 of the SEN Code of Practice and (b) Equality Act 2010.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879311", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879310, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111441", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the cost of providing written guidance to schools on how to write accessible SEN Information Reports.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879310", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879309, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111440", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she has she taken to help ensure schools comply with (a) paragraph 6.81 of the SEN Code of Practice and (b) Equality Act 2010.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879309", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879453, "askingMemberId": 4765, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "111439", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, the current (a) mean average and (b) longest waiting time for a Work Capability Assessment reassessment.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879453", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879452, "askingMemberId": 4765, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "111438", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many cases were awaiting Work Capability Assessment reassessments as of 31 January 2026 in each constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879452", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879451, "askingMemberId": 4716, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "111437", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when she plans to publish further information on the new Places of Worship Renewal Fund.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879451", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879366, "askingMemberId": 4716, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "111436", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of improving a) research, b) monitoring and c) labelling of perfluoroalkyl and polyfluoroalkyl substances.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879366", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879365, "askingMemberId": 4716, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "111435", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if her Department will consider a universal restriction on perfluoroalkyl and polyfluoroalkyl substances.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879365", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879364, "askingMemberId": 4716, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "111434", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when her Department plans to launch the consultation on restricting perfluoroalkyl and polyfluoroalkyl substances in consumer articles.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879364", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879423, "askingMemberId": 4515, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111433", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what funding provisions his Department has made in relation to the forthcoming National Tuberculosis Action Plan 2026\u20132031.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879423", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879372, "askingMemberId": 4513, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "111432", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, whether the investment announced for Welsh railways forms part of a multi-year funding settlement; and how much of the investment is guaranteed beyond 2025\u201326, including planned spend in 2026\u201327 and 2027\u201328.", "answeringBodyId": 28, "answeringBodyName": "Wales Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879372", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879371, "askingMemberId": 4513, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "111431", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions she has had with her counterpart in the Welsh Government on how much and what proportion of the \u00a3450 million investment in Welsh railways will be spent in the current spending review period; and wh", "answeringBodyId": 28, "answeringBodyName": "Wales Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879371", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879370, "askingMemberId": 4513, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "111430", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions she has had with her counterpart in the Welsh Government on how much of the \u00a3445 million funding for Welsh railways will be spent on (a) electrification, (b) railway station development, (c) railwa", "answeringBodyId": 28, "answeringBodyName": "Wales Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879370", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879368, "askingMemberId": 4513, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "111429", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, if she will provide a breakdown by operations, maintenance, renewals and enhancement of funding committed by the UK Government to Welsh railways between 2025\u201326 and 2028\u201329.", "answeringBodyId": 28, "answeringBodyName": "Wales Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879368", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879377, "askingMemberId": 4491, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111428", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what recent progress his Department has made towards the publication of the Local Power Plan; and when he plans to publish that plan.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879377", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879330, "askingMemberId": 4360, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "111427", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what performance metrics the Davies Group are held to; and how frequently those metrics are evaluated.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879330", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879329, "askingMemberId": 4360, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "111426", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many hearing loss cases are pending with the Davies Group.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879329", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879275, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111425", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to provide additional resources to gynaecology services to help reduce waiting times.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879275", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879274, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111424", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, to detail the average waiting time for gynaecological surgery, in each of the last five years, broken down by Health and Social Care Trust.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879274", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879273, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111423", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, to detail the average waiting time for gynaecological consultant appointments, in each of the last five years, broken down by Health and Social Care Trust.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879273", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879272, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111422", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve waiting times for gynaecological (i) consultant appointments and (ii) surgery.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879272", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879271, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111421", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she plans to introduce a statutory code of practice for private parking operators.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879271", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879403, "askingMemberId": 3973, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "111420", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what delivery mechanisms will be used to implement the Warm Homes Scheme to ensure effective and timely delivery of funding.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879403", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879402, "askingMemberId": 3973, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "111419", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps he is taking to help mitigate potential job losses in the energy efficiency sector and associated supply chains following plans to close the Energy Company Obligation scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879402", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879345, "askingMemberId": 3973, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "111418", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether the Department for International Development commissioned a study on the value for money of people to people programmes in Israel and Palestine in 2021.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879345", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879344, "askingMemberId": 3973, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "111417", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether her Department has made an assessment of the value for money of the International Fund for Israeli-Palestinian Peace.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879344", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879321, "askingMemberId": 54, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "111416", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what procedures will apply to enable access by the Intelligence and Security Committee to such documentation necessary to fulfil the duties placed upon it n relation to dealings between Peter Mandelson and Jeffr", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879321", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879320, "askingMemberId": 54, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "111415", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if she will make it her policy to pause the passage of the Diego Garcia Military Base and British Indian Ocean Territory Bill until after the (a) release and (b) full assessm", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879320", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879319, "askingMemberId": 54, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-06T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "111414", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if she will provide the Intelligence and Security Committee with (a) correspondence and (b) a list of engagements between (i) Peter Mandelson, and (ii) other advisers to and ", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879319", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879261, "askingMemberId": 5186, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "907850", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of changes to electric Vehicle Excise Duty on the use of internal combustion engine vehicles.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879261", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879016, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "111413", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the answer given to question 109756 on 4 February 2026, for what reason he will not publish the representations received.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879016", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878999, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111412", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the role of media literacy in helping children identify misleading or harmful online content.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878999", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878998, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111411", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure schools tackle gender-specific online harm.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878998", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878997, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111410", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps he is taking to promote media literacy among child users.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878997", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878996, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111409", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether he has had discussions with Ofcom on improving media literacy among parents and children.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878996", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878995, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111408", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what comparative assessment she has made of trends in the level of online harm experienced by (a) girls and (b) boys.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878995", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878994, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111407", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of children under the age of 13 having personal social media profiles including public profile pictures on their safety.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878994", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878987, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111406", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether his Department provides guidance to parents on the use of smartphones and internet-enabled devices by children of pre-school age.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878987", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878985, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111405", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what assessment he has made of the prevalence of 3-5 year old children owning personal mobile devices and the implications for online safety.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878985", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878900, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111404", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to reduce the long-term reliance of asylum seekers on local authority social care services.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878900", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878899, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111403", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he has had discussions with the leader of Kent County Council on the potential impact of delays in asylum decision-making contribute on local authority social care costs.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878899", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878898, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111402", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department plans to publish regular forecasts of asylum-related social care costs incurred by local authorities.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878898", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878897, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111401", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to help reduce the concentration of asylum-related social care costs in a small number of local authorities.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878897", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878896, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111400", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will list the ten local authorities which incurred the highest asylum-related social care costs in the 2024-25 financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878896", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878895, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111399", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the sustainability of current funding arrangements for unaccompanied asylum-seeking children.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878895", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878894, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111398", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the average cost per unaccompanied asylum-seeking child to local authorities was in the 2024-25 financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878894", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878893, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111397", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many unaccompanied asylum-seeking children were supported by local authorities in each financial year since 2019-20.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878893", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878892, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111396", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of asylum-related social care costs on (a) council tax levels and (b) core service provision.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878892", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878891, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111395", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department plans to fully reimburse local authorities for the costs of providing social care to asylum seekers.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878891", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878890, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111394", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much and what proportion of local authority spending on asylum-related social care was reimbursed by central government in each financial year since 2019-20.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878890", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878909, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111393", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when her Department plans to publish the consultation on restricting Perfluoroalkyl and Polyfluoroalkyl Substances (PFAS) in consumer articles.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878909", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879115, "askingMemberId": 5358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111392", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with stakeholders in the agricultural sector on securing an SPS Agreement between the UK and the EU.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879115", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879114, "askingMemberId": 5358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111391", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to help ensure that the implementation of a common UK\u2013EU SPS agreement is compatible with the operation of the Precision Breeding Act.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879114", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878970, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111390", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether his Department has considered the potential impact of alternative rooftop land uses, including solar panels and energy infrastructure, on the (a) valuation of properties hosting telec", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878970", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878969, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111389", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether his Department has assessed the potential impact of the removal, relocation and temporary decommissioning of rooftop telecommunications equipment as part of programmes to install roof", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878969", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878959, "askingMemberId": 5343, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111388", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of the repayment term for post-2012 student loans being set at 40 years on (a) graduates in lower-paid or insecure employment, (b) social mobility", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878959", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878957, "askingMemberId": 5343, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111387", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of the student loan repayment threshold remaining at its current level on (a) graduates in lower-paid or insecure employment, (b) social mobility ", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878957", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878920, "askingMemberId": 5343, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111386", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department is taking to help reduce regulatory barriers for exporting businesses through digitisation.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878920", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878919, "askingMemberId": 5343, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111385", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what digital resources his Department provides to support small and medium-sized enterprises with exporting.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878919", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878889, "askingMemberId": 5327, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111384", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the planned minimum learning period for drivers will apply to learner drivers of all ages.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878889", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878888, "askingMemberId": 5327, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111383", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she plans to take steps to collect information from on-board vehicle diagnostics systems at the point of (a) an MOT and (b) vehicle servicing to guide measures.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878888", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879210, "askingMemberId": 5322, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111382", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has taken steps to review public safety at protests.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879210", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879208, "askingMemberId": 5322, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111381", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he plans to amend the Matrimonial Causes Act.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879208", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879015, "askingMemberId": 5322, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111380", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has made an assessment of the potential impact of derelict school buildings on children\u2019s education.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879015", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879014, "askingMemberId": 5322, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111379", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment has she made of the adequacy of school buildings in Surrey.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879014", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879013, "askingMemberId": 5322, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111378", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many times have schools been rejected for Condition Improvement Funding in Surrey in the last 20 years.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879013", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879011, "askingMemberId": 5322, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111377", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which schools have received Condition Improvement Funding in Surrey in the last 20 years.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879011", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878979, "askingMemberId": 5319, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "111376", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much funding her Department has provided to (a) the Invictus Games and (b) UK participants in the Invictus Games (i) in each of the last three games and (ii) how much funding she plans to pro", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878979", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879005, "askingMemberId": 5318, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111375", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what guidance she has issued to companies conducting autonomous vehicle trials on public communications on the (a) capability and (b) legal compliance of prototype systems.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879005", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879004, "askingMemberId": 5318, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111374", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether her Department maintains a record of safety interventions, traffic contraventions and near-misses arising from autonomous vehicle trials.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879004", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879001, "askingMemberId": 5318, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111373", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what guidance her Department has issued to the police on detecting and enforcing traffic contraventions committed by autonomous vehicles where no human driver is actively controlling the vehicle.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879001", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879000, "askingMemberId": 5318, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111372", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of the ability of autonomous systems to correctly interpret traffic signals at complex or partially obscured junctions in dense urban environments.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879000", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878980, "askingMemberId": 5318, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111371", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of introducing an inflation adjustment mechanism for capital gains tax calculations.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878980", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878978, "askingMemberId": 5318, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111370", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of safety measures on the A34 including (a) signage, (b) road markings, (c) LED road studs and (d) speed management protocols; and if she will publis", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878978", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878975, "askingMemberId": 5318, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111369", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the National Work-Related Road Safety Charter, what guidance he plans to issue to riders of e-bikes on (a) training, (b) vehicle standards and (c) safe working practices.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878975", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878973, "askingMemberId": 5318, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111368", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department holds information related to an independent comparative assessment of the potential cost to the public pursue of Thames Water's White Horse reservoir proposal wi", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878973", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878965, "askingMemberId": 5318, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111367", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will publish the flood and safety risk assessments for the proposed SESRO reservoir.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878965", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878961, "askingMemberId": 5318, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111366", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the potential impact of the SESRO project on the water bills of customers of (a) Thames Water, (b) Southern Water and (c) Affinity Water; and whether this", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878961", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878958, "askingMemberId": 5318, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111365", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department had a cap for the level of cost increase for Thames Water\u2019s SESRO project above which the project would not have been approved.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878958", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878956, "askingMemberId": 5318, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111364", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has held discussions with Buckinghamshire, Oxfordshire and Berkshire West Integrated Care Board on its policy on access to fertility services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878956", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878955, "askingMemberId": 5318, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111363", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of whether individual ICBs are deviating from NICE guidance.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878955", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878954, "askingMemberId": 5318, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111362", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will make it her policy that the Road Safety Investigation Branch (a) record and (b) publish data on collisions involving illegally modified e-bikes separately from those involving standard pedal cycles.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878954", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878953, "askingMemberId": 5318, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111361", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure illegally modified e-bikes and (a) identified and (b) addressed within the scope of the National Work-Related Road Safety Charter.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878953", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878884, "askingMemberId": 5310, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111360", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make it his policy to end the use of body mass index as a criterion for determining eligibility for joint replacement surgery.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878884", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879099, "askingMemberId": 5281, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111359", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of funding the full cost of specialist palliative care delivered by hospices.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879099", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879089, "askingMemberId": 5281, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111358", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure General Practice nursing and administrative staff are offered a pay increase as a result of the funding increase for GP contracts for 2025/26.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879089", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879087, "askingMemberId": 5281, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111357", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department plans to provide exemptions from Electronic Travel Authorisation for children living abroad who hold dual citizenship having inherited their British Citizenship from a Parent bu", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879087", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879202, "askingMemberId": 5277, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "111356", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if he will implement the recommendations of the Social Tariff Working Group\u2019s final report, published 23 April 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879202", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879176, "askingMemberId": 5277, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "111355", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if his Department will review the suitability of UK Government contracts with Palantir.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879176", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879198, "askingMemberId": 5265, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111354", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans her Department has to help support sustainable fishing through investment.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879198", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879196, "askingMemberId": 5265, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111353", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department if taking steps to help promote fish as part of a healthy diet.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879196", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879195, "askingMemberId": 5265, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111352", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to support small fishing fleets.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879195", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879194, "askingMemberId": 5265, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111351", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to encourage young people to enter the fishing industry.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879194", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879191, "askingMemberId": 5265, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111350", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to support young people in the fishing industry.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879191", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879190, "askingMemberId": 5265, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111349", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to ensure European fishing boats comply with the UK-EU fishing deal, particularly within the UK 12-mile limit.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879190", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879072, "askingMemberId": 5265, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111348", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, will the RAF's Eurofighter Typhoon be upgraded with the Aerodynamic Modification Kit.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879072", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879136, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111347", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure patients are not wrongly removed from the official NHS waiting list due to administrative issues.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879136", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879135, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "111346", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of the reduction in NHS waiting lists since April 2025 is attributable to patient removals; and if he will publish a breakdown of waiting-list change by treatment status.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879135", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879133, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111345", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will report the number of patients removed from waiting lists data and the reasons for their removal.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879133", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879131, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "111344", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will publish full, raw NHS waiting-list data including removals and treatment activity on a weekly and monthly basis.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879131", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879130, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111343", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions she has had with the optical sector on (a) proposals to modernise driver vision testing and (b) any other proposals to strengthen road safety standards.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879130", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879129, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111342", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps her Department is taking to help support public awareness of the Don\u2019t Swerve a Sight Test campaign.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879129", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879128, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "111341", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of increasing the number of vision checks required for drivers aged over 70 on road safety.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879128", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878971, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111340", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of an increase in urgent care Units of Dental Activity on trends in the level of the provision of routine and preventative NHS dental care.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878971", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879201, "askingMemberId": 5212, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111339", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions her Department has had with industry on the number of flight instructors; and assessment she has made of the capacity of flight schools to train commercial airline pilots.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879201", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878947, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111338", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people became unemployed while waiting for a decision on their application to the Access To Work Scheme in 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878947", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878946, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111337", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of applications for the Access To Work scheme had a wait time of more than two weeks from submitting an application to receiving a decision in 2025 in (a) Berkshire and (b) ", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878946", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878952, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111336", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what progress her Department has made to help improve the energy efficiency of homes in Harpenden and Berkhamsted constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878952", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878951, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111335", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of the levels of funding for music and dance schools on the adequacy of the provision of music and dance training.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878951", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878950, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111334", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans her Department has to provide support to schools that face financial challenges to participate in the Music and Dance Scheme Schools.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878950", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878949, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111333", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans her Department has to provide long-term funding for schools supported by the Music and Dance Scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878949", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878948, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111332", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to help ensure children from non-privileged backgrounds can access music and dance training (a) through the Music and Dance Scheme Schools and (b) any other schemes.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878948", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879162, "askingMemberId": 5193, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111331", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of children in care that are unable to access stable fostering placements in the Buckingham and Bletchley constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879162", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879161, "askingMemberId": 5193, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111330", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to (a) monitor and (b) shorten the fostering approval process to meet the Government\u2019s pledge for getting vulnerable children into foster homes.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879161", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879160, "askingMemberId": 5193, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111329", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what metrics her Department will use to assess the potential impact of additional investment on fostering support models.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879160", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879159, "askingMemberId": 5193, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111328", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what estimate he has made of the potential impact of an enhanced UK-Switzerland trade agreement on jobs in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879159", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879158, "askingMemberId": 5193, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111327", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of how export credit support affects business resilience to global economic shocks.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879158", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879157, "askingMemberId": 5193, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111326", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, how UK Export Finance measures the economic impact of its support across domestic supply chains.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879157", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879156, "askingMemberId": 5193, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111325", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the contribution of export credit to the UK economy over the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879156", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879155, "askingMemberId": 5193, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111324", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps she is taking to help ensure regulatory co-operation with China does not impact on UK standards in financial supervision.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879155", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879154, "askingMemberId": 5193, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111323", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what mechanisms she will use to monitor the implementation of agreements reached on innovative biodiversity financing with China.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879154", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879152, "askingMemberId": 5193, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111322", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps she has taken to ensure UK firms are impacted the designation of the Bank of China\u2019s London Branch as the UK\u2019s second renminbi clearing bank.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879152", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879151, "askingMemberId": 5193, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111321", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of the outcomes of the UK-China Financial Working Group on UK-China trade flows.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879151", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879150, "askingMemberId": 5193, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111320", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the agreements from the first UK-China Financial Working Group in Beijing on UK financial services.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879150", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879149, "askingMemberId": 5193, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111319", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what evaluation framework he will use to measure the economic impact of the High Street Strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879149", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879148, "askingMemberId": 5193, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111318", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he us taking to help ensure new regeneration tools like Community Right to Buy deliver outcomes for independent retailers.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879148", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879147, "askingMemberId": 5193, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111317", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of betting shops on town centre vitality.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879147", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879107, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111316", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps she is taking to help improve the efficiency of His Majesties Revenue and Customs' operations.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879107", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878963, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111315", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the social housing sector in (a) Yeovil constituency, (b) Somerset and (c) England.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878963", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878960, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "111314", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of trends in the level of administrative errors made by social housing providers when a resident transitions from Housing Credit to Universal Credit.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878960", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878974, "askingMemberId": 5184, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111313", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he has with the Secretary of State for Business and Trade on the number of wheelchair accessible vehicles that are purchased through the Motability Scheme are produced in the United Kin", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878974", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878972, "askingMemberId": 5184, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111312", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps he is taking to help ensure that wheelchair accessible vehicles are produced in the United Kingdom.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878972", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879118, "askingMemberId": 5177, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111311", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of low levels of rail enhancement funding for railways in Wales on passenger numbers in Wales.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879118", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879102, "askingMemberId": 5177, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111310", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what percentage of UK Government rail (a) Enhancement and (b) Operations, Maintenance and Renewal spending does Wales receive.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879102", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879101, "askingMemberId": 5177, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111309", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions she has had with his EU counterparts on a future SPS agreement and the potential impact of this on the rollout of Bovine TB vaccines in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879101", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879100, "askingMemberId": 5177, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111308", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much capital funding has the Welsh Government received for highway maintenance up to 2030.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879100", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879098, "askingMemberId": 5177, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111307", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what recent discussions he has had with the Welsh Government on the inclusion of coal tips in the forthcoming coal license ban.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879098", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879079, "askingMemberId": 5171, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111306", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential impact the EU\u2019s bans on certain pesticides and fungicides taking effect and the UK\u2019s planned alignment in June 2027 on British farmers.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879079", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879078, "askingMemberId": 5171, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111305", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what mechanisms are in place to help protect farmers from fluctuations in milk prices following the removal of the Basic Payment Scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879078", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878902, "askingMemberId": 5171, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111304", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will take steps to ensure that Metro Mayors retain roles in heavy rail governance under the provisions of the Railways Bill.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878902", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878938, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111303", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many nights were spent in hotels by Departmental staff in financial year 2024-25 by the star rating of the hotel.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878938", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878937, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111302", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many nights were spent in hotels by Departmental staff in financial year 2024-25 by the star rating of the hotel.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878937", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878936, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111301", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many nights were spent in hotels by Departmental staff in financial year 2024-25 by the star rating of the hotel.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878936", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878935, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111300", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many nights were spent in hotels by Departmental staff in financial year 2024-25 by the star rating of the hotel.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878935", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878934, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111299", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many nights were spent in hotels by Departmental staff in financial year 2024-25 by the star rating of the hotel.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878934", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878933, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111298", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, how many nights were spent in hotels by Departmental staff in financial year 2024-25 by the star rating of the hotel.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878933", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878932, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111297", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many nights were spent in hotels by Departmental staff in financial year 2024-25 by the star rating of the hotel.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878932", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878931, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111296", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many nights were spent in hotels by Departmental staff in financial year 2024-25 by the star rating of the hotel.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878931", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878930, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111295", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many nights were spent in hotels by Departmental staff in financial year 2024-25 by the star rating of the hotel.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878930", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878929, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111294", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, how many nights were spent in hotels by Departmental staff in financial year 2024-25 by the star rating of the hotel.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878929", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878928, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111293", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many nights were spent in hotels by Departmental staff in financial year 2024-25 by the star rating of the hotel.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878928", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878927, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111292", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how many nights were spent in hotels by Departmental staff in financial year 2024-25 by the star rating of the hotel.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878927", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878926, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111291", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many nights were spent in hotels by Departmental staff in financial year 2024-25 by the star rating of the hotel.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878926", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878925, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111290", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many nights were spent in hotels by Departmental staff in financial year 2024-25 by the star rating of the hotel.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878925", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878924, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111289", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, how many nights were spent in hotels by Departmental staff in financial year 2024-25 by the star rating of the hotel.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878924", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878923, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111288", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many nights were spent in hotels by Departmental staff in financial year 2024-25 by the star rating of the hotel.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878923", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878921, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111287", "questionText": "To ask the Solicitor General, how many nights were spent in hotels by Departmental staff in financial year 2024-25 by the star rating of the hotel.", "answeringBodyId": 88, "answeringBodyName": "Attorney General", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878921", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878916, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111286", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if her Department will publish all information it holds on child sexual exploitation committed by illegal migrants.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878916", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878906, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111285", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether Great British Railways will record and publish standardised data on the causes of Penalty Fares.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878906", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878905, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111284", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what data her Department collects on the reasons given for the issuing of Penalty Fares on the rail network.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878905", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879132, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111283", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether he plans to bring forwards an alternative to the Audit Reform and Corporate Governance Bill.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879132", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879209, "askingMemberId": 5110, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111282", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the statutory walking distance for entitlement to home to school transport under section 42(4) of the Education (Scotland) Act 1980.", "answeringBodyId": 2, "answeringBodyName": "Scotland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879209", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879188, "askingMemberId": 5102, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111281", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of the the crude oil and diesel spill from the Piper Bravo Platform on 6 January 2026 on the marine environment.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879188", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879207, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111280", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of making thatching existing properties zero-rated for VAT.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879207", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879206, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111279", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the number of domestic thatch growers on the future of the industry.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879206", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879205, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111278", "questionText": "To ask the Solicitor General,?how many people have been prosecuted for flying a drone in a Restricted Fly Zone around (a) closed prisons and (b) young offender institutions since January 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 88, "answeringBodyName": "Attorney General", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879205", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879185, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111277", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to page 22 of the Police reform white paper, From Local to National: A New Model for Policing (CP1489), by when will every neighbourhood police officer and Police Community Support Offi", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879185", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879184, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111276", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to page 22 of the Police reform white paper, From Local to National: A New Model for Policing (CP1489), by when will she design new standards so that neighbourhood officers are not rout", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879184", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879146, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111275", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to page 22 of the Police reform white paper, From Local to National: A New Model for Policing (CP1489), how can local residents find out who their named, contactable officer is.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879146", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879145, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111274", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to page 16 of the Police reform white paper, From Local to National: A New Model for Policing (CP1489), by when will the Police Efficiency and Collaboration Programme be fully operation", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879145", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879144, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111273", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which MOD sites are in scope to be sold under the Defence Estates Optimisation Plan.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879144", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879143, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111272", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what NATO intelligence functions are based at RAF Wyton.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879143", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879142, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111271", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many MOD sites used by Cadets have been closed under the Future Defence Infrastructure Services programme.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879142", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879141, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "111270", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment has he made of the potential merits of exceptions for (a) Military Intelligence Services and (b) Special Forces operators under the Hillsborough Law.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879141", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879140, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111269", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what information does her Department hold on the number of occasions that Ministers from her Department met with representatives from MBR Acres since 5 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879140", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879125, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111268", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many civil servants have left the Ministry of Defence via the targeted voluntary exit scheme since 5 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879125", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879124, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111267", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many civil servant positions within the Ministry of Defence were gapped as at (a) 5 July 2024 and (b) 1 February 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879124", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879122, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "111266", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what information her Department holds on the Government Departments Lord Mandelson could access using his work pass.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879122", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879120, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "111265", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what information her Department holds on (a) severance and (b) compensation payments received by Lord Mandelson following the termination of his role as the UK Ambassador to ", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879120", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879065, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111264", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when will he lift the civil service recruitment controls in his department.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879065", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879059, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "111263", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what is the UK\u2019s contribution to the NATO special operations force.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879059", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879137, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111262", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to help support children in schools to develop their vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation and listening skills.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879137", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879108, "askingMemberId": 5085, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111261", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps his Department has taken to help support the decarbonisation of off-grid homes including the uptake of Hydrotreated Vegetable Oil in homes where heat-pump technology is not viable.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879108", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879104, "askingMemberId": 5085, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111260", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what estimate he has made of the number of off-grid homes in Wales that are not suitable for heat pump technology.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879104", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879103, "askingMemberId": 5085, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111259", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what estimate he has made of the number of jobs that will be created by the (a) Awel Y Mor and (b) The Erebus Project will be based in Wales.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879103", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879112, "askingMemberId": 5059, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111258", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of using wasted and stranded renewable energy to mine bitcoin as an alternative DSR capability.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879112", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878886, "askingMemberId": 5059, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111257", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what research he has undertaken into (a) inequalities in the criminal justice system and (b) the impact of DBS checks on those inequalities.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878886", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878885, "askingMemberId": 5059, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111256", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what demographic data in relation to ethnicity, gender and age his Department holds on convictions and cautions over the last 30 years.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878885", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879163, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111255", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of implementing the recommendations in the report Externalised asylum and migration policies and human rights law, published by th", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879163", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879043, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111254", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish a list of stakeholders that ministers have met to develop a best practice guidance for the use of Live Facial Recognition technology by the police.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879043", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879041, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111253", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to help ensure that data collected by live facial recognition technology cannot be accessed by foreign states.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879041", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879038, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111252", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department plans to take to ensure that data collected by live facial recognition will be stored safely.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879038", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879036, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111251", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to Part 3 of her Department's White paper entitled From local to national: a new model for policing White Paper, published on 26 January 2026, what her planned timetable is for the revi", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879036", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879035, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111250", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of aligning strategic authority mayoral boundaries with new regional policing boundaries.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879035", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879034, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111249", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to Part 3 of her Department's White paper entitled From local to national: a new model for policing White Paper, published on 26 January 2026, how many (a) strategic authority mayors an", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879034", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879033, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111248", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding has been allocated to Opal in the National Policing Intelligence Unit in each year since 2021.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879033", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879032, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111247", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her Department's White Paper entitled From local to national: a new model for policing, published on 26 January 2026, whether the funding announced for Opal is an yearly increase on ", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879032", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879031, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111246", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to Pillar 1 entitled Police Back on the Beat within the white paper entitled From local to national: a new model for policing, published on 27 January 2026, CP 1489, how many police off", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879031", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879030, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111245", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what are the current boundaries of operational independence for police forces.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879030", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879029, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111244", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to Section 22 of the Department's White Paper entitled From local to national: a new model for policing, published on 26 January 2026, how does her Department define dangerous behaviour", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879029", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879187, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111243", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of lowering the income threshold for the NHS salary sacrifice car scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879187", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879186, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111242", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what role local community safety groups will have in the consultation relating to the From local to national: a new model for policing white paper published on 26 January 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879186", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879183, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111241", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of current notification procedures for County Court Judgments; and whether he will make an assessment of the potential merits of requiring that all notifications of imp", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879183", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879181, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111240", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of requiring organisations to contribute to legal fees when (a) an unfair dismissal and (b) a discriminatory employment practice ha", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879181", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879179, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111239", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of penalties to deter organisations from discriminatory employment practices.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879179", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879177, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111238", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether his Department provides support to pregnant employees that have challenged their unfair dismissal and discriminatory employment practices that they have experienced.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879177", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879175, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111237", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps he has taken to ensure that employment protections for pregnant employees are legally enforceable.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879175", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879174, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111236", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to help support people with short and long-term spinal cord injuries.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879174", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878977, "askingMemberId": 5041, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "111235", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing a public interest assessment for large-scale acquisitions in the adult social care sector.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878977", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878976, "askingMemberId": 5041, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "111234", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the compatibility of offshore ownership of care assets in the United Kingdom on his Department's plans to introduce (a) a National Care Service and (b) neighbourhood-", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878976", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879166, "askingMemberId": 5040, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111233", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what her proposed timetable is for launching the consultation on the reform of weddings law in England and Wales; and what the proposed duration of that consultation will be.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879166", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879073, "askingMemberId": 5040, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111232", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidance his Department provides to local authorities on decisions affecting individuals with dementia who are already living in suitable care homes, once their capital falls below the adult s", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879073", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879153, "askingMemberId": 5032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "111231", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to respond to the letters of 7 October 2025 and 8 January 2026 from the hon. Member for Harrogate and Knaresborough with case reference TG09539.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879153", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879180, "askingMemberId": 5030, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111230", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to support networks of (a) clinicians and (b) health professionals who wish to share best practice on responding to domestic abuse.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879180", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879138, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111229", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of hospital handover delays on ambulance response times in (a) Shropshire and (b) the West Midlands.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879138", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879123, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111228", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when she will respond to Question 107479 regarding the Valuation Office Agency\u2019s valuation method for small independent hotels.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879123", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879121, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111227", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he will respond to Question 106613 of 16 January 2026 regarding the timely delivery of NHS mail to patients.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879121", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879117, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111226", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will take steps to provide self-employed workers who choose to adopt with the same support as employees who are entitled to statutory adoption pay.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879117", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879116, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111225", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the provision of parental allowance for self-employed workers who choose to adopt.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879116", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879006, "askingMemberId": 4864, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111224", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of a Substitute Teachers Register to help ensure supply teachers are not underpaid or maltreated by their employer.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879006", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878968, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "111223", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether she has had discussions with the Charity Commission on the potential use of religious charities by networks aligned with the Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878968", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878967, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "111222", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her polices of reports that religious centres in the UK are being used to (a) promote and (b) support the activ", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878967", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878966, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "111221", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to (a) make representations to the Iranian authorities on lifting the internet blackout and (b) assist Iranian citizens to stay connected ", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878966", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878964, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111220", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure modelled increases in expected deaths are not used to retroactively redefine excess mortality as normal.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878964", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878962, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111219", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the trends in the level of excess mortality above pre-2020 trends in the 50- to 64-year-old age group.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878962", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878883, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111218", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of research by Velez et al entitled New-Onset Mental Illness Among Gestational Carriers, published on 25 July 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878883", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878882, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111217", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of research from King\u2019s College London, Anglia Ruskin University and the University of Leeds entitled Comparing the Outcom", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878882", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879203, "askingMemberId": 4827, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111216", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if will make an assessment of the potential merits of (a) the introduction of a compensation scheme to support those facing financial hardship as a result of the delays in administering pensions and lump sums an", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879203", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879199, "askingMemberId": 4827, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111215", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what resources he has allocated to help ensure the timely and efficient processing of the 86,000 cases inherited by Capita from My CSP.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879199", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879058, "askingMemberId": 4824, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "111214", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the performance of Capita in delivering and administering the civil service pension scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879058", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879057, "askingMemberId": 4824, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "111213", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish the assessment criteria the Department uses to determine whether the supplier of externally-contracted services has been responsible for a critical performance failure in delivering its contra", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879057", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879200, "askingMemberId": 4799, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111212", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make it her policy to reverse the 2014 increase in subsidy for grouse moorlands.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879200", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879085, "askingMemberId": 4788, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111211", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what her planned timetable is for disbursing the humanitarian assistance package for El Fasher.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879085", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879088, "askingMemberId": 4787, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111210", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the oral contribution of the Chief Secretary to the Treasury in the urgent question on the resignation of the chair of the OBR at column 991, 3 December 2025, whether special advisers have been req", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879088", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879086, "askingMemberId": 4787, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111209", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the oral contribution of the Chief Secretary to the Treasury of 3 December 2025 on OBR: Resignation of Chair, Official Report, column 991, if she will provide an update on the progress of the leak ", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879086", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878918, "askingMemberId": 4783, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111208", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential impact of applying only one of the (a) RPI-linked uprating and (b) one-off tobacco duty increase scheduled to take effect from 1 October 2026 on inflati", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878918", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878917, "askingMemberId": 4783, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111207", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of the Office for Budget Responsibility\u2019s assessment of the impact of tobacco prices on CPI inflation in December 2025 on her (a) plan to apply an upra", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878917", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879111, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111206", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of current safeguards in place to protect NHS staff from patient assaults, and subsequent follow-up procedures.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879111", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879110, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111205", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the safeguards to protect mental health facility staff from patient assaults and subsequent follow-up procedures.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879110", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879080, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111204", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to promote community engagement on the new Air Navigation Guidance.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879080", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878991, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111203", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will set up a meeting between the Aviation Minister and the Hon. Members for Twickenham and Richmond Park following his correspondence referenced MC 00050628.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878991", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879134, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111202", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to improve the diagnosis rate for secondary breast cancer.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879134", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879119, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111201", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to help improve treatment pathways for patients with secondary breast cancer.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879119", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879077, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111200", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will outline a timeline he expects there to be standard treatment for recurrent glioblastoma available in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879077", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879076, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111199", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to support the development and approval of personalised cancer vaccines.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879076", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879075, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111198", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will outline the nature of the joint process between NICE and MHRA referenced in 2026 National Cancer Plan.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879075", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879074, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111197", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the commitment to explore novel procurement routes for diagnostics or treatments for rarer cancers contained in the 2026 National Cancer Plan includes assessing the suitability of the curre", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879074", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879204, "askingMemberId": 4716, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "111196", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when her Department plans to publish the results of its consultation on Out-of-school settings safeguarding which closed on 21 September 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879204", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879053, "askingMemberId": 4716, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "111195", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to answer 109832 of 4 February 2026 on Animal Welfare: Fines, what conversations she has had with the Leader of the House regarding the planned timetabling for the introductio", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879053", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879028, "askingMemberId": 4658, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111194", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if her Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of allowing partial refunds for overlapping immigration health surcharges in cases where the applicant has applied to (a) extend and (", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879028", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879027, "askingMemberId": 4658, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111193", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if her Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of reviewing the immigration health surcharge refund policy to allow for partial refunds to be made for periods of overlapping payment", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879027", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878910, "askingMemberId": 4657, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111192", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps her Department is taking to support research institutions in the period before UK Research and Innovation budget allocations are determined.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878910", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878908, "askingMemberId": 4657, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111191", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what applicant-led funding streams are available to medical researchers.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878908", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878907, "askingMemberId": 4657, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111190", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what funding schemes her Department provides for medical researchers.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878907", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879197, "askingMemberId": 4651, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111189", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his Department's policies of the analysis by Age UK on A&E wait times, published on 21 January 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879197", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879139, "askingMemberId": 4630, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111188", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how will property subject to tenancies agreed under (a) the Agricultural Holdings Act 1986 and (b) the Agricultural Tenancies Act 1995 be valued for the purposes of calculating an estate's inheritance tax liability.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879139", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879097, "askingMemberId": 4630, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111187", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps she is taking to help protect and support Kurdish communities in North-East Syria.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879097", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879096, "askingMemberId": 4630, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111186", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps she is taking to ensure equitable funding by the national wealth fund across all nations of the United Kingdom.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879096", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879092, "askingMemberId": 4630, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111185", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate she has made of the spending of the national wealth fund in Wales.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879092", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879113, "askingMemberId": 4623, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "111184", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 3 February 2026 to Question 109187 and Question 109186 on Religious Buildings: Wales, what additional funding was agreed with the Treasury to support the Places of Worsh", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879113", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879178, "askingMemberId": 4613, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111183", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2025 to Question 88303 on Prime Minister: Correspondence, what progress he has made on responding to the correspondence of 15 August 202", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879178", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879045, "askingMemberId": 4608, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111182", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when Home Office ministers or officials last met with Peter Mandelson; and what was discussed at that meeting.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879045", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879044, "askingMemberId": 4608, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111181", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, when Scotland Office ministers or officials last met with Peter Mandleson; and what was discussed at that meeting.", "answeringBodyId": 2, "answeringBodyName": "Scotland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879044", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879037, "askingMemberId": 4608, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111180", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether (a) Ministers and (b) officials in her Department had discussions with Peter Mandelson on the establishment of an inquiry into grooming gangs in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879037", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879127, "askingMemberId": 4598, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111179", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the proposed loan charge settlement scheme cut off date of 1 June 2021 for excluding taxpayers who have entered into contract settlements with HMRC before that date; a", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879127", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879106, "askingMemberId": 4573, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "111178", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what data his Department holds on the efficacy of the Housing First\u00a0pilots\u00a0on tenancy sustainment for people experiencing homelessness.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879106", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879109, "askingMemberId": 4521, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111177", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions she has had with the Welsh Government on the potential merits of introducing a Graduate Driving License scheme in Wales.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879109", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879214, "askingMemberId": 4500, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111176", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether (a) she or (b) any members of her Department met or corresponded with Lord Mandelson on Palantir.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879214", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879213, "askingMemberId": 4500, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111175", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether (a) she or (b) any members of her Department met or corresponded with Lord Mandelson on Palantir.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879213", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879212, "askingMemberId": 4500, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111174", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether (a) he or (b) any members of his Department met or corresponded with Lord Mandelson on Palantir.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879212", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879211, "askingMemberId": 4500, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111173", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether (a) he or (b) any members of his Department met with or corresponded with Lord Mandelson on Palantir.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879211", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878944, "askingMemberId": 4471, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111172", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the report from the All Party Parliamentary Group for Adoption and Permanence entitled Adoptee Voices, published on 28 January 2026, if she will take steps to provide (a) a safe space in schoo", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878944", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878943, "askingMemberId": 4471, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111171", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the report from the All Party Parliamentary Group for Adoption and Permanence entitled Adoptee Voices, published on 28 January 2026, if she will take steps to provide additional support for ad", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878943", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878942, "askingMemberId": 4471, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111170", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the report from the All Party Parliamentary Group for Adoption and Permanence entitled Adoptee Voices, published on 28 January 2026, if she will take steps with the Secretary of State for Heal", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878942", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878941, "askingMemberId": 4471, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111169", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the report from the All Party Parliamentary Group for Adoption and Permanence entitled Adoptee Voices, published on 28 January 2026, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of o", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878941", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878940, "askingMemberId": 4471, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111168", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the report from the All Party Parliamentary Group for Adoption and Permanence entitled Adoptee Voices, published on 28 January 2026, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of e", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878940", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879083, "askingMemberId": 4434, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "111167", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department is providing support to Capita to assist in clearing the backlog of Civil Service pension cases.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879083", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879082, "askingMemberId": 4434, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "111166", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he has had discussions with Capita on the administration of Civil Service pensions.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879082", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879081, "askingMemberId": 4434, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "111165", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2025 to Question 93760 on Driving Tests: Scotland, what progress she has made on the recruitment of driving examiners for driving test centres in (a) Arbroath and (b) Dunde", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879081", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878945, "askingMemberId": 4389, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111164", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many qualified driving test examiners were available to carry out tests in (a) September, (b) October, (c) November and (d) December 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878945", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879071, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111163", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the answer of 12 January 2026 to Question 101767 on Jeffery Epstein, what information her Department holds on Lord Mandelson's representations on the disposal of RBS Sempra Commodities to JP Morgan in 20", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879071", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879069, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111162", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, further to the comments by the Parliamentary Secretary to the Cabinet Office of 4 February 2026, Official Report, Column 372, on Lord Mandelson, if he will make it his policy to ensure that the letter from the C", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879069", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879068, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111161", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Humble Address passed by the House on 4 February 2026, Official Report, Column 374, whether (a) Ministers and (b) special advisers, will be (i) sighted or (ii) consulted on the redactions o", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879068", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879067, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111160", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what is the anticipated timetable for the Government to provide a substantive response to the Humble Address passed by the House on 4 February 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879067", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879066, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111159", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will list the dates that Morgan McSweeney had a meeting with Peter Mandelson whilst he was Ambassador to the United States, according to information held in (a) Mr Sweeney\u2019s Outlook diary in Downing Street", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879066", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879064, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111158", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, further to the comments by the Parliamentary Secretary to the Cabinet Office of 4 February 2026, Official Report, Columns 372, on Lord Mandelson, which KCs will be advising the Cabinet Secretary.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879064", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879063, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111157", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make it his policy to approach the US Department of Justice to request whether there are additional communications held by the Department, but which have not been publicly disclosed, between Jeffery E", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879063", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879062, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111156", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the answer of 2 February 2026 to Question 107710, on Erasmus+ programme: flags, whether any other Government programme in Great Britain will now be required to follow European Commission communicati", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879062", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879060, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111155", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which Government contracts were awarded to Palantir by direct award or without open competition since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879060", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879050, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111154", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what information her department holds on whether representatives of Global Counsel attended (a) meetings or (b) receptions in the Embassy in Washington, during the tenure of ", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879050", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879049, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111153", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether Peter Mandelson used a non-corporate communication device for government business whilst Ambassador to the United States.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879049", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879048, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111152", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what involvement Lord Mandelson had, whilst Ambassador to the United States, in relation to the Chagos Islands treaty.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879048", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879047, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111151", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether Peter Mandelson has retained a Civil Service pension during his tenure in the Senior Civil Service as Ambassador to the United States.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879047", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879046, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111150", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, pursuant to the answer of 30 January 2026, to Question 107377, on Jeffery Epstein, whether Lord Mandelson\u2019s private office files from 2009-10 will now be cross-referenced with the unauthorised disclosu", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879046", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879042, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111149", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, on which dates Peter Mandelson attended meetings at 10 Downing Street since 4 July 2024, according to records held by the Downing Street Visitor Notification Service database.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879042", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879039, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111148", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if she will make representations to her French counterpart to recommend the forfeiture of Peter Mandelson\u2019s decoration of the Legion of Honour.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879039", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879003, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111147", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February 2026 to Question 107710 on Erasmus+ programme: flags, whether the European Commission communication and visibility rules will apply to universities participating in the sche", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879003", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879002, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111146", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the answer of 2 February 2026, to Question 107710, on Erasmus+ programme: flags, which legal instrument sets out the European Commission communication and visibility rules.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879002", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879023, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111145", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what criteria his Department uses to decide whether to translate documents and communications into foreign languages.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879023", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879022, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111144", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his oral statement of 22 January 2026, Official Report, Column 486, on Local Government Reorganisation, whether he will reimburse councils for the administrativ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879022", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879021, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111143", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of the Greater London Authority supplementary business rate arising from increases in Rateable Values from the 2026 business", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879021", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879020, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111142", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the answer of 28 January 2026, to Question 107026, on Asylum: Housing, what criteria was used to select the range of local authorities to engage with on the new model", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879020", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879019, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111141", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the answer of 14 January 2026, to Question 103297, on Local Government Finance, whether areas where mayoral elections have been delayed will have access to any of the", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879019", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879018, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111140", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the answer of 19 January 2026 to Question 104668 on council tax, how county councils which are fire authorities and do not have separate fire precepts are treated for", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879018", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879017, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111139", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the answer of 20 January 2026 to Question 104669 on Business Rates, whether she has made an assessment of the potential impact of the increases in Rateable Values for (a) hotels and (b) pubs from the 202", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879017", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879012, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111138", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what information his Department holds on the (a) number, (b) total and (c) individual amount of local authority exit payments by authority in 2024-25.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879012", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879010, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111137", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the answer of 19 January 2026 to Question 104789 on Council Tax: Tax Yields, whether his Department has unpublished working estimates of the revenue from council tax ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879010", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879009, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111136", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the statistics entitled Local authority Council Taxbase in England 2025 (revised), 21 January 2026, for what reason there are some exceptions where the premium ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879009", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879008, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111135", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether core spending power figures published in the Local Government Finance assumes (a) that each principal local authority sets the maximum level of council tax that does not ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879008", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879007, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111134", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what his policy is on (a) further delaying or (b) cancelling under scheduled council elections in 2027 in areas with local government restructuring.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879007", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878993, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111133", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the Land Registry holds information on the numbers of sales of primary homes by local authority area in 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878993", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878992, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111132", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many Section 321 directions have been issued to allow for closed planning hearings in each of the last ten years.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878992", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878988, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111131", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the answer of 28 January 2026 to Question 107021 on Affordable Housing: Asylum, what types of accommodation, including (a) change of use, (b) HMOs, (c) hotels or comm", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878988", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878986, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111130", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether there is a tracker document for the (a) pipeline and (b) applications in relation to the 150 national infrastructure application target.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878986", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878984, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111129", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the British High Commission Islamabad news story of 17 April 2025, which individuals and external organisations Lord Khan met during his visit to the (a) Overse", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878984", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878983, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111128", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the answer of 13 January 2026 to Question 103186 on Asylum: Council Housing, if he will publish the information or guidance given to participating local authorities o", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878983", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878982, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111127", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the answer of 14 January 2026 to Question 103284 on Council Tax: Warwick, whether a local authority must undertake an impact assessment before introducing a second ho", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878982", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878981, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111126", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has had discussions with the Greater London Authority on extending the 2026 (a) pubs and live music relief and (b) revaluation transitional relief to inclu", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878981", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879056, "askingMemberId": 4360, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111125", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how the Davies Group is tracking and reporting costs associated with delays in case progression.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879056", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879055, "askingMemberId": 4360, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111124", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, to outline the average turnaround time for resolution in Hearing Loss Cases in each of the four regions of the United Kingdom.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879055", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879054, "askingMemberId": 4360, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111123", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, to detail the longest outstanding case with the MOD/Davies group relating to Hearing Loss.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879054", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879052, "askingMemberId": 4360, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111122", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, to provide the costs of Hearing Loss Claims in last 5 years to the MOD, including damages, costs and costs per case.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879052", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879051, "askingMemberId": 4360, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111121", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, to provide the annual cost of the contract with the Davies Group for the last 5 years for managing all MOD civil claims.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879051", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878904, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111120", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what arrangements are in place to support UK travellers and airlines when Gibraltar-bound flights are diverted to Schengen territory and passengers are refused entry.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878904", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878903, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111119", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what aspects of the implementation of the UK-EU Gibraltar treaty she considers non-negotiable; and how this negotiating position will protect UK citizens and Gibraltar reside", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878903", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879189, "askingMemberId": 4084, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111118", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2026 to Question 109089 on Coronavirus: Research, when the UK Health Security Agency requested the report.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879189", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878939, "askingMemberId": 4074, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111117", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people on the basic State Pension have inherited part of the additional State Pension from their deceased spouse or partner.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878939", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878922, "askingMemberId": 4074, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111116", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people receive the basic state pension and the additional state pension.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878922", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878915, "askingMemberId": 4032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111115", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of uprating Pension Protection Fund compensation for members who lost indexation from April 1997, to reflect the value their pensions would have", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878915", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878914, "askingMemberId": 4032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111114", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that Plan 2 student loan borrowers are informed of the changes to repayment thresholds due to take effect in April 2027.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878914", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878913, "askingMemberId": 4032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111113", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department has conducted an equality impact assessment on the freeze to the Plan 2 student loan repayment threshold due to take effect in April 2027.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878913", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878912, "askingMemberId": 4032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111112", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the potential impact of the freeze to the repayment threshold from April 2027 on average annual repayments for Plan 2 student loan borrowers.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878912", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878911, "askingMemberId": 4032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111111", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of freezing the Plan 2 student loan repayment threshold from April 2027 on existing student loan borrowers.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878911", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878901, "askingMemberId": 4008, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111110", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the (a) adequacy of regulation and (b) level of trade body membership of funeral service providers contracted by local authorities for provision of services that fall outside of a l", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878901", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879193, "askingMemberId": 4005, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111109", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the UK and Eire Glaucoma Society 2025 consensus on Minimally Invasive Glaucoma Surgery, whether he has made an assessment of the potential impact on secondary care services when p", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879193", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879192, "askingMemberId": 4005, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111108", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the UK and Eire Glaucoma Society 2025 consensus on Minimally Invasive Glaucoma Surgery, what estimate he has made of the number of glaucoma patients who weren't offered a combined", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879192", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879105, "askingMemberId": 3973, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111107", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make an estimate of the number of civilian seafarers in scope of the (a) Defence Maritime Regulator and (b) the Memorandum of Understanding between the MoD and the Maritime and Coastguard Agency.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879105", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879095, "askingMemberId": 3973, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111106", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department applies the provisions of the Maritime Labour Convention to the (a) merchant navy seafarers and (b) vessels in the Royal Fleet Auxiliary.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879095", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879094, "askingMemberId": 3973, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111105", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) inspection dates and (b) deficiencies recorded were by officials from the Maritime and Coastguard Agency following inspection of Royal Fleet Auxiliary vessels in each year since 2014.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879094", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879093, "askingMemberId": 3973, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111104", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many inspections of Royal Fleet Auxiliary vessels have been carried out by officials from the Maritime and Coastguard Agency since the updated Memorandum of Understanding was published in November 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879093", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879091, "askingMemberId": 3973, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111103", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how he plans to measure progress on increasing public sector insourcing.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879091", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879090, "askingMemberId": 3973, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111102", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential implications for its policies of the report by the Institute of Alcohol Studies entitled Now You See It, Now You Don't, published on 29 Janu", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879090", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879126, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "111101", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2026 to Question 102744 on Hospitality Industry and Retail Trade: Business Rates, what estimate she has made for the total business rates liability for the current set of propert", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879126", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879182, "askingMemberId": 3935, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111100", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make it her policy to publish the total business rates receipts from all pubs for each financial year from 2023-24 to 2029-30.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879182", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879026, "askingMemberId": 1593, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111099", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that the proposed expansion of the UK Emissions Trading Scheme to international maritime voyages is not in addition to the International Maritime Organisation\u2019s exp", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879026", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879025, "askingMemberId": 1593, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111098", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues and the Northern Irish Government on using funds raised by the expansion of the UK Emissions Trading Scheme to maritime to support maritime", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879025", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879024, "askingMemberId": 1593, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111097", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what analysis her Department has undertaken on the potential impact of the UK Emissions Trading Scheme expansion to maritime on the competitiveness of Northern Irish ports in attracting cruise business.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879024", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879061, "askingMemberId": 1521, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "111096", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether regional cost-of-living variations will be factored into proposed maintenance grant calculations.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879061", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878990, "askingMemberId": 1512, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111095", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with the Royal Mail's on its ability to deliver outgoing and returned postal votes.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878990", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878989, "askingMemberId": 1512, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111094", "questionText": "To ask the Right hon. Member for Kenilworth and Southam, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what discussions he has had with the Royal Mail's on its ability to deliver outgoing and returned postal votes.", "answeringBodyId": 36, "answeringBodyName": "Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878989", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878887, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111093", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions he has had with (a) Ministerial colleagues and (b) external partners on the 25-year conservation plan for Akrotiri Salt Lake in the Sovereign Base Areas of Akrotiri and Dhekelia.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878887", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879070, "askingMemberId": 1211, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111092", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether her Department will provide \u00a350 million per year, for the next two years, to the Global Polio Eradication Initiative.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879070", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879084, "askingMemberId": 410, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111091", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what is the average time taken to complete a mandatory reconsideration for a Disability Living Allowance for Children.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879084", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879040, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111090", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if she will publish official communications from the US State Department sent in March 2025 on the legal premise for transferring the sovereignty of the Chagos Islands to Mau", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879040", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879173, "askingMemberId": 227, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111089", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to help ensure that bereaved families are treated equitably within the compensation scheme and retain a route to seek recognition of the full extent of injuries suffered by their relative", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879173", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879172, "askingMemberId": 227, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111088", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether an equality impact assessment has been undertaken of the eligibility criteria for the proposed Special Category Mechanism.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879172", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879171, "askingMemberId": 227, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111087", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Infected Blood Compensation Authority will accept a range of evidence for assessing injuries suffered by deceased victims - including medical, social care, police, employment and family records, and ", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879171", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879170, "askingMemberId": 227, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111086", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the consultation undertaken on the proposed Special Category Mechanism was assessed against (a) the Gunning Principles and (b) the Cabinet Office Consultation Principles, including requirements relating ", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879170", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879169, "askingMemberId": 227, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111085", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department has taken to help facilitate the participation of bereaved families and representatives of deceased victims in the Technical Expert Group consultation on the Special Category Mechanism;", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879169", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879168, "askingMemberId": 227, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111084", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he will set out the evidential routes through which the estates of deceased infected individuals will be able to seek compensation for psychological injuries experienced before death, including in cases ", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879168", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879167, "askingMemberId": 227, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111083", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the compensation proposals for the estates of infected individuals who died before the establishment of Infected Blood Support Schemes in 2017; and whether ", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879167", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879165, "askingMemberId": 227, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111082", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the consistency of the proposed Special Category Mechanism with the recommendations of the Infected Blood Inquiry.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879165", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1879164, "askingMemberId": 227, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111081", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Government\u2019s proposed Special Category Mechanism on access to enhanced awards and appeals for infected and affected people, including individuals who we", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1879164", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878744, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111080", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his assessment is of the effectiveness of Reciprocal Enforcement of Maintenance Orders.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878744", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878671, "askingMemberId": 5403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111079", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reason the disabled persons bus pass is only valid after 9:30am on weekdays.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878671", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878490, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111078", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of local authority expenditure on asylum-related social care in 2025-26 and 2026-27.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878490", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878489, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111077", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what information his Department holds on (a) changes in local authority spending on social care for asylum seekers between 2019-20 and 2024-25 and (b) the reasons for those chang", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878489", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878488, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111076", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the cost to local authorities was of providing social care to asylum seekers in each financial year since 2019-20 by (a) adults, (b) children in families and (c) unaccompani", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878488", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878473, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111075", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to provide a response to Question 93556 on Schools: Standards, tabled on 21 November 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878473", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878393, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111074", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, with reference to his Department\u2019s press release entitled UK lenders step up with \u00a311 billion push to back British businesses, published on 26 January 2026, what assessment he has made of the level of ", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878393", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878392, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111073", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, pursuant to his Department\u2019s press release entitled \u2018UK lenders step up with \u00a311 billion push to back British businesses\u2019 published on 26 January 2026, what steps he is taking to ensure businesses with", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878392", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878391, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111072", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, with reference to his Department\u2019s press release entitled UK lenders step up with \u00a311 billion push to back British businesses, published on 26 January 2026, whether the \u00a311 billion lending commitment r", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878391", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878390, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111071", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, with reference to his Department\u2019s press release entitled UK lenders step up with \u00a311 billion push to back British businesses, published on 26 January 2026, how much of the \u00a311 billion lending package ", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878390", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878389, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111070", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, with reference to his Department\u2019s press release entitled UK lenders step up with \u00a311 billion push to back British businesses, published on 26 January 2026, over what time period the \u00a311 billion lendin", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878389", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878385, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111069", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what lessons his Department has learnt from other countries that have reduced curtailment while expanding renewables.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878385", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878384, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111068", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what recent estimate his Department has made of the proportion of curtailment costs borne by domestic consumers.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878384", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878383, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111067", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what recent assessment he has made of the role of battery storage in reducing renewable curtailment.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878383", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878382, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111066", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of whether curtailment payments create incentives to locate generation in areas with insufficient grid capacity.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878382", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878381, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111065", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps he is taking to ensure that the expansion of renewable generation does not lead to higher electricity bills for consumers.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878381", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878380, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111064", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the compatibility of his Clean Power 2030 target with current grid capacity constraints.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878380", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878379, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111063", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what measures are in place to limit curtailment costs during the period before new grid infrastructure becomes operational.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878379", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878378, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111062", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what the expected completion dates are for major new transmission projects intended to reduce renewable curtailment.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878378", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878377, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111061", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how often gas-fired power stations were used to replace curtailed renewable generation in 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878377", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878376, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111060", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what recent assessment he has made of the impact of curtailment payments on average household energy bills in 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878376", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878375, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111059", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what estimate his Department has made of curtailment costs to electricity billpayers in 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878375", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878609, "askingMemberId": 5357, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111058", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent discussions she has had with (a) her Israeli counterpart, (b) the Commonwealth War Graves Commission and (c) the Royal British Legion on the bulldozing of parts o", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878609", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878600, "askingMemberId": 5356, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "111057", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent steps he has taken to help support (a) safeguarding reform in Northern Ireland and (b) cross-border learning with safeguarding regulators in England, Scotland and Wales under the Four Nations", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878600", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878604, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111056", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what discussions his Department has had with (a) Waverley Borough Council and (b) East Hampshire District Council on the provision of Suitable Alternative Natural Greenspaces and", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878604", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878602, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111055", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department collects or holds data on the number of residential planning permissions that cannot be implemented due to a lack of available Suitable Alternative Natural", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878602", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878601, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111054", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the availability of Suitable Alternative Natural Greenspace capacity within local planning authorities covering the (a) Thames Basin Heaths, (b) ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878601", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878497, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111053", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether his Department plans to undertake an assessment of the potential economic impacts on (i) Cornwall, and (ii) the wider UK economy, arising from capacity constraints in the commercial laundry sec", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878497", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878496, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111052", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment her Department has made of the role of commercial laundries in the resilience of the hospitality supply chain, including the extent to which hotels and the wider hospitality secto", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878496", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878494, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111051", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the resilience of NHS services to disruptions within the commercial laundry sector.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878494", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878492, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111050", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment his Department has made of the potential contribution of the commercial laundry industry to the economy.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878492", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878727, "askingMemberId": 5341, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111049", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to reduce gynaecology waiting lists, which include those who need a diagnosis of, and treatment for, endometriosis.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878727", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878552, "askingMemberId": 5341, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111048", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding he plans to provide for treatments for secondary breast cancer in each of the next three years.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878552", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878577, "askingMemberId": 5339, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111047", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to manage conflicts of interest associated with alcohol industry involvement in public health policy.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878577", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878575, "askingMemberId": 5339, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111046", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing restrictions on alcohol in line with existing restrictions on the marketing of less healthy food and drink.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878575", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878573, "askingMemberId": 5339, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111045", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to develop a new national alcohol strategy for England.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878573", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878449, "askingMemberId": 5302, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111044", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to ensure the widest set of projects as part of biodiversity net-gain calculations.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878449", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878448, "askingMemberId": 5302, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111043", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department has taken with Homes England to help support start-up builders.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878448", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878474, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111042", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding was allocated to dementia research by (a) the National Institute for Health and Care Research and (b) UK Research and Innovation in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878474", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878441, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111041", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the length of time medical malpractice legal proceedings take to complete on (a) families and (b) staff.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878441", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878440, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111040", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of trends in the number of court sitting days on the Crown Court backlog.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878440", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878439, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111039", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which (a) professional bodies and (b) legal organisations his Department consulted prior to the publication of proposals to restrict jury trials; and what alternative measures his Department has considered to red", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878439", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878437, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111038", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he plans to reform powers in relation to Strategic Litigation Against Public Participation cases.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878437", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878663, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111037", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether her Department has made an estimate with the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport of the additional costs incurred by musicians seeking to perform in the European Union due to delays in the issuan", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878663", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878661, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111036", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many applications for Musical Instrument Certificates from touring musicians were outstanding at the end of each calendar year since 2021.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878661", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878660, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111035", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the average length of time taken to issue Musical Instrument Certificates to touring musicians was in each calendar year since 2021.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878660", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878659, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111034", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many A1 form applications from touring musicians were outstanding at the end of each year since 2021.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878659", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878658, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111033", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average length of time taken to issue A1 forms to touring musicians was in each year since 2021.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878658", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878507, "askingMemberId": 5283, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111032", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether Appendix ECAA visa holders will be affected by retrospective changes to settlement requirements.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878507", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878451, "askingMemberId": 5277, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111031", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 12 January 2026 to Question 103618, when the Armed Forces Foundation Year Scheme placement details will be finalised.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878451", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878396, "askingMemberId": 5273, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111030", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of introducing zonal electricity pricing on (a) consumer energy bills in regions with high renewable generation, such as those ", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878396", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878395, "askingMemberId": 5273, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111029", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 20 October 2025 to Question 77869 on Teachers: Disclosure of Information, whether her Department plans to consider the experiences of teachers subject to non-disclosure agreements in s", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878395", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878394, "askingMemberId": 5273, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111028", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of introducing a railcard for adults over the age of 30 who rely on regular rail travel for work in (a) the north and (b) other areas of England; ", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878394", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878690, "askingMemberId": 5265, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111027", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how his Department plans to replace the batch 1 River Class of ships.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878690", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878669, "askingMemberId": 5265, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111026", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 6 May 2025 to Question 48851 on Reserve Forces: Finance, what assessment he has made of the level of available reserve service days; and what steps his Department is taking to increase t", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878669", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878537, "askingMemberId": 5265, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111025", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the number and proportion of the capability requirements that Ajax-family Capability Drop 4 vehicles will fully comply with.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878537", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878536, "askingMemberId": 5265, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111024", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what proportion of the capability requirements have Ajax-family Capability Drop 3 vehicles been verified to fully comply with.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878536", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878535, "askingMemberId": 5265, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111023", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many of the Capability Drop 3 Ajax-family vehicles that have undergone acceptance testing by the Joint Acceptance Group required concessions against specifications or contractual requirements to be submitted ", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878535", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878534, "askingMemberId": 5265, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111022", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what proportion of the original capability requirements specified for the Ajax-family vehicles have been relaxed or amended due to an inability of the vehicles to meet the original requirements.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878534", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878511, "askingMemberId": 5263, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-25T00:00:00", "uin": "111021", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of regional differences in the (a) availability, (b) accessibility and (c) resourcing of NHS Long COVID assessment and treatment services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878511", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878533, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111020", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she plans to require in-vehicle CCTV in licensed taxis and private hire vehicles.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878533", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878458, "askingMemberId": 5248, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111019", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how many workers applied to the Oil and Gas Transition Training Fund during the pilot programme; and what estimate he has made of the number of workers who will be supported by the Oil and Ga", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878458", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878374, "askingMemberId": 5248, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111018", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of trends in the availability of flexible, remote or hybrid working on mothers with childcare responsibilities, including in Basingstoke; whether he h", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878374", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878445, "askingMemberId": 5227, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111017", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps she is taking to help ensure that genocide is not committed in the Occupied Palestinian Territories.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878445", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878450, "askingMemberId": 5225, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111016", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress she has made on a strategy for integrating bus ticketing in England.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878450", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878454, "askingMemberId": 5208, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111015", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how much funding within the consolidated low income household energy efficiency scheme will be ringfenced for community level low carbon heat technologies, including (a) Shared Ground Loops a", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878454", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878453, "askingMemberId": 5208, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111014", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what proportion of funding in the consolidated low income household energy efficiency scheme will be allocated to (a) private sector homes and (b) social housing properties.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878453", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878670, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111013", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what assessment he has made of the trends in the level of foreign acquisition of UK technology companies in the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878670", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878668, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111012", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, how many UK technology startups and scale-ups were acquired by foreign companies in each of the last three years; and what the total value of those acquisitions was in each of the last three years.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878668", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878664, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "111011", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, how many UK technology company acquired by foreign buyers were of (a) pre-revenue startups and (b) companies with revenues (i) under \u00a310 million, (ii) between \u00a310-50 million and (iii) \u00a350 million in th", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878664", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878682, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111010", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of local authorities' guidance on how to (a) assess or (b) identify (i) dyslexia or (ii) support literacy dif?culties.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878682", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878677, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111009", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the phonics screener for the early identification of dyslexia in primary schools.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878677", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878672, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111008", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she had made of the potential implications for her policies of the British Dyslexia Association's report entitled Lost in the system: Councils\u2019 blind spot on dyslexia, published on 3 February 20", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878672", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878648, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111007", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to increase training on Personal, Social, Health and Economic education for teachers in Yeovil constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878648", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878647, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111006", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of changing the national curriculum to increase awareness of cancer prevention amongst pupils in Yeovil constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878647", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878645, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111005", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to raise awareness amongst men in Yeovil constituency about the risks of breast cancer.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878645", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878644, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111004", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of people walking on (a) cancer prevention and (b) cancer recovery.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878644", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878642, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111003", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to expand screening programmes for cancer in Yeovil constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878642", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878640, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111002", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of reducing the starting age for routine mammograms to 40.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878640", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878636, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111001", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that people over the age of 71 can request a breast cancer screening in Yeovil constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878636", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878627, "askingMemberId": 5171, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "111000", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she will take to assess passenger affordability when setting rail fares.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878627", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878626, "askingMemberId": 5171, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110999", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how the Railways Bill will support improved connectivity for communities currently without such links.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878626", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878625, "askingMemberId": 5171, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110998", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how the Railways Bill will ensure that access rights to the network are fair, transparent and enforceable, particularly where Great British Rail will both manage infrastructure and operate services.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878625", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878624, "askingMemberId": 5171, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110997", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Railways Bill will set out the duties of the Great British Railways.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878624", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878457, "askingMemberId": 5170, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110996", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information her Department holds on the amount of Theatre Tax Relief for Corporation Tax provided to Scottish Companies over the last two tax years.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878457", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878444, "askingMemberId": 5156, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110995", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to develop a National Trauma Strategy for England.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878444", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878585, "askingMemberId": 5150, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110994", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to answer Question 107246 tabled on 20th January 2026, regarding safeguarding issues and Academies.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878585", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878422, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110993", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to revise his Department\u2019s autism strategy when the current one expires in July 2026, in the context of the provisions of section 1 of the Autism Act 2009.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878422", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878641, "askingMemberId": 5140, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110992", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many residential fires caused by lithium-ion battery failure were recorded by Fire and Rescue Services in 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878641", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878638, "askingMemberId": 5140, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110991", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of UK Conformity Assessed marking requirements for lithium-ion batteries used in e-bikes and e-scooters; and what steps he is taking to ensure th", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878638", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878434, "askingMemberId": 5140, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "110990", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of maintaining thresholds for Plan 2 student loan repayments on trends in the level of repayments made by graduates; and what discussions she has ", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878434", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878435, "askingMemberId": 5138, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110989", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of battery-electric trains for passenger rail lines.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878435", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878485, "askingMemberId": 5128, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110988", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of proposed police reforms on the integration of Mayoral Combined Authorities and Police and Crime Commissioners.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878485", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878550, "askingMemberId": 5122, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "110987", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what consideration he has given to amending the NHS Charges to Overseas Visitors Regulations 2015 to remove the exclusion of assisted conception services for Ukrainian nationals who are lawfully re", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878550", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878549, "askingMemberId": 5122, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "110986", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, for what reason assisted conception services are excluded from the exemption from NHS charges for people in the UK under (a) the Homes for Ukraine and (b) Ukraine Permission to Extend visa schemes.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878549", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878501, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110985", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what process her Department uses for (a) approving and (b) being consulted on pilot deployments of AI-enabled policing tools that integrate sensitive personal data; and what criteria are used to asses", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878501", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878500, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110984", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what role her Department has in (a) overseeing and (b) advising on pilot deployments of novel AI systems that process sensitive personal data in policing.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878500", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878499, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110983", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether her Department (a) maintains and (b) plans to maintain a register of AI systems across government.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878499", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878498, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110982", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what standards her Department sets for the ethical and technical assurance of AI systems used in law enforcement.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878498", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878546, "askingMemberId": 5103, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110981", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on what date the Government intends to launch the public consultation on wedding law reform.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878546", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878447, "askingMemberId": 5103, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110980", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with the Home Office on fire safety and the use of flammable materials in indoor entertainment venues.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878447", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878446, "askingMemberId": 5103, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110979", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether he has considered introducing a ban on the use of indoor pyrotechnics in nightclubs.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878446", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878743, "askingMemberId": 5090, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110978", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the requirement to have GCSEs to enter apprenticeships on young people with disabilities, learning difficulties and neurodivergence.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878743", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878742, "askingMemberId": 5090, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110977", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what support she is providing to students who want to pursue a creative course for further education but cannot due to not obtaining English and Maths GCSEs despite resits.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878742", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878741, "askingMemberId": 5090, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110976", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to support young people pursuing apprenticeships who are unable to obtain English and Maths GCSEs; and what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the requirement to o", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878741", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878739, "askingMemberId": 5090, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110975", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has made an assessment of the potential impact of the requirement to resit Maths and English GCSEs until passing on young people starting their careers and pursuing vocational further education and ", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878739", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878711, "askingMemberId": 5090, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110974", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in each of the last 5 years, a) how many complaints have been made to his Department, b) how many of those complaints\u00a0have been referred to the Independent Case Examiner, and c) how many of those referr", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878711", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878709, "askingMemberId": 5090, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110973", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in each of the last 5 years, a) how many complaints to his Department have resulted in a consolatory payment being made to benefit recipients in recognition of delays or errors made by DWP; and b) what ", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878709", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878698, "askingMemberId": 5090, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110972", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what role the UK Government is playing internationally to support equitable access to long-acting HIV prevention technologies, including long-acting PrEP, in low-income setti", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878698", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878695, "askingMemberId": 5090, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110971", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, how the Government is working with international partners to ensure that new HIV prevention technologies are affordable and accessible to populations most at risk.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878695", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878693, "askingMemberId": 5090, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110970", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that funding reductions do not undermine progress towards ending AIDS as a public health threat by 2030.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878693", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878692, "askingMemberId": 5090, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110969", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions she has had with international partners on protecting global HIV funding and increasing progress towards ending AIDS by 2030.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878692", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878689, "askingMemberId": 5090, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110968", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether he has made an assessment of the adequacy of the regularity of identity verification for businesses and shops possibly operating illegally.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878689", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878679, "askingMemberId": 5090, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110967", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps she is taking maximise the public sharing of evidence on which assertions by the VOA are made; and how the VOA's duty to taxpayer confidentiality will be used when responding to queries.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878679", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878676, "askingMemberId": 5090, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110966", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps she is taking to ensure transparency in the work of the VOA.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878676", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878736, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110965", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to page 16 of the Police reform white paper \u201cFrom Local to National: A New Model for Policing\u201d (CP1489), by when will she establish a new Performance Unit in the Home Office.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878736", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878735, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110964", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the answer of 3 February 2026, to question 108369 on Armoured Fighting Vehicles: Procurement, on what date was the project cancelled.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878735", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878734, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110963", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what is the full scope of Project Goshawk.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878734", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878733, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110962", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what is the full scope of Project Troubler.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878733", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878731, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110961", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to page 13 of the Police reform white paper \u201cFrom Local to National: A New Model for Policing\u201d (CP1489), by when will she publish her new Fraud Strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878731", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878730, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110960", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to page 13 of the Police reform white paper \u201cFrom Local to National: A New Model for Policing\u201d (CP1489), what will be the location of the new National Centre for AI in Policing.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878730", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878729, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110959", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many pre-existing foodbanks have been brought into official statistics each year since 2010.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878729", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878472, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110958", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information his Department holds on the criteria for foodbanks to be included within official foodbank statistics.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878472", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878471, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110957", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what information his Department holds on the full scope of Project Goldweed.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878471", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878470, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110956", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what information his Department holds on the full scope of Project Lily.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878470", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878469, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110955", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what information his Department holds on the full scope of Project Upham.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878469", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878468, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110954", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what information his Department holds on the scope of the Royal Navy\u2019s Eagles Eye trials in relation to the development of a naval aviation hybrid air wing.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878468", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878467, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110953", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 30 January 2026 to Question 107819 on Military Intelligence, what was the (a) cost and (b) start date of the existing multi-year contract with Google for Secret-level cloud hosting and d", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878467", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878466, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110952", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his proposed timetable is for producing the first Ajax-family vehicles at Capability Drop 4 standard.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878466", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878465, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110951", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what information his Department holds on the vetting process related to the appointment of Lord Mandelson as the UK Ambassador to the United States.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878465", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878464, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110950", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what information his Department holds that was provided by the (a) security and (b) intelligence services regarding the appointment of Lord Mandelson as the UK Ambassador to the United States.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878464", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878463, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110949", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what information her Department holds on (a) the official termination date of Lord Mandelson as the UK Ambassador to the United States of America and (b) the last day Lord Ma", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878463", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878462, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110948", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which a) current or b) former Government Ministers were involved in the appointment of Lord Mandelson as the UK Ambassador to the United States.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878462", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878403, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110947", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the terror threat posed by the forthcoming Universal Studios theme park on (a) traffic, (b) firearms and (c) neighbourhood policing in the tri-f", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Universal Studios: Bedfordshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878403", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878402, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110946", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which Royal Navy project is working to harness AI through machine-speed, data-centric decision making to improve the decision action cycle.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Navy: Artificial Intelligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878402", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878667, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110945", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if her Department has made any assessment of the merits of introducing national tracking of looked-after children and previously looked-after children on health waiting lists.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878667", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878662, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110944", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has has with (i) the Royal College of Paediatrics and Child Health, (ii) the Children's Commissioner, (iii) the Local Government Association and (iv) Adoption UK on waiting time", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878662", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878656, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110943", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether NHS England holds data on the number of (i) current and (ii) previously looked-after children on waiting lists for (a) mental health services and (b) neurodevelopmental assessments.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878656", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878586, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110942", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of recommendations 11 and 12 of the Nuclear Regulatory Review on the level playing field provisions in the EU-UK Trade and Cooperation Agre", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878586", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878665, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110941", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to answer 104272 of 14 January on Child Benefit, how many of the 5,637 enquiries which remained open have since been addressed; and what the outcomes were.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878665", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878653, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110940", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to help ensure that people that do not use TV or radio services do not receive incorrect correspondence about TV licensing.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878653", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878510, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110939", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the written Answer of 29 January 2025 to Question 108043 on Roads: Wildlife, if she will amend Section 170 of the Road Traffic Act 1988 to reclassify cats to ensure drivers are required to stop and ", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878510", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878482, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110938", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information her Department holds on how Ofwat calculates the cap on which water companies can increase water bills for customers.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878482", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878579, "askingMemberId": 5070, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110937", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the number of complaints received by NHS Trusts relating to end of life care priorities in hospitals; and what assessment he has made of the adequacy of (a)", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878579", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878680, "askingMemberId": 5067, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "110936", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what commemorations are being planned to mark the 100th anniversary of the passing of the Representation of the People Act 1928.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878680", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878456, "askingMemberId": 5065, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110935", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that road freight trade associations will be included on the road safety Expert Advisory Panel.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878456", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878455, "askingMemberId": 5065, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110934", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what criteria will be used to determine membership of the road safety Expert Advisory Panel.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878455", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878584, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110933", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many Sharia law courts have operated in the UK in each year since 2010 and broken down by local authority area.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878584", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878583, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110932", "questionText": "To ask the Solicitor General,?what information his Department holds on the number of people that have been prosecuted for honour-based offences broken down by (a) local authority area and (b) category of offence in each year since 2010.", "answeringBodyId": 88, "answeringBodyName": "Attorney General", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878583", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878582, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110931", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many illegal marriages have been recorded in each year since 2010, broken down by local authority area.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878582", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878581, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110930", "questionText": "To ask the Solicitor General,?what information his Department holds on the number of people that have been prosecuted for facilitating forced marriages in each year since 2010 and broken down by local authority area.", "answeringBodyId": 88, "answeringBodyName": "Attorney General", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878581", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878580, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110929", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many charges were laid under Prison rule 51 relating specifically to aggravation towards a protected characteristic of (a) race, (b) religion and (c) belief in the last year where data exists; and how many of", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878580", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878578, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110928", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which faith-based (a) charities and (b) organisations are permitted to visit prisons.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878578", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878576, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110927", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress has been made by law enforcement on apprehending those responsible for the Legal Aid Agency cyber attack.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878576", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878574, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110926", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Written Statement of 22 January 2026 on Response to Legal Aid Agency cyber attack, HCWS1265, how much funding will be allocated to the transformation programme for Legal Aid Agency digital s", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878574", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878572, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110925", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many legal aid cases there were in each month since 23 April 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878572", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878571, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110924", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to Answer of 22 December 2025 to Question 100065 on Legal Aid Scheme, how many legal aid providers have left the market in total since 23 April 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878571", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878570, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110923", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what representations he has received from counterparts in Five Eyes countries that do not have a statutory duty of candour.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878570", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878569, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110922", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of introducing a statutory duty of candour on (a) military intelligence and (b) Special Forces.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878569", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878568, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110921", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Defence on the effectiveness of introducing a statutory duty of candour on the military.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878568", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878547, "askingMemberId": 5054, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110920", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to (a) publish for pre-legislative scrutiny and (b) introduce the Defence Readiness Bill in (i) 2026, (ii) 2027, (iii) 2028 and (iv) 2029.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878547", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878431, "askingMemberId": 5051, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110919", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she made of the potential implications for her policies of trends in the level of coral bleaching; and what steps she is taking with Cabinet colleagues to help tackle c", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878431", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878651, "askingMemberId": 5040, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110918", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of Making Tax Digital on the childminding sector.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878651", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878548, "askingMemberId": 5040, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110917", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what discussions his Department has had with relevant stakeholders on the creation of memorials to recognise war-time ammunition factory workers.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878548", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878513, "askingMemberId": 5034, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "110916", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of funding under the (a) Landscape Recovery and (b) Countryside Stewardship Higher Tier scheme has been received by farms smaller than 200 acres.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878513", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878509, "askingMemberId": 5034, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "110915", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of including wraparound extensions within permitted development rights for householders.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878509", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878508, "askingMemberId": 5034, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "110914", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of salary differences between college lecturers and school teachers on recruitment to further education teaching posts for (a) construction", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878508", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878506, "askingMemberId": 5034, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "110913", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent progress her Department has made on aligning the Fish Export Service with the EU CATCH system.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878506", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878505, "askingMemberId": 5034, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "110912", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent progress her Department has made on digitising the catch certificate scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878505", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878646, "askingMemberId": 5028, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110911", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the (a) retention of DVSA employed driving test examiners and (b) pay of DVSA driving test examiners in comparison to the earnings of private sector driving instr", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878646", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878643, "askingMemberId": 5028, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110910", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the (a) average and (b) longest waiting time was for a driving test in each of the the test centres in the North East region in each of the last ten years.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878643", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878718, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110909", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps she is taking to encourage alternative providers to use the broadband infrastructure installed by Freedom Fibre in North Shropshire constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878718", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878717, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110908", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many new telecommunications masts have been built for the Emergency Services Network in (a) total (b) Shropshire and (c) North Shropshire constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878717", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878716, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110907", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will set out (a) when and (b) in which locations the Emergency Services Network has been used in an operational setting.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878716", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878715, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110906", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the public purse of (a) the Airwave network and (b) the Emergency Services Network was in each of the last five financial years.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878715", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878714, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110905", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what data her department holds on the number of incidents where emergency service response times have been impacted by communication network coverage.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878714", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878713, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110904", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what data her department holds on the (a) quality and (b) availability of the Airwave network in (i) Shropshire and (ii) North Shropshire.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878713", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878712, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110903", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of Airwave network coverage for emergency service delivery in rural areas.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878712", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878433, "askingMemberId": 4874, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110902", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what plans her Department has to support the development of satellite based internet to help improve rural broadband connectivity in West Sussex.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878433", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878532, "askingMemberId": 4858, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110901", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what diplomatic steps she is taking to help protect religious minorities in Eritrea.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878532", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878603, "askingMemberId": 4827, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110900", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in the Home Office and Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office on extending medical evacuation support to people currently in Gaza requiring a", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878603", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878415, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110899", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if her Department will commission a specific inquiry into the motorcycle insurance market to examine underwriter withdrawals, geographic exclusions and pricing anomalies.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878415", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878414, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110898", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 20 January 2026 to Question 104868, what the service standard wait times at passport control are, and what assessment the Department has made of the economic impact of passen", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878414", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878413, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110897", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate she has made of the additional cost to the public purse of the Royal Air Force transitioning to 100 per cent sustainable aviation fuel by 2040; and whether her Department has undertaken any assessment ", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878413", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878412, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110896", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 26 January 2026 to Question 106604, whether growing revenue and delivering value for money for passengers carry equal priority in the rollout of Great British Railways branding.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878412", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878410, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110895", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what guidance his Department issues to Natural England on the circumstances in which staff may not attempt to fight wildfires on land they manage.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878410", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878408, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110894", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) Notices to Improve and (b) written instructions her Department issued to train operating companies for which the Department is the operator in relation to (i) service performance and (ii) financial", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878408", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878407, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110893", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average waiting time for a practical car driving test was in January 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878407", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878406, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110892", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many full-time equivalent driving examiners recruited by the Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency were (a) in post and (b) delivering practical car driving tests in January 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878406", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878405, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110891", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what information his Department holds on the number of vacancies in the automotive manufacturing sector in (a) January 2024 and (b) each subsequent month up to and including the most recent month for which data ", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878405", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878404, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110890", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 27 October 2025 to Question 82998, whether the Department plans to extend the HGV Parking and Driver Welfare Grant Scheme beyond March 2026; and what assessment has been made of the im", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878404", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878400, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110889", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether his Department provides (a) funding and (b) any other support for increasing (i) grid capacity and (ii) enabling electrification at Portsmouth International Port.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878400", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878399, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110888", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether his Department provides (a) funding and (b) any other support for increasing (i) grid capacity and (ii) enabling electrification at the Port of Southampton.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878399", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878388, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110887", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment has she made of requiring (a) regulatory and (b) policy frameworks to be in place before the Heathrow third runway project can proceed to its next phase.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878388", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878387, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110886", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January 2026 to Question 104858 on Roads: Biodiversity, what information her Department holds on the (a) estimated cost, (b) estimated cost range and (c) modelling of the biodiversi", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878387", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878386, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110885", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 6 January 2026 to Question 101484 on Electric Vehicles: Charging Points, what estimate she has made of the average amount of public funding provided per chargepoint.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878386", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878373, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110884", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Government\u2019s view, as set out in paragraph 4.5.10 of the draft National Policy Statement for Ports dated 4 June 2025, that there is no national resilience case for requiring climate resilience stand", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878373", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878372, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110883", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to her Department's report entitled Rail customer experience survey pilot report, published on 25 April 2024, what plans she has to use the survey findings to inform performance standards for pub", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878372", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878371, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110882", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to pages 30 and 31 of the Government's report entitled Motor Insurance Taskforce: final report, published on 10 December 2025, whether the Department has concluded its consideration of penalties ", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878371", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878370, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110881", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether her Department has measurable targets for helping to reduce average motor insurance premiums.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878370", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878678, "askingMemberId": 4787, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110880", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the oral answer of 25 November 2025, Official Report Column 201, on NHS Dental Services in Norfolk, when he will issue a direction to the Office for Students.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878678", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878675, "askingMemberId": 4778, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110879", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will take steps to replace the number-plate eyesight test with a standardised, clinically validated vision assessment.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878675", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878674, "askingMemberId": 4778, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110878", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether her Department plans to introduce a requirement for all drivers to have their eyesight tested by a qualified optometrist when applying for or renewing their driving licence.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878674", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878673, "askingMemberId": 4778, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110877", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of current eyesight standards for driving; and whether her Department plans to review the regulations governing driver vision requirements.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878673", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878611, "askingMemberId": 4778, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110876", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of cancer patients in Mid Buckinghamshire constituency receive first treatment within the 62 day target.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878611", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878608, "askingMemberId": 4778, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110875", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what evidential criteria were applied when assessing motorcycle bus lane consultation responses.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878608", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878607, "askingMemberId": 4778, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110874", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 18 December 2025 to Question 99588, when her Department plans to publish the evaluation of the \u00a33 bus fare cap.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878607", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878606, "askingMemberId": 4778, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110873", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what support, including business rates relief, direct financial assistance, or other fiscal measures, is being offered to regional airports in England; and how this compares to the support provided to Heathrow ", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878606", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878605, "askingMemberId": 4778, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110872", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of her policy of no reduced rate or exemption for children or family travelling in premium economy of Air Passenger Duty on families travelling with children in p", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878605", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878502, "askingMemberId": 4736, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "110871", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the minimum number of available warships is that the Royal Navy requires to meet basic operational requirements.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878502", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878486, "askingMemberId": 4736, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "110870", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Royal Navy surface warships are (a) available for deployment and (b) deployed.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878486", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878418, "askingMemberId": 4736, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110869", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of implementing measures similar to those adopted in other European countries to help reduce electricity prices for (a) consume", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878418", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878416, "askingMemberId": 4736, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110868", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of constraint payments and balancing actions in each year since 2020; and what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of ", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878416", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878622, "askingMemberId": 4716, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "110867", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the Motability Scheme in providing access to wheelchair accessible vehicles for disabled people.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878622", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878619, "askingMemberId": 4716, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "110866", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions she has had with the Welsh Government on supporting improved access to transport for disabled people across Wales.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878619", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878612, "askingMemberId": 4716, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "110865", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2026 to Question 109591 on Responsible Dog Ownership Working Group, what the timetable is for receipt by her Department of the a) findings and b) r", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878612", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878620, "askingMemberId": 4673, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110864", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will consider Tourette's in its Independent Review into Mental Health Conditions, ADHD and Autism.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878620", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878487, "askingMemberId": 4651, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110863", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what his proposed timetable is for publishing the Government review of CQC regulation 9A.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878487", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878484, "askingMemberId": 4651, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110862", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of introducing primary legislation to guarantee the right for every person in (a) care and (b) health settings to have at leas", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878484", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878724, "askingMemberId": 4647, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110861", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether her Department has directed HMRC to review the application of VAT upon medicines supplied free-of-charge via EAMS and other compassionate access schemes.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878724", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878722, "askingMemberId": 4647, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110860", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what discussions she has had with Cabinet colleagues on the impact of (a) VAT and (b) other taxation on the viability of the life sciences sector.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878722", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878720, "askingMemberId": 4647, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110859", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what discussions she has had with the life sciences sector on the application of VAT on medicines supplied free-of-charge via EAMS and other compassionate access schemes.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878720", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878719, "askingMemberId": 4647, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110858", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the correspondence from the Minister for Science, Innovation, Research and Nuclear to the Chair of the Science, Innovation and Technology Committee, dated 30 January 2026, if he w", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878719", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878666, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110857", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent steps she has taken to help reduce dog bites.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878666", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878649, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110856", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Business and Trade on the environmental impact of high-carbon advertising.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878649", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878628, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110855", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she is taking steps with Cabinet colleagues to ensure that private parking companies provide adequate notice to individuals served with a fine regarding the period in which they must (a) pay or (b) appe", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878628", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878623, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110854", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of people that have been waiting over six months to access Child and Adolescent Mental Health Services support in Slough constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878623", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878621, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110853", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of interim support available to children waiting for access to CAMHS support.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878621", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878618, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110852", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps he has taken to help improve Child and Adolescent Mental Health Services referral times in Slough.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878618", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878617, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110851", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has assessed the adequacy of children's access to Child and Adolescent Mental Health Services in the Slough constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878617", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878558, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110850", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps has he taken to increase bowel screening uptake in Slough constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878558", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878430, "askingMemberId": 4630, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110849", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of data on the impact of flooding on social housing tenants.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878430", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878740, "askingMemberId": 4623, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110848", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate she has made of the Barnett consequentials allocated to the Northern Ireland Executive from the \u00a3750,000 uplift provided in 2019 for an increase in officer numbers to 20,000 in England and Wales.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878740", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878738, "askingMemberId": 4623, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110847", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate she has made of the Barnett consequentials allocated to the Northern Ireland Executive following increases in police funding to PCCs in England and Wales in each year since 2020.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878738", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878737, "askingMemberId": 4623, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110846", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what estimate he has made of UK Government funding allocated to the PSNI as Additional Security Funding in each financial year since 2011.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878737", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878438, "askingMemberId": 4591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110845", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions her Department has had with Transport for London on the distribution of the structure fund for repairs and renovations.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878438", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878560, "askingMemberId": 4571, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110844", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department has taken to help bring awareness to the National Year of Reading within schools and alternative provision settings.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878560", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878559, "askingMemberId": 4571, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110843", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department has to help bring awareness to the National Year of Reading.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878559", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878436, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "110842", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Youth Hubs there were in January (a) 2025 and (b) 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878436", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878726, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110841", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Chancellor of the Exchequer's Oral Statement on 26 March 2025 entitled Spring Statement, Official Report, whether any programmes in existence prior to 26 March 2025 will be included in the 1", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878726", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878725, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110840", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 25 November to Question 91684 on F-35 Aircraft: Procurement, who is responsible for the definition of a Defence Choice.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878725", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878723, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110839", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 25 November to Question 91684 on F-35 Aircraft: Procurement, if he will provide a list of all Defence Choices.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878723", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878721, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110838", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will list the specified operational locations which qualify service personnel to receive the Operational Allowance.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878721", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878710, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110837", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Government press release entitled Huge biosecurity centre investment to boost pandemic protection, published on 17 July 25, if the Defence Science and Technology Laboratory (Dstl) will be re", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878710", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878708, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110836", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will state the total cost of delivering Project Corvus.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878708", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878707, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110835", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent progress he has made on delivering Project Corvus.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878707", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878706, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110834", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what is the out of service date for Bowman.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878706", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878705, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110833", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January to Question 107733 on Unmanned Air Systems: Procurement, what conditions need to be met to declare Initial Operating Capability.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878705", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878704, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110832", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has held discussions regarding the number of Anti-Submarine Warfare frigates that will be manufactured as part of the \u00a310 billion deal with Norway.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878704", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878703, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110831", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 21 January to Question 105260 on Artillery: Procurement, when the full production contract will be placed.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878703", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878702, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110830", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 23 January to Question 99911, if he will name the two AI contracts that have been awarded by his Department since 5 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878702", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878701, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110829", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 26 January to Question 107089 on Typhoon Aircraft: Radar, whether the \u00a3205 million investment to deliver the European Common Radar System (ECRS) MK2 includes funding for the Phase 4 Enha", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878701", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878700, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110828", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 30 January to Question 107727 on Unmanned Air Systems: Higher Education, how many of the (a) civilians and (b) soldiers enrolled on the undergraduate drone degree does he expect to parti", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878700", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878699, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110827", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many personnel will participate in the British Army's small Uncrewed Aircraft Systems training pathways in each remaining financial year of the current Parliament.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878699", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878697, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110826", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many personnel are currently participating in the British Army's small Uncrewed Aircraft Systems training pathways.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878697", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878696, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110825", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 30 January to Question 108701 on Skynet: Procurement, when the Skynet 6A will complete the testing and validation phase.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878696", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878694, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110824", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) UK and (b) international long-range kinetic drone testing sites will be operational in each remaining financial year of the current Parliament.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878694", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878538, "askingMemberId": 4515, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110823", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent discussions she has had with her Pakistani counterpart on the alleged forced disappearances of Muhammad Bakhsh Sajidi, Naeem Sajidi and Rafeeq Baloch.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878538", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878443, "askingMemberId": 4436, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110822", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to publish updated guidance on managing conflicts of interest between civil servants and Ministers in relation to unhealthy commodity industries.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878443", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878442, "askingMemberId": 4436, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110821", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to introduce mandatory alcohol labelling requirements.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878442", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878616, "askingMemberId": 4434, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110820", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what information her Department holds on the date Peter Mandelson ceased being employed by her Department.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878616", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878504, "askingMemberId": 4389, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110819", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what representations she has made to her Israeli counterpart on the future of the Ibrahimi Mosque.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878504", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878531, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110818", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Prime Minister discussed UK defence procurement of services from Palantir during his visit in February 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878531", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878530, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110817", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether Lord Mandelson's (a) Fellowship of the 48 Group and (b) work for Global Counsel was considered during his Department's due diligence prior to appointment as Ambassador of the United States.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878530", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878529, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110816", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to his oral statement of 2 February 2026, Official Report, Col. 49, on US Department of Justice Release of Files, if he will publish the (a) letter sent by Gordon Brown to the Cabinet Secretary an", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878529", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878528, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110815", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether No10 special advisers have auto-delete functionality turned on for (a) corporate and (b) non-corporate communication devices when discussing government business.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878528", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878527, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110814", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, on what matters Tim Allan has recused himself.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878527", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878522, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110813", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, when the US government informed the Government of the pending disclosure of files relating to (a) Peter Mandelson and bi) Andrew Mountbatten-Windsor.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878522", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878521, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110812", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, to which public inquiries his Department has submitted (a) documents and (b) other communications created between June 2007 and May 2010.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878521", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878520, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110811", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will ask the US Department of Justice to provide the unredacted email addresses of people included in the emails to Jeffery Epstein that included Government documents.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878520", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878519, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110810", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department archived emails (a) sent by and (b) received from John Pond between 2007 and 2010.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878519", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878518, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110809", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Prime Minister was the appointing Minister of Lord Mandelson as Head of Mission.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878518", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878517, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110808", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether 10 Downing Street had discussions with representatives of Global Counsel over the visit of the Prime Minister to the offices of Palantir with Lord Mandelson.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878517", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878516, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110807", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the No10 press release entitled Appointment of Victoria Buhler as the Prime Minister\u2019s Deputy Adviser on Business, Investment, and Trade and Hannah Bronwin as the Prime Minister\u2019s Expert Advise", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878516", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878515, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110806", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the answer of 13 October 2025, to Question 77563, on Palantir, which representatives of (a) his department and (b) the Armed Forces accompanied the Prime Minister.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878515", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878514, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110805", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether representatives of Global Counsel were invited to (a) meetings and (b) receptions in the UK Embassy in Washington during the tenure of Lord Mandelson as Ambassador.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878514", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878512, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110804", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions did the Prime Minister\u2019s Chief of Staff have with the then Permanent Under-Secretary of the department in relation to the appointment of Lord Mandelson as Am", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878512", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878401, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110803", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what his policy is on disclosing the remuneration of individual direct ministerial appointments who were appointed prior to the creation of the Direct Ministerial Appointment portal.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878401", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878541, "askingMemberId": 4371, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110802", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether she had made representations to the Government of Malaysia on the detention and deportation of Rohingya refugees.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878541", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878539, "askingMemberId": 4371, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110801", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions she has had with her Chinese counterpart on the arrest and charging of people affiliated with the Atajurt movement.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878539", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878567, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-11T00:00:00", "uin": "110800", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will publish the full meeting, visit and event schedule for Lord Khan's visit to Pakistan from 13 to 17 April 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878567", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878566, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110799", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what research his Department has undertaken into the reasons for sites with planning permission being (a) stalled and (b) not built out.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878566", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878565, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110798", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to consult the public on formal new names for new unitary councils.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878565", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878564, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110797", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what his policy is on establishing (a) shadow unitary councils and (b) preparing councils when undertaking local government restructuring.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878564", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878562, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110796", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the answer of 28 May 2024, to Question 53574, on Chinese Embassy: Planning Permission, and with reference to page 26 of the Section 106 agreement, for what reason the", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878562", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878561, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110795", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what are the internal areas within the proposed Chinese Embassy that would be exempt from UK inspection and verification.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878561", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878557, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110794", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 13 January 2026 to Question 102765, on Planning: Publications, whether he intends to update any of the other Plain English guides published on gov.uk by", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878557", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878556, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110793", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether any staff in his Department work a four day week.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878556", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878555, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110792", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to introduce planning reforms through primary legislation.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878555", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878554, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110791", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the publication ENTITLED MHCLG register of board members\u2019 interests 2025 to 2026, updated 21 January 2026, whether any of the individuals have declared politica", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878554", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878553, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110790", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reason the proposed High Value Council Tax Surcharge will be levied on the property owner of the dwelling.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878553", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878551, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110789", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many headcount staff in his Department work compressed hours on full pay.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878551", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878432, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110788", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's guidance entitled The implementation of the council tax premiums on long-term empty homes and second homes, published on 1 November 2024, what ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878432", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878409, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110787", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 20 January 2026 to Question 104897 on Strategic Migration Partnership: Finance, and with reference to the Cabinet Office Guide to Parliamentary Work, paragraph 233, if he wil", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878409", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878691, "askingMemberId": 4362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110786", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what percentage of calls to the 24/7 Rape Support Line were answered in a) July 2025, b) August 2025, c) September 2025, d) October 2025, e) November 2025 and f) December 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878691", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878688, "askingMemberId": 4362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110785", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many call handlers were employed to staff the 24/7 rape support line in a) July 2025, b) August 2025, c) September 2025, d) October 2025, e) November 2025, and f) December 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878688", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878687, "askingMemberId": 4362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110784", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what was the number of calls to the 24/7 rape support line in a) July 2025, b) August 2025 , c) September 2025 , d) October 2025, e) November 2025 and f) December 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878687", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878686, "askingMemberId": 4362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110783", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what male supportive gender specific rape and abuse support services were commissioned directly by his Department in 2025; and if he will list each service and how much spending was allocated to each in 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878686", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878684, "askingMemberId": 4362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110782", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what percentage of calls to the 24/7 rape support line were answered substantively within 5 minutes in a) July 2025, b) August 2025 , c) September 2025 , d) October 2025, e) November 2025 and f) December 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878684", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878639, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110781", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what interim arrangements are in place to manage border and entry for Gibraltar pending the implementation of the UK-EU Gibraltar treaty.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878639", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878637, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110780", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether her Department has issued guidance to (a) airlines and (b) British travellers on Schengen entry requirements for flights to Gibraltar that may be diverted into the Sc", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878637", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878635, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110779", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to help protect British citizens from detention or refusal of entry following flight diversions into the Schengen area.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878635", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878634, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110778", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether she has made representations to her Spanish counterpart on the detention and return of British nationals at M\u00e1laga Airport following flight diversions.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878634", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878633, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110777", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions she has had with the Government of Gibraltar on the functioning of border arrangements.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878633", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878632, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110776", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, which authorities are responsible for controlling Schengen entry checks at Gibraltar\u2019s airport and ports, and how the Government ensures UK travellers are not subject to impr", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878632", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878631, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110775", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether UK citizens will retain unrestricted access to Gibraltar once the UK-EU Gibraltar treaty and associated border arrangements are fully implemented.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878631", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878630, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110774", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions she has had with her (a) Spanish and (b) European Union counterparts on the application of Schengen entry rules to passengers travelling to Gibraltar.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878630", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878629, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110773", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether she has reviewed the legal and regulatory frameworks governing Gibraltar\u2019s aviation, immigration and border arrangements.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878629", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878495, "askingMemberId": 4357, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110772", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of issuing emergency visas to students in Gaza who have confirmed UK university places; and whether her Department has had recent discussions wit", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878495", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878493, "askingMemberId": 4357, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110771", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of border arrangements in Gaza for supporting eligible students to travel to study in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878493", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878491, "askingMemberId": 4357, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110770", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to help support students in Gaza with confirmed offers from UK universities to come to the UK; and whether her Department has set a timeta", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878491", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878728, "askingMemberId": 4095, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110769", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he was made aware of conclusion 1 in the Sixty-second Report of the Committee of Public Accounts entitled Faulty energy efficiency installations, HC 1229, prior to the decision to appoint a new Permanent ", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878728", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878461, "askingMemberId": 4095, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110768", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the establishment of the Jean Bishop Centre in Hull in 2018, whether his Department has conducted a cost\u2013benefit analysis of a more integrated model of service for elderly patient", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878461", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878426, "askingMemberId": 4089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110767", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what is his Department's policy on the recycling of aluminium in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878426", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878425, "askingMemberId": 4089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110766", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information her Department holds on which countries critical mineral waste and scrap are exported under licence for recycling.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878425", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878424, "askingMemberId": 4089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110765", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will publish a list of companies that have a licence to export critical mineral waste and scrap for recycling abroad.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878424", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878481, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110764", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions she has had with her US counterpart on the future sovereignty of the Chagos Archipelago since 20 January 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878481", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878480, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110763", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what representations she has received from her Mauritian counterpart on the UK-Mauritius Treaty since 1 January 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878480", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878479, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110762", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if she will make an estimate of when the first payment under the UK-Mauritius Treaty will be made.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878479", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878478, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110761", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, how much funding has been provided to Mauritius under the UK-Mauritius Strategic Partnership Framework.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878478", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878477, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110760", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether she has received advice on the UK unilaterally revising the 1966 Exchange of Notes with the US on the sovereignty of the British Indian Ocean Territory.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878477", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878476, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110759", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, when (a) she and (b) Ministers in her Department held discussions with her US counterparts on the 1966 Exchange of Notes with the US on the sovereignty of the British Indian ", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878476", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878460, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110758", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions she has had with the Government of Rwanda on the UK-Rwanda Asylum Partnership Agreement.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878460", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878459, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110757", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what information her Department holds on discussions between Lord Mandelson and (a) the US Administration and (b) the National Security Adviser on the future of the Chagos Is", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878459", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878610, "askingMemberId": 4008, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110756", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of Local Authorities contracting funeral services where those services fall outside of a Local Authority's obligations under Section 46 of", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878610", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878526, "askingMemberId": 4005, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110755", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the nationality breakdown was of people subject to decisions under paragraphs SUI 26.1 and SUI 26.2 of the Part Suitability of the Immigration Rules in each year since 1 December 2020.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878526", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878525, "askingMemberId": 4005, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110754", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many referrals Immigration Enforcement has received from (i) local authorities and (ii) police forces regarding rough sleeping by non-UK nationals.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878525", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878524, "askingMemberId": 4005, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110753", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many non-UK nationals have been removed from the UK following a decision under paragraphs SUI 26.1 or SUI 26.2 of Part Suitability of the Immigration Rules.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878524", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878523, "askingMemberId": 4005, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110752", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many non-UK nationals have had their permission to stay refused or cancelled under paragraphs SUI 26.1 and SUI 26.2 of Part Suitability of the Immigration Rules on the grounds of rough sleeping.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878523", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878483, "askingMemberId": 4005, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110751", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of the expansion of the UK National Screening Committee\u2019s remit to include consideration of targeted screening programmes on the eval", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878483", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878615, "askingMemberId": 3973, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110750", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will have discussions with sports authorities on ensuring that (a) football-related Chronic Traumatic Encephalopathy is recognised as a public health issue and (b) appropriate education an", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878615", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878614, "askingMemberId": 3973, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110749", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will work with sports charities to create a national education programme and slogan to raise awareness of Chronic Traumatic Encephalopathy in football.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878614", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878613, "askingMemberId": 3973, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110748", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to raise awareness of football related Chronic Traumatic Encephalopathy caused by repetitive head impacts from heading a football.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878613", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878685, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110747", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, further to her oral contribution during the statement on Mobile Phones and Social Media on 20th January 2026 whether \"before the summer\" indicates prior to the House rising for the summ", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878685", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878683, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110746", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, further to the three month consultation announced by the Government on further measures to keep children safe online, whether her Department plans to review submissions (a) as they come", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878683", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878681, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110745", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, further to the three month consultation announced by the government on further measures to keep children safe online, how many full-time equivalent officials she has assigned to this co", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878681", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878417, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110744", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what capacity his Department has made available for Work Capability Assessments in the next six months; and what the backlog of cases is.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878417", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878599, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110743", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps he is taking to ensure a just transition and economic fairness for communities when reducing air pollution from the energy sector.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878599", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878598, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110742", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential (a) direct and (b) indirect impact of current levels of (i) ambient and (ii) indoor air pollution on the (A) current and (B) future health o", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878598", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878597, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110741", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of poor air quality in (a) ambient air and (b) indoor air on different age groups of people in England.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878597", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878596, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110740", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on air pollution impacting people's health in relation to (a) ambient air and (b) indoor air in England.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878596", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878595, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110739", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to (a) bring awareness to and (b) help address the potential adverse impact of poor ambient air quality.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878595", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878594, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110738", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on delivering national targets for ambient air including by sharing data.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878594", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878593, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110737", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what comparative assessment she has made of his Department's (a) targets, (b) requirements and (c) performance standards for ambient air pollution and the World Health Organisation's A", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878593", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878592, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110736", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will set out the types of health impacts of poor (a) ambient and (b) indoor air quality by (i) geography and (ii) socioeconomic groups.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878592", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878591, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110735", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to strengthen communities' powers to improve accountability and local action on air pollution.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878591", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878590, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110734", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with Cabinet colleagues to determine the extent that her Department's policies on ambient air quality are interacting with policies on climate change mitig", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878590", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878589, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110733", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of whether local authorities in England have the resources and powers to enforce existing legislation and regulation to improve local air quality.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878589", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878588, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110732", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how her Department's ambient air quality policy is interacting with climate change mitigation, nature recovery and land use planning.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878588", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878587, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110731", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the UK's performance in comparison with international counterparts in setting standards for air quality in (a) ambient air and (b) indoor air.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878587", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878503, "askingMemberId": 1516, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110730", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has set a timeline for publication of legislation to reverse the effects of R (on the application of PACCAR Inc and others) v Competition Appeal Tribunal.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878503", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878411, "askingMemberId": 1516, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110729", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will take legislative steps to reverse the effects of R (on the application of PACCAR Inc and others) v Competition Appeal Tribunal and provide for the changes to apply retrospectively.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878411", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878452, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110728", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, when she last met her Irish counterpart face to face to discuss people arriving illegally and crossing the border into Northern Ireland.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878452", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878421, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110727", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has been made of the change in the amounts claimed in Universal Credit between (a) September 2024 and (b) September 2029.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878421", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878420, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110726", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will hold discussions with the BBC on ensuring its (a) TV and (b) radio programming is made across the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878420", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878419, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110725", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of Operation Gull in Northern Ireland in the last 15 years.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878419", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878657, "askingMemberId": 373, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110724", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions her Department had with US counterparts on extraditing Omar al Bayoumi in 2001.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878657", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878655, "askingMemberId": 373, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110723", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what contact her department had with counterparts in the US on the release and ongoing surveillance of Omar al Bayoumi in 2001 and 2002.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878655", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878654, "askingMemberId": 373, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110722", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which of her Department's officials informed US authorities that they would not observe the interrogation of Omar al Bayoumi in 2001.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878654", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878652, "askingMemberId": 373, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110721", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which of her Department's officials informed the Metropolitan Police that the US would not be extraditing Omar al-Bayoumi in 2001.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878652", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878650, "askingMemberId": 373, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110720", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the work of the Metropolitan Police in September 2001 on the possible extradition of Omar al Bayoumi.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878650", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878398, "askingMemberId": 373, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110719", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he has had with the Solicitors Regulation Authority's on that organisation's ability to regulate solicitors where it is unable to access material over which privilege is claimed during investigat", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878398", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878397, "askingMemberId": 373, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110718", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he has had with the Solicitors Regulation Authority on the operation of it complaints procedure for matters involving alleged Strategic Lawsuits Against Public Participation.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878397", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878563, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110717", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2026 to Question 106994 on Veterans: Radiation Exposure, whether research on the effects of radiation on British servicemen held by the Technical Cooperation Programme of the ", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878563", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878732, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110716", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment has the department made of the potential impact of the government\u2019s Warm Homes Plan on levels of fuel poverty in North East Somerset and Hanham.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878732", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878423, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110715", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster's speech entitled Move fast. Fix things., published on 20 January 2026, what discussions he has had with regional mayors on lessons learned from Project", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878423", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878545, "askingMemberId": 185, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110714", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the legislative basis is for the United States' use of force from bases in the United Kingdom being subject to joint decision-making.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878545", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878544, "askingMemberId": 185, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110713", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether there are confidential arrangements in place governing the US military's use of bases in the UK in addition to the NATO Status of Forces Agreement 1951, the Visiting Forces Act 1952 and UK/US Cost Sharing", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878544", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878543, "askingMemberId": 185, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110712", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, where United States (a) naval, (b) army and (c) marine detachments are stationed in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878543", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878542, "askingMemberId": 185, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110711", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the work carried out at MOD Bicester; how many of his Department\u2019s personnel are stationed there; and who owns the site.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878542", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878540, "askingMemberId": 185, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110710", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the role is of RAF Oakhanger; how many of his Department\u2019s personnel are stationed there; and who owns the site.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878540", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878475, "askingMemberId": 178, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110709", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of Pakistan\u2019s compliance with its obligations under international human rights conventions, particularly in relation to enforced ", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878475", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878429, "askingMemberId": 54, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110708", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether (a) she and (b) her immediate predecessor had discussions with their United States counterparts on the opt-out provisions applying to (i) Diego Garcia and (ii) the Ch", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878429", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878428, "askingMemberId": 54, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110707", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to the Diego Garcia military base, whether an exemption will exist from the Africa Nuclear Weapon-Free Zone provisions of the Pelindaba Treaty after sovereignt", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878428", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878427, "askingMemberId": 54, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110706", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if she has had discussions with her United States counterpart the potential security implications of the existence of opt-outs in respect of (a) Diego Garcia and (b) the Chag", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878427", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878304, "askingMemberId": 5122, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "907753", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking with Cabinet colleagues to help tackle organised crime networks involved in fly-tipping in rural areas.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878304", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878078, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110705", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to her Department\u2019s press release entitled Foreign Secretary sets out new cooperation on illegal migration from Horn of Africa on visit to Ethiopia, published ", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Horn of Africa: Undocumented Migrants", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878078", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877963, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110704", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether local authorities will have discretion following the implementation of electoral boundary changes to determine whether elections are held by thirds, halves, or all-out el", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877963", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877885, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110703", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of soil excavated as part of the Lower Thames Crossing construction will be a) re-used on site, b) recycled or c) disposed of off-site.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Lower Thames Crossing: Excavation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877885", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877884, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110702", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the environmental impact of a) soil excavation and b) disposal generated by the Lower Thames Crossing.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Lower Thames Crossing: Excavation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877884", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877859, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110701", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, pursuant to the Prime Minister\u2019s press release entitled \u2018Prime Minister unlocks new opportunities for British businesses in China\u2019 published on 29 January 2026, what steps are being taken to improve re", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Trade Agreements: China", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877859", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877858, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110700", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, with reference to Prime Minister\u2019s press release entitled Prime Minister unlocks new opportunities for British businesses in China, published on 29 January 2026, if he will make it his policy to ensure", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Trade Agreements: China", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877858", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877857, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110699", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, with reference to Prime Minister\u2019s press release entitled Prime Minister unlocks new opportunities for British businesses in China, published on 29 January 2026, when the joint feasibility study on a U", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Trade Agreements: China", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877857", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877856, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110698", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, with reference to Prime Minister\u2019s press release entitled Prime Minister unlocks new opportunities for British businesses in China, published on 29 January 2026, what assessment he has made of the pote", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Trade Agreements: China", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877856", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877848, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110697", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to her Department\u2019s press release entitled UK leads global efforts to help communities save the ocean and beat poverty, published on 26 January 2026, if she will set out", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ocean Community Empowerment and Nature Grants Programme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877848", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877847, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110696", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to her Department\u2019s press release entitled UK leads global efforts to help communities save the ocean and beat poverty, published on 26 January 2026, what proportion of ", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ocean Community Empowerment and Nature Grants Programme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877847", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877846, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110695", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to her Department\u2019s press release entitled UK leads global efforts to help communities save the ocean and beat poverty, published on 26 January 2026, if she will list th", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ocean Community Empowerment and Nature Grants Programme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877846", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877845, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110694", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to her Department\u2019s press release entitled UK leads global efforts to help communities save the ocean and beat poverty, published on 26 January 2026, what steps her Depa", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ocean Community Empowerment and Nature Grants Programme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877845", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877844, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110693", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to her Department\u2019s press release entitled UK leads global efforts to help communities save the ocean and beat poverty, published on 26 January 2026, what outcome measur", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ocean Community Empowerment and Nature Grants Programme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877844", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877843, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110692", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to her Department\u2019s press release entitled UK leads global efforts to help communities save the ocean and beat poverty, published on 26 January 2026, what proportion of ", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ocean Community Empowerment and Nature Grants Programme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877843", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877842, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110691", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to her Department\u2019s press release entitled UK leads global efforts to help communities save the ocean and beat poverty, published on 26 January 2026, what Department's b", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ocean Community Empowerment and Nature Grants Programme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877842", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877841, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110690", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to her Department\u2019s press release entitled UK leads global efforts to help communities save the ocean and beat poverty, published on 26 January 2026, what proportion of ", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ocean Community Empowerment and Nature Grants Programme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877841", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877840, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110689", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to her Department\u2019s press release entitled UK leads global efforts to help communities save the ocean and beat poverty, published on 26 January 2026, over what period th", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ocean Community Empowerment and Nature Grants Programme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877840", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877839, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110688", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to her Department\u2019s press release entitled UK leads global efforts to help communities save the ocean and beat poverty, published on 26 January 2026, how much funding ha", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ocean Community Empowerment and Nature Grants Programme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877839", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878067, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110687", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he will increase the level of funding for import of medication from abroad to treat Acute Myeloid Leukaemia.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Leukaemia: Drugs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878067", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878066, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110686", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of medication available on the NHS to treat Acute Myeloid Leukaemia in babies.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878066", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878042, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110685", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with stakeholders on his Department's modelling of workforce numbers in the 10 Year Workforce Plan.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Staff", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878042", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877883, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110684", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to restrict the number of House in Multiple Occupation developments in residential areas.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Multiple Occupation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877883", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878081, "askingMemberId": 5357, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110683", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, when the last Joint Analysis of Conflict and Stability strategic assessment was carried out to evaluate the situation in the Occupied Palestinian Territories.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878081", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878019, "askingMemberId": 5354, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110682", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to ensure children, especially from lower-income families, have access to regular, free community sports activities.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sports: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878019", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878017, "askingMemberId": 5354, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110681", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to ensure stable, long-term funding for free community sports activities.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sports: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878017", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878016, "askingMemberId": 5354, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110680", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to improve environmental education in schools.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Environment Protection: Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878016", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878015, "askingMemberId": 5354, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110679", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of resources to support schools to reach net zero.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: Carbon Emissions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878015", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878014, "askingMemberId": 5354, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110678", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to streamline the recruitment process for the armed forces.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Armed Forces: Recruitment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878014", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878012, "askingMemberId": 5354, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110677", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to streamline the transition between regular and reserve service.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Reserve Forces", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878012", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878011, "askingMemberId": 5354, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110676", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure the reliability of issued kit.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Armed Forces: Equipment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878011", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878010, "askingMemberId": 5354, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110675", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of a joint procurement plan for the nations making up the Coalition of the Willing.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Defence: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878010", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878008, "askingMemberId": 5354, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110673", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to support the development of experimental treatments for Type 1 diabetes.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Diabetes: Medical Treatments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878008", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878007, "askingMemberId": 5354, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110672", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department has taken to reduce the financial cost of blood ketone tests.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Blood Tests: Costs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878007", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878005, "askingMemberId": 5354, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110671", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department has taken to improve diagnosis of Type 1 diabetes in children.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Diabetes: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878005", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878116, "askingMemberId": 5352, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110670", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment has been made of passenger demand and capacity on Great Western Railway services between Kemble and London Paddington, and what steps are being taken to ensure that service provision reflects de", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Golden Valley Line: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878116", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878114, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110669", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has made an assessment of the risk to public safety from the publication of sensitive information relating to the physical security of properties on local authority planning registers.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878114", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878071, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110668", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2026 to Question 106884, whether the requirement for local planning authorities to maintain published plans and drawings of residential devel", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878071", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877988, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110667", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with stakeholders on his Department's modelling of workforce numbers in the 10 Year Workforce Plan.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Staff", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877988", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878173, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110666", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the Children and Young Persons Act 1933.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Children and Young Persons Act 1933", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878173", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878020, "askingMemberId": 5347, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110665", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with the the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology on updating the Computer Misuse Act 1990 to remove limits on the ability of cybersecurity profession", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cybersecurity: Artificial Intelligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878020", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878108, "askingMemberId": 5343, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110664", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the (a) total number of full-time equivalent customer service staff employed by HM Revenue and Customs was in each of the last ten financial years and (b) number of these positions that were based in (i) call c", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878108", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878003, "askingMemberId": 5343, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110663", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to reduce the backlog for NHS England\u2019s Clinical Priorities Advisory Group Prioritisation meeting.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Medical Treatments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878003", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878002, "askingMemberId": 5343, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110662", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what level of recurrent funding has been identified to fund new treatments through NHS England\u2019s Clinical Priorities Advisory Group Prioritisation meeting.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Medical Treatments: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878002", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878001, "askingMemberId": 5343, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110661", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many times NHS England\u2019s Clinical Priorities Advisory Group Prioritisation meeting happens each year; and when the next meeting will be.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Medical Treatments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878001", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877918, "askingMemberId": 5343, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110660", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the average time taken to complete earnings assessments for carers in receipt of Carer's Allowance who undertake part-time self-employment; and if he will make a", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Carer's Allowance: Self-employed", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877918", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878102, "askingMemberId": 5342, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110659", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to help support ex-footballers with neurodegenerative diseases.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Football: Neurological Diseases", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878102", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877927, "askingMemberId": 5342, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110658", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps his Department is taking to coordinate planning, energy policy and building regulations to maximise solar deployment across the built environment.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Solar Power: Buildings", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877927", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877925, "askingMemberId": 5342, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110657", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether his Department has plans for new incentives to help encourage businesses to install rooftop solar panels on large industrial and commercial buildings.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Solar Power: Business Premises", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877925", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877924, "askingMemberId": 5342, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110656", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of current mechanisms supporting small-scale solar generation following the closure of the Feed-in Tariff scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Solar Power: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877924", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877877, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110655", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what dedicated funding streams exist across Departments to support food, nature, and sustainability education.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sustainable Development: Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877877", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877876, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110654", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that curriculum, vocational training, and teacher development programs are used to promote students' understanding of ecosystems, soil health, and climate adaptation within th", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Environment and Food: Curriculum", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877876", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877875, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110653", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking with the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government to help tackle inequalities in access to healthy, minimally processed food through education.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food: Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877875", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877874, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110652", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to empower local community initiatives, farms, and schools to implement practical food and nature education; and how his Department is measuring their imp", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Environment and Food: Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877874", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877873, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110651", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how her Department is ensuring that early year\u2019s provision includes learning about food, soil, biodiversity, and ecosystems.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Environment and Food: Pre-school Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877873", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877872, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110650", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to align apprenticeship standards, T Levels, and other vocational qualifications with future food system needs.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Vocational Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877872", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877871, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110649", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how her Department is ensuring that young people gain practical, vocational skills in regenerative farming, agroecology, and sustainable horticulture.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture and Horticulture: Vocational Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877871", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877870, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110648", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to embed practical food, nature, and sustainability education across the national curriculum from EYFS to post-16, including T Levels.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture and Food: Curriculum", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877870", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877934, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110647", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of implementing a public awareness campaign to promote the new Highway Code rules.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Highway Code: Publicity", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877934", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877932, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110646", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when her Department plans to publish its review of safeguarding requirements in childcare nurseries.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Children: Protection", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877932", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877931, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110645", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will hold a consultation on the mandatory use of CCTV in childcare nurseries.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Nurseries: CCTV", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877931", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877930, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110644", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to support school\u2019s in administering statutory suicide prevention training from September 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: Suicide", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877930", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877929, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110643", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that businesses undertaking a transition to digital services, such as BT\u2019s transition to Digital Voice, have considered the potential impac", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Service Industries: Digital Technology", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877929", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877928, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110642", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that businesses switching to digital services, such as BT\u2019s transition to Digital Voice, communicate these changes appropriately with custo", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Service Industries: Digital Technology", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877928", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877926, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110641", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Education and the Home Secretary on the Child Protection Authority consultation.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Child Protection Authority: Public Consultation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877926", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878140, "askingMemberId": 5330, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110640", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she has made a recent assessment of the potential merits of abolishing the Office for Budget Responsibility.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Office for Budget Responsibility", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878140", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878138, "askingMemberId": 5330, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110639", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the number of arms-length bodies across Government departments has increased since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Arms Length Bodies", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878138", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878134, "askingMemberId": 5330, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110638", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent assessment he has made of the potential merits of abolishing the House of Lords Appointments Commission.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878134", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877968, "askingMemberId": 5330, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110637", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to help increase physiotherapy employment opportunities for the cohort graduating in 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877968", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877966, "askingMemberId": 5330, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110636", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to support physiotherapists that qualified last year into employment.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877966", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877965, "askingMemberId": 5330, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110635", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of levels of availability of entry-level physiotherapy roles on musculoskeletal waiting lists.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877965", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877964, "askingMemberId": 5330, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110634", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that newly qualified physiotherapists are able to access Band 5 employment opportunities within the NHS, in the context of recruitment freezes and rece", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877964", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878162, "askingMemberId": 5327, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110633", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she will make an assessment of the potential merits of lowering the speed limit on rural single carriageway roads.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878162", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878159, "askingMemberId": 5327, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110632", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to her Department's policy paper entitled the Road Safety Strategy, published on 7 January 2026, whether she has had conversations with optometrists on mandatory eye testing for drivers.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878159", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878101, "askingMemberId": 5327, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110631", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made with Cabinet colleagues of the potential impact of the proposed changes to indefinite leave to remain status on (a) holders of ECAA Turkish Businessperson visas and (b) th", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878101", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877867, "askingMemberId": 5327, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110630", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department's upcoming leasehold reforms will include changes that will impact those living in (a) park homes and (b) accommodation purchased under the Mobile Homes Ac", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877867", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877866, "askingMemberId": 5327, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110629", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment his Department have made of the potential impacts of a 14-day cooling off period for all online subscriptions on the number of people that cancel their subscription after visiting a sit", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877866", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878029, "askingMemberId": 5325, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110628", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department has taken to help support parents of students with SEND with having Education, Health and Care Plans in place.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Educational Needs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878029", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878180, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110627", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential impact of the provision of data on employee health benefits to SME decision makers on levels of employee ill health.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Small Businesses: Health", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878180", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878174, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110626", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what data her Department holds on the Holiday Activities and Food Programme from returns submitted by local authorities following the end of each holiday period.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Holiday Activities and Food Programme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878174", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878120, "askingMemberId": 5313, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110625", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to prevent individuals subject to active civil court orders from receiving Legal Aid.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Legal Aid Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878120", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878119, "askingMemberId": 5313, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110624", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he has taken to monitor and evaluate the adequacy of Legal Aid funding awarded under the Schedule 1 of the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Legal Aid Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878119", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878118, "askingMemberId": 5313, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110623", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to address the funding anomaly whereby Legal Aid funding may be granted to alleged or confirmed perpetrators rather than judicially recognised victims.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Legal Aid Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878118", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878117, "askingMemberId": 5313, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110622", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what safeguards are in place to ensure that Legal Aid awarded under the LASPO Schedule 1 pathway is provided solely to individuals who have been judicially recognised as victims.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Legal Aid Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878117", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878104, "askingMemberId": 5308, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110621", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has considered the merits of allowing police to issue Community Protection Warnings and Notices to 10-16 year-olds.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Community Protection Notices: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878104", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878216, "askingMemberId": 5303, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110620", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with Suffolk County Council on the (a) social and (b) economic impact of housing (i) refugees and (ii) asylum seekers on the local area.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Suffolk", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878216", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878215, "askingMemberId": 5303, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110619", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to protect British agricultural produce from foreign competition.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Trade Competitiveness", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878215", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877868, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110618", "questionText": "To ask the Leader of the House, whether he has had discussions with the House Authorities on guidance issued on parliamentary engagement with organisations whom the Government have banned engagement with.", "answeringBodyId": 34, "answeringBodyName": "Leader of the House", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Parliament: Public Consultation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877868", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878133, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110617", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking with Cabinet colleagues to help (a) tackle and (b) prevent organised crime networks involved in fly-tipping in (i) Surrey and (ii) Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fly-tipping: Surrey", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878133", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878132, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110616", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to improve the inspection of water infrastructure in Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Water Supply: Surrey Heath", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878132", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878131, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110615", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to support farming in (a) Surrey and (b) Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Surrey", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878131", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878130, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110614", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what progress her Department has made on the rollout of gigabit broadband in Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Broadband: Surrey Heath", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878130", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878129, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110613", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps her Department is taking to help improve the resilience of mobile networks in Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mobile Phones: Surrey Heath", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878129", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878128, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110612", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of social media on young people\u2019s wellbeing in (a) Surrey and (b) Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Media: Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878128", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878127, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110611", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of plans to replace the copper wire communications network in Surrey.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Telecommunications Cables: Surrey", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878127", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878126, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110610", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of AI on trends in the level of employment in (a) Surrey and (b) Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employment: Artificial Intelligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878126", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878124, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110609", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure that (a) education and (b) training programmes support the rehabilitation of people leaving prison in Surrey.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offenders: Rehabilitation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878124", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878123, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110608", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to support armed forces families in Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Armed Forces: Surrey Heath", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878123", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878100, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110607", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what estimate he has made of the number of business insolvencies in the UK road haulage sector in each of the past 20 years.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878100", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878191, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110606", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she has taken to prevent parents from avoiding paying VAT on private school fees by paying several years' fees in advance.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878191", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878155, "askingMemberId": 5270, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110605", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what assessment has been made of the potential impact of recent UK Research and Innovation and The Science and Technology Facilities Council's decisions to reduce funding for particle p", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878155", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878096, "askingMemberId": 5262, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110604", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with stakeholders on his Department's modelling of workforce numbers in the 10 Year Workforce Plan.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Staff", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878096", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878094, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110603", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will provide, for each driving test centre in Great Britain, the car practical driving test waiting time in weeks in January 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878094", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878093, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110602", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average processing time was for driving licence applications in December 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878093", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878092, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110601", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what her proposed timeline is for publishing her Department's response to the consultation and evidence-gathering exercise on removing the 50km restriction for 18 to 20-year-old bus and coach drivers.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878092", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878091, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110600", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment her Department has made of the impact of Air Passenger Duty on domestic air routes and regional airport connectivity in the UK, compared with the approach taken by other European countries to support", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878091", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878090, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110599", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment her Department has made of the extent to which business rates relief and other fiscal support provided to Heathrow and Gatwick is available to regional airports; and what steps she is taking to ", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878090", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877994, "askingMemberId": 5250, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110598", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the number of residential properties built in Taunton and Wellington constituency in each year from 2009.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Taunton and Wellington", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877994", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878000, "askingMemberId": 5247, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110597", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to consider the development of national standards for adult social care in England.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878000", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877999, "askingMemberId": 5247, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110596", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of trends in the level of social care standards across England; and what steps he is taking to support greater consistency of care provision.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877999", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877923, "askingMemberId": 5242, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "110595", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of the RPI plus 3 per cent interest rate on Plan 2 student loan debt on the ability of graduates earning the UK median wage to begin to pay down t", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877923", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877922, "askingMemberId": 5242, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "110594", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of outstanding Plan 2 student loan debt in the year the first loans become eligible to be written off; and what assessment she has made of the potential impact of that debt", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877922", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877896, "askingMemberId": 5242, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "110593", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has considered the implications of the UK-US Economic Prosperity Deal for the potential approval of Jascayd (nerandomilast).", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877896", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877894, "askingMemberId": 5242, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "110592", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has an estimate of the earliest possible date Jascayd (nerandomilast) could be available to idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis patients.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877894", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878115, "askingMemberId": 5232, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "110590", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of integrating all at risk screening for breast cancer into the National NHS Breast Screening Programme.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878115", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878018, "askingMemberId": 5227, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110589", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the proposed Earned Settlement framework on the (a) family stability, (b) day-to-day security and (c) ability to access credit of Skilled Worker", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Immigration", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878018", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878013, "askingMemberId": 5227, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110588", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the retrospective increase in ILR on skill levels in key industries such as health and social care.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Immigration", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878013", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878006, "askingMemberId": 5227, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110587", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the cumulative impact of the extension and retrospective application of settlement requirements, including impacts on (a) workforce retention, (b) industrial", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Immigration", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878006", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878004, "askingMemberId": 5227, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110586", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her department has made of the potential impact of implementing retrospective a increase in the 5 year ILR route to 10 years on the wellbeing of children and families currently in the ", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Immigration", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878004", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877997, "askingMemberId": 5227, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110585", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of implementing transitional arrangements for people on the 5 year ILR route.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Immigration", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877997", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878064, "askingMemberId": 5219, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110584", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of introducing Making Tax Digital at the same time as removing the wear and tear allowance on childminders.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Childminding: Taxation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878064", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878056, "askingMemberId": 5219, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110583", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of ringfencing Section 31 grants.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878056", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878033, "askingMemberId": 5214, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110582", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate his Department has made for when the backlog of the Civil Service Pension payments will be resolved.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Civil Servants: Workplace Pensions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878033", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878026, "askingMemberId": 5214, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110581", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to establish who is responsible for the delays in payments of the Civil Service Pension Scheme and ensure they are held accountable.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Civil Servants: Workplace Pensions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878026", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878163, "askingMemberId": 5212, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110580", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his department has made of the findings of the Held in Our Hearts Impact Report on hospital-to-home bereavement support for families following the loss of a baby.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Infant Mortality: Bereavement Counselling", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878163", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877990, "askingMemberId": 5212, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110579", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what progress has been made on the development and publication of guidance on access to single-sex spaces for women; and when she expects this guidance to be published.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Women: Public Places", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877990", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878139, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110577", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make it his policy to extend access to free and subsidized vitamin D supplements to at-risk groups identified in NICE PH56.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Vitamin D: Dietary Supplements", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878139", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878137, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110576", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will develop a vitamin D food fortification policy.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food: Vitamin D", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878137", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878136, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110575", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will ask the Scientific Advisory Committee on Nutrition to review whether current vitamin D supplementation recommendations (a) adequately serve all population groups and (b) take adequate ac", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Vitamin D: Deficiency Diseases", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878136", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878135, "askingMemberId": 5207, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110574", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to (a) collect and (b) publish vitamin D deficiency statistics broken down by ethnicity.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Vitamin D: Deficiency Diseases", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878135", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877996, "askingMemberId": 5202, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110573", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department has taken to ensure that veterinary practices are subject to effective regulation.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Veterinary Services: Regulation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877996", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877995, "askingMemberId": 5202, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110572", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that dental practices are subject to effective regulation.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dental Services: Regulation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877995", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877939, "askingMemberId": 5194, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110571", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department has taken to provide resources to help ensure (a) reports of fraud are investigated and (b) victims of fraud receive support.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fraud", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877939", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878192, "askingMemberId": 5164, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110570", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, by what route installers can access funding under the extended ECO4 scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878192", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878107, "askingMemberId": 5164, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110569", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to encourage food surplus redistribution in the baking industry.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878107", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878106, "askingMemberId": 5164, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110568", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what support his Department provides to the baking industry to decarbonise.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878106", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877992, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110567", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 3 February 2026 to Question 107846 on GP Practice lists, how many and what proportion of patients registered on 1 January 2026 were foreign nationals.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "GP Practice Lists: Foreign Nationals", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877992", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878171, "askingMemberId": 5157, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110566", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of proposals to merge Section 1 and Section 2 firearms licensing on (a) employment and (b) economic activity in rural communities, including impact", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Firearms: Licensing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878171", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878179, "askingMemberId": 5140, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110565", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the (a) potential impact of accrued interest on the total debt balances of Plan 2 borrowers and (b) number of graduates whose monthly repayments are lower than the monthly intere", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878179", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878178, "askingMemberId": 5140, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110564", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent estimate her Department has made of the (a) proportion of Plan 2 student loans that will be fully repaid within the 30-year term and (b) average total interest accrued by a Plan 2 borrower over the ", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878178", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878177, "askingMemberId": 5140, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110563", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many dentists have been successfully recruited and retained in the Thornbury and Yate constituency under the 'golden hello' scheme since its inception.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878177", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878176, "askingMemberId": 5140, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110562", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of recent trends in levels of regional disparity in Dental Delivery Rates between the South West and London; and what steps he will take to increase delivery in the Sout", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878176", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878175, "askingMemberId": 5140, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110561", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the sunset clause for the Energy Saving Materials VAT relief on 31 March 2027, whether her Department has conducted an impact assessment on the potential effect on Net Zero targets if the relief re", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878175", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878112, "askingMemberId": 5138, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110560", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to publish a detailed breakdown of the Ministry of Defence's financial losses due to fraud and economic crime.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Defence: Economic Crime", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878112", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878111, "askingMemberId": 5138, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110559", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to give a single senior official authority over different parts of the Ministry of Defence responsible for combating financial losses due to fraud.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Defence: Fraud", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878111", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878110, "askingMemberId": 5138, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110558", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to set a department-wide strategy to bring down the Ministry of Defence's financial losses due to fraud and economic crime.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Defence: Economic Crime", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878110", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878032, "askingMemberId": 5137, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110557", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps his Department has taken with the Scottish Government to ensure the Warm Homes Plan helps support households in Scotland.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Warm Homes Plan: Scotland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878032", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877892, "askingMemberId": 5128, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110556", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, when will her department plans to publish the Economic Diplomacy Review.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Foreign Relations", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877892", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878156, "askingMemberId": 5125, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110553", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with the Northern Ireland Department of Health and the Northern Ireland Executive to ensure that families of children and young people with cancer in Northern Ireland ca", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cancer: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878156", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878154, "askingMemberId": 5125, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110552", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what Barnett consequentials arise for Northern Ireland as a result of the \u00a310 million per year funding announced to cover travel costs for children and young people with cancer in England.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Expenditure: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878154", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878168, "askingMemberId": 5122, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110551", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department has assessed a risk of localised extinction of swan populations as a result of outbreaks of H5N1 avian influenza in (a) England, (b) Warwickshire, and (c) Stratf", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878168", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878166, "askingMemberId": 5122, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110550", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has considered treating static populations of wild birds, including swans and wildfowl that remain in defined local areas, as eligible for vaccination against av", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878166", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878165, "askingMemberId": 5122, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110549", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the policy reason is for limiting avian influenza vaccination to birds kept in zoological settings.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878165", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878147, "askingMemberId": 5122, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110548", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the University of Manchester article entitled The right to play: making play a policy and practice priority, what steps her Department is taking to safeguard (a) break and (b) lunchtimes in sc", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Children's Play: School Day", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878147", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878146, "askingMemberId": 5122, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110547", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an assessment of the recommendations from The University of Manchester article entitled The right to play: making play a policy and practice priority published in September 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Children's Play", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878146", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878145, "askingMemberId": 5122, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110546", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to help tackle the harm caused by sodium valproate to people in (a) England, (b) Warwickshire, and (c) Stratford-on-Avon.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sodium Valproate: Side Effects", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878145", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878089, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110545", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he has had with the Department for Education on assessing the potential impact of reducing assistive technology support during higher education on disabled people\u2019s employment outcomes.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Assistive Technology: Higher Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878089", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878088, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110544", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the impact of changes to Disabled Students\u2019 Allowance support on demand for Access to Work or other employment support schemes.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Disabled Students' Allowances", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878088", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878087, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110543", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department has collected post-implementation data on the academic performance or withdrawal rates of students previously supported with specialist assistive software.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Disabled Students' Allowances: Assistive Technology", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878087", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878086, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110542", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether any further reductions or restrictions to DSA-funded assistive technology or non-medical support are currently under consideration.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Disabled Students' Allowances: Assistive Technology", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878086", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878084, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110541", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many formal requests for meetings her Department has received from disability sector organisations regarding recent DSA policy changes since October 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Disabled Students' Allowances", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878084", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878083, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110540", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department has reviewed the findings of the National Association of Disability Practitioners\u2019 December 2025 critique of the Equality Impact Assessment relating to Disabled Students\u2019 Allowance change", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Disabled Students' Allowances", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878083", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877978, "askingMemberId": 5110, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110539", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) large sites and (b) hotel  sites for Asylum Seekers are there in the Falkirk Council area.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Falkirk", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877978", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878031, "askingMemberId": 5103, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110538", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to prevent the illegal killing of hen harriers.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hen Harriers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878031", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878190, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110537", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the answer of 2 February 2026 to question 108885 on Defence: Artificial Intelligence, what is the full scope of the AI Enabled Cyber Defence project.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878190", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878189, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110536", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the answer of 2 February 2026 to question 108885 on Defence: Artificial Intelligence, what is the full scope of the Underwater Acoustic Foundation Model project.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878189", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878188, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110535", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the answer of 2 February 2026 to question 108885 on Defence: Artificial Intelligence, what is the full scope of the Autonomous Mission Execution project.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878188", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878187, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110534", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the answer of 2 February 2026 to question 108885 on Defence: Artificial Intelligence, what is the full scope of the AI Exploitation for the Digital Targeting Web project.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878187", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878186, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110533", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the answer of 2 February 2026  to question 108885 on Defence: Artificial Intelligence, what is the full scope of the Advanced Reasoning for Decision Advantage project.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878186", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878185, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110532", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the answer of 28 January 2026 to answer 107227 on Challenger Tanks: Exports, what progress he has made in exploring export opportunities for Challenger 3 and its capabilities.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Challenger Tanks: Exports", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878185", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878184, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110531", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if the Ajax Programme is within the scope of the Defence Growth Deal for Wales announced in September 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ajax Vehicles: Wales", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878184", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878183, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110530", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what is the remit of the Wildcat Maritime Force Operational Advantage Group.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Wildcat Helicopters: Unmanned Air Systems", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878183", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878182, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110529", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the need to introduce a legal requirement to consider access to hospital helipads in any planning application in the vicinity of a hospital.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hospitals: Helicopters", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878182", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878181, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110528", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of operating in Ukraine and the High North simultaneously on (a) British Army, (b) Royal Navy and (c) Royal Air Force resources.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Arctic and Ukraine: Armed Forces", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878181", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878070, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110527", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential benefits of adopting the .338 calibre for Project Cairns.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Firearms: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878070", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878068, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110526", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reason has he cancelled the contract with NP Aerospace to provide x-ray scanners for Army bomb disposal units.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Defence Equipment: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878068", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878048, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110525", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what is the remit of the fleet experimental squadron.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Navy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878048", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878046, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110524", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to start the Ajax\u2019s Capability Drop 4 standard Reliability Growth Trials.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ajax Vehicles: Testing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878046", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878044, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110523", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what additional capabilities will be included in Ajax Capability Drop 4 over Drop 3.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ajax Vehicles: Modernisation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878044", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878040, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110522", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, by when will all current Ajax-family vehicles be brought up to Drop 3 standard.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ajax Vehicles: Modernisation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878040", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878038, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110521", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to page 12 of the Police reform white paper entitled From Local to National: A New Model for Policing (CP1489), what assessment she has made of the potential merits of decoupling the po", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Police: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878038", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878037, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110520", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to page 12 of the Police reform white paper entitled From Local to National: A New Model for Policing\u201d (CP1489), what plans she has to bring forward legislative proposals for vetting st", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Police: Disciplinary Proceedings", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878037", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878036, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110519", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to page 11 of the white paper entitled From Local to National: A New Model for Policing (CP1489), what her proposed timetable is for publishing new national policing guarantees.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Police: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878036", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878035, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110518", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to page 11 of the Police reform white paper entitled From Local to National: A New Model for Policing (CP1489), from which financial year does the revised police funding formula apply.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Police: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878035", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878172, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110517", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps he is taking to ensure (a) the UK is establishing a resilient clean energy supply chain and (b) strengthen cooperation with European partners.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Clean Energy: Supply Chains", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878172", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878103, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110516", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to help coordinate services between higher education institutions and NHS mental health services for students.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Students: Mental Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878103", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878099, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110515", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what mechanisms are in place to ensure that universities share learning from reviews of student deaths by suicide.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Students: Suicide", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878099", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878098, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110514", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to ask the Office for Students to introduce a regulatory condition on student mental health and wellbeing.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Students: Mental Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878098", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878097, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110513", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how students and bereaved families are being involved in the work of the Implementation Taskforce on student mental health and suicide prevention.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Students: Mental Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878097", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878095, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110512", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what evidence the Government has considered on whether the absence of a statutory duty of care contributes to inconsistent responses by universities to students at risk of harm.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Universities: Liability", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878095", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877889, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110511", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether her Department has assessed the adequacy of the Green Book's methodology of the social and health benefits of places of worship, including when determining levels of capital and tax relie", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Religious Buildings: Tax Allowances", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877889", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877888, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110510", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reason repairs and maintenance are treated differently for VAT purposes for (a) places of worship and (b) museums and art galleries.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Repairs and Maintenance: VAT", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877888", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877887, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110509", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of whether the \u00a392 million Places of Worship Renewal Fund over four years provides equivalent financial support to places of worship compared with the Previous Listed", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Places of Worship Renewal Fund: VAT Exemptions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877887", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877886, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110508", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the potential impact on places of worship of replacing the Listed Places of Worship Grant Scheme with the Places of Worship Renewal Fund, in the context of the imp", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Places of Worship Renewal Fund: VAT Exemptions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877886", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878072, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110507", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, when he plans to hold the consultation on proposed changes to NDAs under the Employment Rights Bill; and what is the planned timeline for implementation.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Conditions of Employment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878072", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877881, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110506", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to establish a development corporation in support of construction related to the Forest City 1 plan to build a city of a million people between Newmarket and Ha", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877881", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877893, "askingMemberId": 5056, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110505", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance she provides to secondary schools on the identification of speech and language needs in children entering the school from primary education.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Educational Needs: Speech and Language Disorders", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877893", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878069, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110504", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, is Lord Mandelson currently in receipt of a government salary.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878069", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878082, "askingMemberId": 5050, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110503", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she taking to help support councils to seize and crush vehicles involved in fly-tipping.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fly-tipping: Enforcement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878082", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878065, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110502", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to help ensure that Hong Kong SAR passport holders in the asylum system have access to appropriate mental health support.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Hong Kong", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878065", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878063, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110501", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the extent to which exclusions from the BN(O) visa route for Hong Kong born-persons born after 1 Just 1997 and without BN(O) status, contribute to HKSAR passport holder", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Hong Kong", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878063", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878062, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110500", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many persons who are HKSAR passport holders have claimed asylum in the UK in each of the last five calendar years; and how many were (a) granted refugee status, (b) granted humanitarian protection", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Hong Kong", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878062", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878061, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110499", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she will expand eligibility for the BN(O) route to include Hongkongers born on or after 1 July 1997; what assessment she has made of the number of people currently excluded for this reason.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Immigration: Hong Kong", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878061", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878060, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110498", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she will confirm that the current exemption from English language requirements for applicants aged 65 and over will be maintained for those applying for indefinite leave to remain.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Immigration: Older People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878060", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878059, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110497", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she will introduce an exemption from earnings requirement for indefinite leave to remain for persons who were (a) children or (b) enrolled in higher education for all or part of the relevant q", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Immigration: Children and Overseas Students", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878059", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878058, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110496", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of having full transitional arrangements when introducing an earned settlement scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Immigration", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878058", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878055, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110495", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the 10 per cent commission on park home resales, including potential interactions with tax receipts and local authority adu", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Park Homes: Sales", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878055", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878054, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110494", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the feasibility of requiring that utility supply arrangements on (a) new and (b) extended residential park home sites provide supplier choice for r", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Park Homes: Utilities", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878054", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878053, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110493", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, local authorities have had departmental engagement, intervention or support due to concerns about park homes enforcement capacity or performance in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Park Homes", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878053", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878052, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110492", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department provides to local authorities on (a) identifying and (b) tackling unlawful (i) charges, (ii) bullying and (iii) intimidation by park home site operat", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Park Homes", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878052", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878051, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110491", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will take legislative steps to amend the Mobile Homes (Site Licensing) (England) Regulations 2014 to (a) require local authorities to review site licences and site licence ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Park Homes: Licensing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878051", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878050, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110490", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to improve consistency of local authority enforcement of park home site licensing and related protections for residents.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Park Homes: Licensing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878050", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878049, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110489", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 16 April 2025 to Question 44299 on Park Homes: Sales, when he plans to seek evidence from the sector on the potential impact of paying site owners a com", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Park Homes: Sales", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878049", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877921, "askingMemberId": 5036, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110488", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of introducing a permanent exemption to Jury service for people suffering from lifelong or degenerative conditions.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Juries: Chronic Illnesses", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877921", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878153, "askingMemberId": 5030, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110487", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Plan 2 student loan borrowers there are resident in Stroud.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878153", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878144, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110486", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish guidance for members of the Civil Service Pension Scheme who are employed by civil service contractors on how they can access their pensions.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878144", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877993, "askingMemberId": 4874, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110485", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what is the (a) gross and (b) net revenue raised for her Department from the UK Emissions Trading Scheme in the 2024-25 financial year, broken down by auction receipts, administrative costs, and any revenue recyclin", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877993", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877967, "askingMemberId": 4874, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110484", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of the European Union\u2019s proposed Industrial Accelerator Act on the integration of UK-based manufacturers in European supply chains.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877967", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878157, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110483", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent discussions he has had with her Polish counterparts on Reciprocal Enforcement of Maintenance Orders.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Children: Maintenance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878157", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878141, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110482", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether she has had recent discussions with her Polish counterpart on outstanding cases of children abducted from the UK to Poland.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Poland: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878141", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877984, "askingMemberId": 4860, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110481", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of new prisons places that will result from the building of prisons that received planning approval since 5 July 2024; what his proposed timetable is for these prison place", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisons: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877984", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877983, "askingMemberId": 4860, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110480", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners who are biologically (a) male and (b) female are housed in prisons designated for the opposite sex.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisoners: Transgender People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877983", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877982, "askingMemberId": 4860, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110479", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many probation officers have been recruited since 5 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Probation Officers: Recruitment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877982", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877981, "askingMemberId": 4860, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110478", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers have been recruited since 5 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prison Officers: Recruitment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877981", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877980, "askingMemberId": 4860, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110477", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to build new female prisons during this Parliament.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisons: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877980", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878149, "askingMemberId": 4811, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110475", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if his Department will bring forward changes to allow independent celebrants to conduct legally binding weddings.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Marriage", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878149", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878148, "askingMemberId": 4811, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110474", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the policy justification is for applying interest to instalment payments of Electric Vehicle Excise Duty; and whether her Department considered alternative models for collecting eVED.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electric Vehicles: Excise Duties", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878148", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877969, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110473", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of Conflict Management Dogs as a less-lethal option for Counter Terrorism Specialist Firearms Officers; and what plans she has to ensure that capab", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Police: Dogs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877969", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878079, "askingMemberId": 4785, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110472", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will review the cost of travel for all families of children with health conditions requiring repeated attendance at specialist centres.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878079", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877991, "askingMemberId": 4785, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110471", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to his Answer of Question 108286 on Surrey and Borders Partnership NHS Foundation Trust: ADHD and Autism, what steps he is taking to help support Surrey and Borders to meet their dia", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877991", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878047, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110470", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will take steps to improve accessibility for SMEs to the research and development tax credit system.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Research: Tax Allowances", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878047", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878125, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110469", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, pursuant to the Answer of 3 February to Question 108284 on Energy: Databases, whether the continuing assessment with respect to NEED and other datasets comprising household spending on energy", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Energy: Prices", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878125", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878224, "askingMemberId": 4736, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110468", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress he has made on the Scottish allocation of the New Defence Growth Deals announced in September 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Defence: Industry", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878224", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878223, "askingMemberId": 4736, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110467", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions his Department has had with the Scottish Government on  establishing a Defence Technical Excellence College in Scotland.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Defence: Technical Excellence Colleges", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878223", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878222, "askingMemberId": 4736, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110466", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential benefits of  the development of a Regional Defence and Security Cluster in Scotland; and what progress has been made following early-stage discussions with potential p", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Defence: Scotland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878222", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878220, "askingMemberId": 4736, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110465", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many projects have been (a) funded by the UKDI Defence and security accelerator and (b) of these how many were based in Scotland.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Defence: Innovation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878220", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878025, "askingMemberId": 4716, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110464", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what his proposed timetable is for introducing the vaping product registration scheme under the Tobacco and Vapes Bill including indicative dates for (a) consultation, (b) publication of regulation", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878025", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878024, "askingMemberId": 4716, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110463", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to introduce minimum testing standards for vaping product testing.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878024", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878023, "askingMemberId": 4716, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110462", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues about the role (a) HM Revenue and Customs and (b) Border Force will have in verifying compliance with the vaping product registration and testing", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878023", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878022, "askingMemberId": 4716, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110461", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of resources required by Trading Standards to enforce the registration and testing regime for vaping products since the regime was introduced", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878022", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878109, "askingMemberId": 4658, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110460", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether alternative reporting frequencies were considered under Making Tax Digital for self-employed workers whose income is irregular or seasonal.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Self-employed: Income Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878109", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878105, "askingMemberId": 4658, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110459", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment has been made of the impact of Making Tax Digital for Income Tax on workers in the creative industries and gig economy.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Arts and Gig Economy: Income Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878105", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878085, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110458", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions she has had with colleagues in the Department for Education regarding steps taken to increase awareness of the dangers of swimming in (a) cold water, (b) open w", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878085", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878041, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110457", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with local authorities on the provision of services to prevent knife crime among young people.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878041", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878034, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110456", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has been made of the adequacy of national guidance for schools regarding (a) incidents and (b) reports of knife possession on school grounds.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878034", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877833, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110455", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent steps she has taken alongside local authorities to reduce traffic congestion in (a) Slough and (b) Berkshire.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Road Traffic Control: Berkshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877833", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878121, "askingMemberId": 4603, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110454", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the level of respondent burden to provide evidence on the need for an additional data point in the consultation entitled Assessing User Needs for Additional Response Options for th", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878121", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877989, "askingMemberId": 4591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110453", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of Think Pharmacy First campaign on helping to encourage people use pharmacies for treatment.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877989", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878143, "askingMemberId": 4523, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110452", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to help improve safety for the LGBT+ community.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "LGBT+ People: Safety", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878143", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878142, "askingMemberId": 4523, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110451", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to help tackle homophobia in the Metropolitan Police force.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Metropolitan Police: Homophobia", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878142", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878212, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110450", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what is the out of service date for Watchkeeper.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878212", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878211, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110449", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish a list of all (a) UK and (b) overseas sites currently used for long-range kinetic drone testing broken down by the maximum range of each location.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Unmanned Air Systems: Testing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878211", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878210, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110448", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether there is a maximum range at which long-range kinetic drones can be tested.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Unmanned Air Systems: Testing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878210", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878209, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110447", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish a list of all (a) UK and (b) overseas sites currently used for long-range kinetic drone testing.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Unmanned Air Systems: Testing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878209", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878208, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110446", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January to Question 107733 on Unmanned Air Systems: Procurement, if he will provide the reason that the Protector RG MK1 did not declare Initial Operating Capability.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Unmanned Air Systems: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878208", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878207, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110445", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January to Question 107733 on Unmanned Air Systems: Procurement, how many Protector RG MK1s need to be in use in order to declare Initial Operating Capability.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Unmanned Air Systems: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878207", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878206, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110444", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January to Question 107733 on Unmanned Air Systems: Procurement, how many Protector RG MK1s are currently in use.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Unmanned Air Systems: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878206", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878205, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110443", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February to Question 108700 on Strategic Defence Review, whether the \u00a3270 billion to be spent on Defence in this Parliament includes funding for Ukraine.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Defence: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878205", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878204, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110442", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February to Question 108700 on Strategic Defence Review, if he will breakdown \u00a3270 billion to be spent on Defence in this Parliament in each remaining financial year of this Parliament", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878204", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878203, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110441", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February to Question 108700 on Strategic Defence Review, how much of the \u00a3270 billion to be spent on Defence in this Parliament will be spent on the procurement of uncrewed systems for", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Uncrewed Systems: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878203", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878202, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110440", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February to Question 108700 on Strategic Defence Review, how much will be spent on Defence in the next Parliament.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Defence: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878202", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878201, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110439", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February to Question 108700 on Strategic Defence Review, if he will publish a breakdown of the \u00a3270 billion to be spent on Defence in this Parliament as a percentage of GDP for each re", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878201", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878200, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110438", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February to Question 108700 on Strategic Defence Review, how much of the \u00a3270 billion to be spent on Defence in this Parliament will be spent in each remaining financial year of this P", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878200", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878199, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110437", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February to Question 108700 on Strategic Defence Review, how much of the \u00a3270 billion to be spent on Defence in this Parliament is defined as (a) the MOD budget and (b) NATO declared d", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878199", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878198, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110436", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent progress his Department has made on implementing Project Ark Royal.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Aircraft Carriers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878198", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878197, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110435", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent progress his Department has made on implementing Project VIXEN.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Unmanned Air Systems", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878197", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878196, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110434", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many procurement orders are currently awaiting approval by the (a) Treasury and (b) Cabinet Office for a value of (i) over \u00a31 million, (ii) \u00a3500,000 to \u00a31 million and (iii) under \u00a3500,000 since 5 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Defence: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878196", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878195, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110433", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to implement a new project to replace Project Lily.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Unmanned Marine Systems: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878195", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878194, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110432", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether a new competition will be started to replace Project Lily.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Unmanned Marine Systems: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878194", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878193, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110431", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will state the reason for the termination of Project Lily.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Unmanned Marine Systems: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878193", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877864, "askingMemberId": 4510, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110430", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment she has made of the impact of the Independent Commission for Aid Impact on the transparency of UK overseas development assistance.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Development Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877864", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877863, "askingMemberId": 4510, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110429", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment she has made of the impact of the Independent Commission for Aid Impact on the effectiveness of UK overseas development assistance spending.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877863", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878076, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110428", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much additional funding an SME is expected to contribute per apprentice following the reduction in government co-investment once levy-paying employers have exhausted their levy funds.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Apprenticeship Levy: Small Businesses", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878076", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878075, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110427", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what distributional analysis his Department has made of the potential impact of (a) reducing government co-investment once levy-paying employers have exhausted their levy funds, and (b) removing the upl", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Apprenticeship Levy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878075", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878074, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110426", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of recent changes to (a) co-investment in apprenticeships and (b) levy accounts on apprenticeship starts.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Apprenticeship Levy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878074", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878073, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110425", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of (a) the impact of reducing government co-investment in apprenticeships once levy-paying employers have exhausted their levy funds, and (b) the impact of removi", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Apprenticeship Levy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878073", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878161, "askingMemberId": 4441, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110424", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Fireworks Regulations 2004 on tackling the purchase of fireworks for anti-social use.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fireworks: Anti-social Behaviour", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878161", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878160, "askingMemberId": 4441, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110423", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps he is taking with local councils to tackle the anti-social use of fireworks in Hertfordshire.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fireworks: Hertfordshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878160", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878039, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110422", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the answer of 2 December 2025, to Question 94697, on House of Commons Director General: Public Appointments, whether the permanent Director General of the Propriety, Ethics and Constitution Group wil", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Propriety and Constitution Group: Recruitment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878039", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878028, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110421", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether the deadline for applications for the appointment of the Chair of Ofcom was set for either (a) 18 December 2025 or (b) 5 January 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ofcom: Public Appointments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878028", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877986, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110420", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 7 November 2025, to Question 86672, on Palantir, whether there were communications between Embassy officials and Global Counsel over the visit, and ", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Palantir", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877986", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877985, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110419", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether Lord Mandelson used a non-corporate email address, in whole or in part, for Government business, whilst Ambassador to the United States.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Lord Mandelson", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877985", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877979, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110418", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will place in the Library a copy of the election purdah guidance distributed to Whitehall departments for the Gorton and Denton Parliamentary by-election.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "By-elections: Gorton and Denton", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877979", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877977, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110417", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the answer of 2 February 2026, to Question 108238, on Senior Civil Servants: Redundancy Pay, for what reason his exit payment was a severance payment.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Senior Civil Servants: Redundancy Pay", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877977", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877976, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110416", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what changes have been made to (a) Cabinet Office, (b) Government Digital Service and (c) Government Communications Service guidance on the use of (i) HM Government and (ii) UK Government branding, including whe", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Government Departments: Publicity", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877976", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877975, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110415", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will request that the Ethics and Integrity Commission undertakes an investigation in Arden Strategies and lobbying integrity.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Arden Strategies: Lobbying", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877975", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877974, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110414", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to his oral statement of 2 February 2026, Official Report, Column 47, on US Department of Justice Release of Files, whether he has a formal terms of reference for his review into Lord Mandelson; w", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Lord Mandelson", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877974", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877973, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110413", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Cabinet Secretary has received representations from Gordon Brown on communications between Lord Mandelson and Jeffery Epstein.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Lord Mandelson", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877973", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877972, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110412", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether Lord Mandelson had a No10 pass whilst he was Ambassador to the United States.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Lord Mandelson", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877972", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877971, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110411", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the answer of 13 October 2025 to Question 77563 on Palantir, whether there is a record of who the Prime Minister (a) met and (b) spoke to during that visit.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Palantir", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877971", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877970, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110410", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what formal title and position John Pond held on 2 August 2009 within Downing Street.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prime Minister: Email", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877970", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877865, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110409", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the answer of 5 January 2026, to Question 100882, on Disinformation, whether Storyzy is used to monitor content relating to gender issues.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Disinformation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877865", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877891, "askingMemberId": 4368, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110408", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with counterparts in EU Member States on simplifying CITES-related processes for UK musicians travelling by train to perform in Europe.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877891", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877890, "askingMemberId": 4368, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110407", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether her Department has had discussions with transport operators, including Eurostar, on the provision and availability of guidance for the carriage of specialist equipment, including musical instruments.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877890", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877913, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110406", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what information his Department holds on the number of properties for rent in the private rented sector in each of the last three years.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Private Rented Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877913", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877912, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110405", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of changes in council tax on the cost of living from April 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Council Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877912", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877911, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110404", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his policy to amend the Housing supply: indicators of new supply statistics to include a rolling statistic on the yearly shortfall in relation to his 1.5 milli", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877911", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877910, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110403", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 13 January 2026 to Question 103186, on Asylum: Council Housing, which local authorities are participating in the asylum accommodation pilots.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Council Housing: Asylum", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877910", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877909, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110402", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 13 January 2026 to Question 102770 on Waste Disposal: Birmingham, whether the meeting between the Secretary of State and Unite was minuted.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Waste Disposal: Birmingham", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877909", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877908, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110401", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the answer of 19 January 2026, to Question 104773, on Housing: Construction, what is his proposed timeline for the delivery of the 9,000 homes.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877908", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877907, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110400", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2025 to Question 103891 on Business Rates: Tax Allowances, what is the evidential basis for the statement that the temporary Retail, Hospitality and Leisure relief has been windi", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Business Rates: Tax Allowances", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877907", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877906, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110399", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 14 January 2026 to Question 103283 on New Towns: Adlington, on what evidential basis was Adlington added to the list of New Towns.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877906", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877905, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110398", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 20 January 2026 to Question 105220 on MHCLG: Publicity, which suppliers his Department has used for publishing content in foreign languages in the last ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government: Publicity", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877905", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877904, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110397", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answer of 12 February 2025 to Question HL4510 on Community Relations: Muslims, what information her Department holds on the reason that the Muslim Council of Britain's written ev", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Order and Hate Crime Legislation Review", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877904", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877903, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110396", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 20 January 2026, to Question 104987, on Strategic Migration Partnership: Finance, whether her Department has determined the funding envelope for the 2025-26 funding; and on w", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Strategic Migration Partnerships: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877903", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877902, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110395", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her policy is on whether current Police and Crime Commissioners in (a) England and (b) Wales will serve their full term in office before the positions are discontinued, where (i) there is a combi", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Police and Crime Commissioners", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877902", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877901, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110394", "questionText": "To ask the Leader of the House, what guidance he issues to Departments on whether they may decline to publish or signpost information which has otherwise been released to members of the public under Freedom of Information laws.", "answeringBodyId": 34, "answeringBodyName": "Leader of the House", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Government Departments: Freedom of Information", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877901", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877900, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110393", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether all Arm\u2019s Length Bodies, including public corporations and private companies owned by the Government, are required to follow the Cabinet Office local and Parliamentary by-election election purdah guidanc", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Arms Length Bodies: By-elections", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877900", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877899, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110392", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December 2025, to Question 95394, on Housing: Construction, what estimate has ONS made of per capita housebuilding rate in each constituent nation of the UK over the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877899", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877898, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110391", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 21 January 2026, to Question 105789, on Ministers and Public Consultation: Evidence, whether the Government accepts evidence in written consultations from organisations subject to the p", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877898", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877897, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110390", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Northern Growth Strategy, January 2026, CP1485, paragraph 4 and footnotes 3 and 4, what is the evidential basis for the underlying statistics of the 2.2% pr", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Economic Growth: North of England", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877897", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877895, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110389", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 21 January 2026, to Question 105789, on Ministers and Public Consultation: Evidence, whether the Muslim Council of Britain is on the list of organisations subject to the poli", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Muslim Council of Britain", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877895", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877838, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110388", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, for what reason he has incorporated Planning policy for traveller sites into the National Planning Policy Framework.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Travellers: Caravan Sites", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877838", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877837, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110387", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Delegation of the setting of planning fees to local planning authorities, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Fair Funding Review on ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Planning Permission: Fees and Charges", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877837", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877836, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110386", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the answer of 21 November 2025, to Question 88668, on Flags: Palestine, and further to the UK Statement at the High-Level Conference for the Implementation of the Two", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Flags: Palestine", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877836", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877835, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110385", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the answer of 27 November 2025, to Question 90708, and 20 October 2025 to Question 85948, on Immigrant: English Language, what steps she plans to take to support the integration of asylum ", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: English Language", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877835", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877834, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110384", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether (a) Judges' Lodgings and (b) other workplace accommodation are within the scope of the proposed overnight visitor levy.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Visitor Levy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877834", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877862, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110383", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what legislative steps will be required to introduce the Graduated Driver Licensing scheme by October 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Driving Licences", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877862", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877861, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110382", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on what date her Department first raised with the BBC that the announcement on Graduated Driver Licensing scheme could be made on the BBC\u2019s day of road safety coverage.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Driving Licences", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877861", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877860, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110381", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps she is taking to ensure that employers provide supportive, flexible environments, including temperature control, modified duties, and open dialogue to prevent talent loss due to employees' menopausa", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employment: Menopause", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877860", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877855, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110380", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with the devolved institutions on Local Growth Funds.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Growth Fund", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877855", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877854, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110379", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps he is taking to support the hospitality, pub and food to go sectors to remain in business.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hospitality Industry: Government Assistance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877854", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877853, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110378", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to help improve the profitability of UK farm produce.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Profitability", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877853", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877852, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110377", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department has undertaken an assessment of the environmental impacts associated with poor animal health.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Animal Welfare", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877852", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877851, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110376", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to ensure effective regulation and enforcement is in place to tackle the environmental and financial impact of waste crime.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Waste: Crime", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877851", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877850, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110375", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her most recent annual estimate is for the amount of waste deposited illegally across England and Wales.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fly-tipping", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877850", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877849, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110374", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of the labour supply to the agri-food sector.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Employment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877849", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878043, "askingMemberId": 4126, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110373", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent progress she has made on responding to the Migration Advisory Committee\u2019s recommendations on the minimum income requirement for the UK\u2019s spouse and partner visa routes.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878043", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878167, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110372", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what discussions she has had with Ofcom on (a) tackling the proliferation of fake AI generated Auschwitz photographs on social media and (b) the potential impact of those photographs on", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Holocaust: Disinformation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878167", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878113, "askingMemberId": 4118, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110371", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment her Department has made of the potential economic and social impact on rural pubs and hospitality businesses of reducing the drink driving limit; and whether alternative measures have been consi", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Driving under Influence: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878113", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877962, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110370", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, on how many occasions have Ministers in his Department have met with representatives of Royal Mail since September 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877962", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878030, "askingMemberId": 4084, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110369", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether comparisons of the cost of maintained and independent special school placements take account of differences in (a) pupil needs, (b) placement complexity, and (c) length of placement.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Educational Needs: Costs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878030", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878027, "askingMemberId": 4084, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110368", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what (a) methodology and (b) data the Department uses to (i) calculate and (ii) compare the average cost of maintained special school placements and independent school placements.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Educational Needs: Costs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878027", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878221, "askingMemberId": 4076, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110367", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if she will make a statement on the recent ministerial visit to Yemen.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878221", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878219, "askingMemberId": 4076, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110366", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many students have claimed asylum (a) while studying in the UK and (b) after completing their studies in each of the last three years.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878219", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878218, "askingMemberId": 4076, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110365", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many visitors from (a) India, (b) Pakistan, (c) Bangladesh and (d) Nepal were refused visas in 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878218", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878217, "askingMemberId": 4076, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110364", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many complaints she has received on the new electronic visa system.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878217", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878213, "askingMemberId": 4008, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110363", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when she will publish her Local Media Strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878213", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877880, "askingMemberId": 4008, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110362", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Fuller Inquiry Phase 2 Report: Government Interim Update on Progress, when he plans to respond to recommendations 29, 60, 61, 62, 63, 64, 65, 66, 69, 71 and 72.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877880", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877879, "askingMemberId": 4008, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110361", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the efficacy of the Scottish Government's Burial and Cremations Department Funeral Director Code of Practice in reducing the number of funeral directors that are in breach of the la", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877879", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878077, "askingMemberId": 3957, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110360", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of levels of current capacity for in-centre dialysis services; and what plans his Department has to ensure that renal service capacity matches both current a", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Kidney Diseases: Dialysis Machines", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878077", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878164, "askingMemberId": 3952, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110359", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment his Department had made of the potential merits of including the metals recycling industry on the list of eligible sectors for the forthcoming British Industrial Competitiveness Scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Energy Intensive Industries", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878164", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877961, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110358", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what comparisons and best practices can be learned from other countries to help improve air quality in England in (a) ambient air and (b) indoor air.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Air Pollution: Pollution Control", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877961", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877959, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110357", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which Government departments other than his Department are able to have the biggest impact on improving levels of ambient air pollution; and how their policies seek to achieve this.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Air Pollution: Departmental Coordination", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877959", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877957, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110356", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to support change on ambient air quality across Government.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Air Pollution: Departmental Coordination", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877957", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877956, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110355", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of data capture and analysis for air quality within England.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Air Pollution: Monitoring", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877956", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877953, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110354", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of  funding and devolved powers to ensure the comprehensive monitoring of air quality in England.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Air Pollution: Monitoring", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877953", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877952, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110353", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she had made of the adequacy of alignment between national government targets and obligations and local government actions to improve ambient air quality in England.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Air Pollution: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877952", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877950, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110352", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department\u00a0has made of how well examples of local best practice that exist to enforce existing legislation and regulation to improve local air quality are being rol", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Air Pollution: Pollution Control", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877950", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877949, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110351", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of whether examples of best practice exist in England to achieve compliance with legislation and regulation to improve local air quality in each", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Air Pollution: Pollution Control", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877949", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877948, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110350", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of potential barriers and/or challenges to achieving national targets, requirements and performance standards for ambient air quality, indoor ai", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Air Pollution: Pollution Control", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877948", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877946, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110349", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of national targets, requirements and performance standards for air quality and national emission ceilings in protecting public health, cli", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Air Pollution: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877946", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877944, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110348", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the national targets, requirements and performance standards are for ambient air pollution and national emission ceilings in the Air Quality Environment Act target delivery plan a", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Air Pollution: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877944", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877943, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110347", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information her Department holds on the ten most common causes of air pollution in England in (a) ambient air and (b) indoor air.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Air Pollution", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877943", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877920, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110346", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what evidence exists of the direct and indirect impact of air pollution on (a) crop yields, (b) biodiversity, (c) pollinator, (d) rain, (e) stratospheric ozone, (f) water quality and (", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Air Pollution", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877920", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877919, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110345", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what evidence exists of direct and indirect impacts of ambient air pollution\u00a0on (a) the climate, (b) the environment and (c) public health and their cascading effects.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Air Pollution", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877919", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877917, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110344", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the the top five impacts of air pollution in England on each of (a) the climate, (b) the environment and (c) public health and their cascadin", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877917", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877916, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110343", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department holds data on the top five sources in tonnes of primary air pollution emissions in England for each of (i) fine particulate matter (PM2.5); (ii) nitrogen dioxide", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877916", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878045, "askingMemberId": 1576, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110342", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on whether the Security Service was aware of (a) the illegal activities of Jeffrey Epstein, (b) his relationship with Andrew Mountbatten Windsor and (c) advice gi", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Jeffrey Epstein", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878045", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877998, "askingMemberId": 1516, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110341", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he plans to implement proportionate regulation of third-party litigation funding agreements in this parliament.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877998", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878214, "askingMemberId": 1491, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110340", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the environmental and health impacts of their School Food guidance in the context of the 2025 EAT-Lancet Commission; and how she plans to respond to the Commission\u2019s P", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878214", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877960, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110339", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the answer of 8 September 2025 to question 71975 on RAF Akrotiri: Military Aircraft, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of current pan space capacity.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "RAF Akrotiri: Military Aircraft", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877960", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877958, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110338", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the answer of 8 September 2025 to question 71975, whether he has made a recent assessment of the potential merits of expanding the available pan space.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "RAF Akrotiri: Military Aircraft", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877958", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877955, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110337", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many deportations took place from the SBAs in (a) 2026, (b) 2025, (c) 2024 and (d) 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cyprus: Military Bases", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877955", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877954, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110336", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the answer of 16 July 2025 to UIN 66298, what recent discussions he has had with the SBAs and the Republic of Cyprus on crime and immigration.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cyprus: Military Bases", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877954", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877951, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110335", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the implementation of the Immigration (Amendment) Ordinance 2025 on the SBAs of Akrotiri and Dhekelia.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cyprus: Military Bases", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877951", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877947, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110334", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress he has made on the Bilateral Defence Co-operation Programme between the SBAs and the Republic of Cyprus.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cyprus: Military Alliances", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877947", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877945, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110333", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the regional disaster response to the fires in the SBAs of Akrotiri and Dhekelia in July 2025; and whether he has implemented new regional disaster preparedness", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cyprus: Military Bases", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877945", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877942, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110332", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish a breakdown of funding provided to the Sovereign Base Areas of Akrotiri and Dhekelia from the APPOLLO programme; and if he will make an assessment of the effectiveness of this funding.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cyprus: Military Bases", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877942", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877941, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110331", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make an assessment of the effectiveness of the updated land-use framework adopted in the Sovereign Base Areas of Akrotiri and Dhekelia.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cyprus: Military Bases", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877941", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877940, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110330", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to section 5 of his Department's policy paper entitled The Strategic Defence Review 2025 - Making Britain Safer: secure at home, strong abroad, published on 8 July 2025, what assessment he has made", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Antarctic Treaty", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877940", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877938, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110329", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will publish a list of engagements for the UK-EU Withdrawal Agreement Protocol Specialised Committee in 2025 and 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Withdrawal Agreement Joint Committee", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877938", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877937, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110328", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the Standing Committee of the Chinese National People\u2019s Congress work on a draft bill on Antarctic Activities and Envi", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Antarctic: Sovereignty", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877937", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877936, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110327", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 17 October 2025 to Question 79283, if he will make an assessment of (a) the effectiveness of hydrographic surveys to improve the safety of navigation in Antarctic waters and (b) the pote", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Antarctic: Hydrography", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877936", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877935, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110326", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer on 8 December 2025  to Question 97994 on Artic: Shipping, what are the (a) command arrangements and (b) cost contributions for shared ice cutter capability in the British Antarctic Territor", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Arctic: Shipping", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877935", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877933, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110325", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the National Police Service's remit will include dealing with illegal tobacco and organized crime.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Police: Reorganisation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877933", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878122, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110324", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when she expects to receive the report by the FCA into hidden commission costs connected with car purchase loan schemes.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878122", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877869, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110323", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 27 November 2025 to WPQ 93664, whether any ongoing assessment is being made of the success of the take up campaign aimed at the 750,000 people who have not yet claimed their matured Child T", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877869", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877915, "askingMemberId": 1211, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110322", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to support young people to pursue careers in tech start ups in the Midlands.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "New Businesses: Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877915", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877914, "askingMemberId": 1211, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110321", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to work with NHS Birmingham and Solihull ICB to reduce the number of patients that are waiting an extended period for a wheelchair.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS Birmingham and Solihull: Wheelchairs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877914", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877987, "askingMemberId": 1171, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110320", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what estimate his Department has made of the level of the tarrifs avoided on an annual basis as a result of the US-UK Economic Prosperity Deal based on the following assumptions: (a) 100% tariffs remov", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Trade Agreements: USA", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877987", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877878, "askingMemberId": 410, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110319", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Palantir system for managing his Department's data could be unilaterally shut down by Palantir without the Government\u2019s consent.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Defence: Data Protection", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877878", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878152, "askingMemberId": 242, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110318", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, for what reason the new Places of Worship Renewal Fund is open to applications from places of worship which are not listed; and whether the new Places of Worship Renewal Fund is open to applicati", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878152", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878151, "askingMemberId": 242, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110317", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the annual cost to the Exchequer is of the exemption from VAT on repairs enjoyed by museums and galleries.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878151", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878021, "askingMemberId": 242, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110316", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the Minister plans to respond to the email from the hon. Member for Christchurch dated 26 November 2025 on the use of civil enforcement powers by local authorities.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878021", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878080, "askingMemberId": 185, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110315", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will list the properties in the UK owned by the US War Department.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878080", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1878057, "askingMemberId": 152, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110314", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of removing the wear and tear allowance for childminders under Making Tax Digital.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Childminding: Tax Allowances", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1878057", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877546, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110313", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with NHS England on ensuring escalation protocols for deteriorating patients are consistently applied across trusts.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877546", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877545, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110312", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will set out the guidance on the frequency of re-triage for patients whose condition may deteriorate while waiting for treatment.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Services: Waiting Lists", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877545", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877544, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110311", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to help reduce delays between triage and clinical assessment in Accident and Emergency departments.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Accident and Emergency Departments: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877544", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877543, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110310", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of NHS 111 calls resulted in an ambulance dispatch in the East of England in each of the past three years.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS 111: East of England", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877543", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877542, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110309", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of whether current levels of community-based urgent care services have capacity to offset ambulance demand in the East of England.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Community Care: East of England", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877542", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877541, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110308", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of ambulance call-outs were assessed as avoidable or suitable for alternative pathways in the East of England during the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ambulance Services: East of England", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877541", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877493, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110307", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to the British Embassy in Bangkok\u2019s press release entitled UK PACT and Bangkok advancing sustainable transport, published on 30 January 2026, what assessment s", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Thailand: Transport", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877493", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877492, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110306", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to the British Embassy in Bangkok\u2019s press release entitled UK PACT and Bangkok advancing sustainable transport, published on 30 January 2026, which Department'", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Thailand: Development Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877492", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877490, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110305", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to his Department\u2019s press release entitled Government action to avert summer prison disaster, published on 29 January 2026, what steps he has taken to help ensure that changes to sentencing do not ", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prison Sentences", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877490", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877489, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110304", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to his Department\u2019s press release entitled Government action to avert summer prison disaster, published on 29 January 2026, on what date the 2,900 prison spaces were approved for construction.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisons: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877489", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877488, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110303", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to his Department\u2019s press release entitled Government action to avert summer prison disaster, published on 29 January 2026, when the 2,900 prison spaces began construction.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisons: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877488", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877480, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110302", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to his press release entitled New fund to tackle cancer screening inequalities and save lives, published on 29 January 2026, what proportion of the funding will be allocated to cance", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cancer: Screening", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877480", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877479, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110301", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to her Department\u2019s World News Story entitled Cameroon: UK supports new generation of Central Africa researchers, published on 29 January 2026, what assessment", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Central Africa: Climate Change and Rainforests", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877479", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877478, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110300", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to her Department\u2019s World News Story entitled Cameroon: UK supports new generation of Central Africa researchers, published on 29 January 2026, what steps she ", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Central Africa: Rainforests", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877478", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877477, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110299", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to her Department's world news story entitled Cameroon: UK supports new generation of Central Africa researchers, published on 29 January 2026, what proportion", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Central Africa: Development Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877477", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877476, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110298", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to her Department\u2019s world news story entitled Cameroon: UK supports new generation of Central Africa researchers, published on 29 January 2026, what steps she ", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Central Africa: Development Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877476", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877475, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110297", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to her Department\u2019s world news story entitled Cameroon: UK supports new generation of Central Africa researchers, published on 29 January 2026, what measures a", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Central Africa: Rainforests", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877475", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877404, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110296", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Prime Minister\u2019s press release entitled Prime Minister unlocks new opportunities for British businesses in China, published on 29 January 2026, how she plans to monitor and evalu", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Organised Crime and Undocumented Migrants: China", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877404", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877403, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110295", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, with reference to the Prime Minister\u2019s press release entitled Prime Minister unlocks new opportunities for British businesses in China, published on 29 January 2026, what assessment he has made of the ", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Trade Agreements: China", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877403", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877380, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110294", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to her Department\u2019s press release entitled UK leads global efforts to help communities save the ocean and beat poverty, published on 26 January 2026, whether funding awa", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fisheries: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877380", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877641, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110293", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to ensure preserved Armed Forces Pension benefits are claimed.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Armed Forces: Workplace Pensions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877641", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877627, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110292", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the suitability of Ithaca Energy developing on Rosebank oil field.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ithaca Energy: North Sea Oil", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877627", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877498, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110290", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to provide music hubs with three year funding agreements.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Music: Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877498", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877497, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110289", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department plans to provide an uplift in funding to music hubs parallel to that for National Portfolio Organisations.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Music: Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877497", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877496, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110288", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether she is taking steps to ensure that water companies provide low income customers with cheaper social tariffs.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Water Charges: Social Tariffs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877496", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877495, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110287", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps he is taking to (a) promote and (b) enforce the new EN-1 and EN-3 requirements associated with incinerators.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Incinerators: Regulation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877495", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877494, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110286", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to publish a revised National Planning Policy for Waste before May 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Waste Management", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877494", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877411, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110284", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 18 December 2025 to Question 99038 on Armed Conflict: Civilians, to list what metrics were used during the external review to measure the effectiveness of the Ministry of Defence's appro", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Armed Conflict: Civilians", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877411", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877410, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110283", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 18 December 2025 to Question 99038 on Armed Conflict: Civilians, if he will publish the conclusions of the external review.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Armed Conflict: Civilians", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877410", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877517, "askingMemberId": 5335, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110282", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to reduce diagnostic waiting times for endometriosis in (a) England and (b) Chichester constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Endometriosis: Diagnosis", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877517", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877500, "askingMemberId": 5329, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110281", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the answer of 20 January 2026 to UIN 105608, if he will publish the evidence on the application of the Remoteness Adjustment in the Fair Funding Review.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877500", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877651, "askingMemberId": 5327, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110280", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Armed Forces Bill 2026 which, what assessment he has made if the (a) proportion of the cohort aged between 55 and 65 that would meet the physical requirements of service and (b) other forms ", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877651", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877647, "askingMemberId": 5327, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110279", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made with Cabinet colleagues of the potential merits of amending NHS dental contracts so that they apply to armed forces personnel and their families.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877647", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877646, "askingMemberId": 5327, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110278", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made with Cabinet colleagues of the adequacy of armed forces personnel and their families' access to dental services.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877646", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877566, "askingMemberId": 5323, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110277", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what action is being taken to address ongoing illegal tipping a) across the country, and b) in the Forest of Dean constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fly-tipping", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877566", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877516, "askingMemberId": 5322, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110276", "questionText": "To ask the Leader of the House, if he will take steps to review the membership of the Privy Council.", "answeringBodyId": 34, "answeringBodyName": "Leader of the House", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Privy Council: Membership", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877516", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877405, "askingMemberId": 5320, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110275", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make an estimate of the amount of capital funding needed to ensure the provision of effective water services in each area of England in each year until 2030.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Water Supply: Capital Investment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877405", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877667, "askingMemberId": 5319, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "110274", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of amending the closed season for periwinkle gathering in inter-tidal areas in England.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877667", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877499, "askingMemberId": 5316, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110273", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what his planned timeframe is for consulting on national planning policy related to decision-making, including policies on flood risk and sustainable drainage systems.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Planning: Flood Control and Sewers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877499", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877705, "askingMemberId": 5313, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110272", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an assessment of the adequacy of care provided by care agencies to vulnerable people.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Care Workers: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877705", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877704, "askingMemberId": 5313, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110271", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to improve oversight of care agencies and to enhance enforcement powers against providers who fail to meet required care standards.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Care Workers: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877704", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877703, "askingMemberId": 5313, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110270", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will take steps to ensure that agency care workers receive appropriate and accredited training to meet the needs of vulnerable service users.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Care Workers: Training", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877703", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877702, "askingMemberId": 5313, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110269", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to prevent care agencies from supplying staff who deliver unsupervised personal care without the required registration with the Care Quality Commission.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Care Workers: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877702", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877512, "askingMemberId": 5303, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110268", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the impact of housing (a) refugees and (b) asylum seekers in Ipswich on social cohesion.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Ipswich", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877512", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877510, "askingMemberId": 5303, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110267", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of funding the construction of a Northern Bypass around Ipswich.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Bypasses: Ipswich", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877510", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877509, "askingMemberId": 5303, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110266", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to ensure the long-term financial viability of farming.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Profitability", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877509", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877508, "askingMemberId": 5303, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110265", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has had discussions with the (a) farming, (b) rural and (c) game sports industries on changes to shotgun licensing.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Firearms: Licensing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877508", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877455, "askingMemberId": 5303, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110264", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate has been made of the economic impact of housing (a) refugees and (b) asylum seekers in Ipswich.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Ipswich", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877455", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877454, "askingMemberId": 5303, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110263", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions she has had with Suffolk County Council regarding the construction of a Northern Bypass around Ipswich.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Bypasses: Ipswich", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877454", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877449, "askingMemberId": 5303, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110262", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to help improve the profitability of farming in England.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Profitability", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877449", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877448, "askingMemberId": 5303, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110261", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to publish the consultation into licensing controls for shotguns.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Firearms: Licensing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877448", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877599, "askingMemberId": 5301, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110259", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of the regionalisation of foster care commissioning on the role of independent fostering agencies, including on (a) placement availability, (b) co", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Foster Care", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877599", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877598, "askingMemberId": 5301, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110258", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of independent fostering agencies on a) costs to local authorities and b) outcomes for children in care; and whether plans to regionalise the comm", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Foster Care", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877598", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877701, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110257", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how much she has spent on legal advice pertaining to the revised Code of practice for services, public functions and associations.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Equality: Codes of Practice", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877701", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877399, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110256", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, which external organisations or groups her Department has engaged or consulted with on the draft Code of Practice for services, public functions, and associations.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Equality: Codes of Practice", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877399", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877398, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110255", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, whether her Department has submitted any proposed amendments to the revised Code of practice for services, public functions and associations to the Equality and Human Rights Commission.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Equality: Codes of Practice", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877398", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877397, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110254", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what external legal advice has she sought on the revised Code of practice for services, public functions and associations, submitted to her for approval on 5 September 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Equality: Codes of Practice", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877397", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877396, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110253", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what discussions her Department has had with the Equality and Human Rights Commission on the revised Code of practice for services, public functions and associations, submitted to the Minister for Women and Eq", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Equality: Codes of Practice", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877396", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877382, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110252", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what consideration his Department has given to the potential merits of allowing inquests into the death of a child by suicide to be conducted in private.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Suicide: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877382", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877379, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110251", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many biologically male prisoners were held in E Wing of HMP Downview as at 1st February 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "HMP/YOI Downview: Transgender People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877379", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877378, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110250", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that Civil Service workplace policies fully comply with the Equality Act 2010 as interpreted in the ruling of the Supreme Court in For Women Scotland Ltd v The Scott", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Women: Equality", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877378", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877377, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110249", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will list the meetings between his Department, including the Office for Equality and Opportunity, and the Equality and Human Rights Commission on the implications of the For Women Scotland Ltd v The Scotti", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Women: Equality", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877377", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877376, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110248", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how much how her Department spent on external legal advice primarily relating to transgender equality policy since 16 April 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Transgender People: Equality", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877376", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877375, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110247", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how many full-time equivalent staff are currently assigned primarily to policy work relating to transgender matters within the Office for Equality and Opportunity.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Transgender People: Equality", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877375", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877374, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110246", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what has been the cost to the public purse of staff working in his Department on trans equality and related policy matters since 16 April 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Transgender People: Equality", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877374", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877373, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110245", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many staff members are currently working on policy connected to trans equality and related matters.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Transgender People: Equality", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877373", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877372, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110244", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department has sought to recruit a senior official to lead on trans equality since January 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Transgender People: Equality", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877372", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877361, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110243", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 15.27 of the Valuation Office Agency's technical manual, what recent assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of widening the provision to allow landlords to serve bligh", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Planning Blight", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877361", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877533, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110235", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of allowing HGV drivers with controlled Type 1 diabetes to renew their Class 1 licence every three years.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Large Goods Vehicle Drivers: Diabetes", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877533", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877532, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110234", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of reducing public funding for Level 7 apprenticeships for learners over the age of 21 on access to advanced training in marine engineering, naval arc", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Apprentices: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877532", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877531, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110233", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that contracts for Trinity House multi-function vessels are awarded to UK shipyards.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Shipping: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877531", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877530, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110232", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when she plans to announce details of the next steps of the Maritime Decarbonisation Plan, including responses to calls for evidence on net zero ports and decarbonising small vessels.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Shipping: Carbon Emissions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877530", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877529, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110231", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that contracts for Border Force patrol vessels are awarded to UK shipyards.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "UK Border Force: Patrol Craft", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877529", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877527, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110230", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she plans to publish the response to the Stage 3 consultation on managing bottom trawl fishing in 41 English marine protected areas.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Marine Protected Areas: Bottom Trawling", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877527", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877526, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110229", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of using empty school classrooms for health services.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877526", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877525, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110228", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department considers clinical nursing care delivered in education settings to constitute NHS healthcare for which Integrated Care Boards hold commissioning responsibility under existing", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Nurses: Educational Institutions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877525", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877524, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110227", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure a nationally consistent delivery model for NHS-commissioned clinical\u00a0nursing services for children and young people in education settings.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Nurses: Educational Institutions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877524", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877664, "askingMemberId": 5277, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110226", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many times has the Government rejected recommendations for compensation made by the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman following a finding of maladministration since 2010.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877664", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877414, "askingMemberId": 5250, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110223", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of aligning Section 2 shotgun licensing with Section 1 firearms licensing on (a) participation in shooting sports and (b) rural businesses; whether", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Firearms: Licensing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877414", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877622, "askingMemberId": 5247, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110222", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if her Department has made an assessment of the effectiveness of road signs used by local authorities to help prevent road causalities among (a) hedgehogs and (b) other small mammals.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Road Signs and Markings", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877622", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877561, "askingMemberId": 5228, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110221", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what powers other than additional funding she has to ensure Lancashire County Council fills potholes in Ribble Valley in a timely and thorough way.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Roads: Ribble Valley", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877561", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877559, "askingMemberId": 5228, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110219", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department has plans to implement mandatory trauma-informed training and accreditation for all professionals working with adopted children.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Adoption: Health Professions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877559", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877558, "askingMemberId": 5228, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110218", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, (i) whether Vaccine Damage Payment Scheme (VDPS) claims are matched to assessors with condition-specific expertise, (ii) whether the Department for Health and Social Care holds audits or quality as", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Vaccine Damage Payment Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877558", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877575, "askingMemberId": 5227, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110217", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to help protect Jewish people in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Antisemitism", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877575", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877574, "askingMemberId": 5227, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110216", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to help tackle antisemitism.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Antisemitism", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877574", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877412, "askingMemberId": 5226, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110215", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department is taking to help reduce the time taken for quotes to be issued to people who are members of the Civil Service pension scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Civil Servants: Workplace Pensions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877412", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877413, "askingMemberId": 5221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110214", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to help ensure adequate security provision for the Palestinian Embassy in London.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Palestine Embassy: Security", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877413", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877584, "askingMemberId": 5216, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110213", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps her Department is taking to improve communication with rural communities about Project Gigabit rollout timelines.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877584", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877582, "askingMemberId": 5216, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110212", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, when the Project Gigabit voucher scheme will reopen to communities in South Devon constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877582", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877581, "askingMemberId": 5216, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110211", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that households in areas with poor mobile signal are not excluded from smart meters.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877581", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877578, "askingMemberId": 5212, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110210", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether funding from expansion of the UK Emissions Trading Scheme to maritime will be used to support maritime decarbonisation.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Shipping: UK Emissions Trading Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877578", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877577, "askingMemberId": 5212, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110209", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on using funds raised by the expansion of the UK Emissions Trading Scheme to support maritime decarbonisation projects in Scotland.", "answeringBodyId": 2, "answeringBodyName": "Scotland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "UK Emissions Trading Scheme: Shipping", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877577", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877437, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110208", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to help tackle the decline of British birds.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Birds: Conservation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877437", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877436, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110207", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of climate change on UK wildlife.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Climate Change: Wildlife", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877436", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877434, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110206", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies of the EU\u2019s proposed restrictions of PFAS.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Per- and Polyfluorinated Alkyl Substances", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877434", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877432, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110205", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to help tackle barriers to work for disabled people in Harpenden and Berkhamsted constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employment: Disability", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877432", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877429, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110202", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the amount of technology required by state schools in England.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: ICT", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877429", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877425, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110199", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to help tackle the decline in the numbers of British birds.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Birds: Conservation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877425", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877630, "askingMemberId": 5196, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110197", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the seizure of the Russian-flagged oil tanker Marinera and the removal of its captain and first officer from UK jurisdiction by United States Coast Guards, what engagement the Government receive", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Russia: Tankers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877630", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877474, "askingMemberId": 5195, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110196", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of converting short-term tenancies into periodic tenancies on the number of tenancies required to make anniversary calculations for Stamp Duty Land Tax.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Shorthold Tenancies: Stamp Duty Land Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877474", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877518, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110193", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps she is taking to help reduce the number of non-essential scientific experimentations on live animals.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877518", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877442, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110192", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking with Cabinet colleagues to help reduce the number of drink driving incidents in Yeovil constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Driving under Influence: Yeovil", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877442", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877440, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110191", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to help tackle the decline in native wild birds in (a) Yeovil constituency (b) Somerset and (c) the British Isles.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Birds: Conservation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877440", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877595, "askingMemberId": 5186, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110189", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of trends in national illiteracy levels; and what steps her Department is taking to ensure that groups at high risk of illiteracy receive adequate education.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Literacy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877595", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877591, "askingMemberId": 5186, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110188", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that societal groups, such as young women and girls, who present a-typical symptoms do not receive delayed diagnosis because standard symptoms are based on other s", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Diagnosis: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877591", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877409, "askingMemberId": 5177, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110187", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she has made an estimate of how average journey times on railways in Wales compare to equivalent distances on the railways in (a) London and (b) the southeast of England.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Wales", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877409", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877487, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110186", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she has taken with Cabinet colleagues to help increase workforce numbers in the farming and agriculture sectors in (a) Newcastle-under-Lyme, (b) Staffordshire and (c) Englan", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Employment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877487", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877486, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110185", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with Cabinet colleagues on helping to provide young people with the skills and knowledge to undertake jobs in the farming and agriculture sector.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Training", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877486", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877485, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110184", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of a national campaign showcasing the diversity and rewards of young people with careers in the agriculture industry.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877485", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877625, "askingMemberId": 5157, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110183", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has commissioned the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence to produce clinical guidance on pica.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Eating Disorders", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877625", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877708, "askingMemberId": 5140, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110181", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of retired civil servants experiencing financial hardship due to them not receiving their Civil Service Pension payments on time; and what funding has been allocated for i", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Civil Servants: Workplace Pensions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877708", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877528, "askingMemberId": 5138, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110179", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to (a) reduce losses of public funding to fraud during defence procurement and (b) increase the amount of funding recovered from those losses.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Defence: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877528", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877611, "askingMemberId": 5137, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110176", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, how many workers in Glasgow are estimated to benefit from day-one rights when the Employment Rights Act comes into force on 1 April 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Conditions of Employment: Glasgow", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877611", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877607, "askingMemberId": 5137, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110175", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has been made of how the Employment Rights Act will help reduce economic inactivity.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employment Rights Act 2025", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877607", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877605, "askingMemberId": 5137, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110174", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what guidance and support is available to businesses in Scotland to help ensure compliance with the Employment Rights Act.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Conditions of Employment: Scotland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877605", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877604, "askingMemberId": 5137, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110173", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how the grassroots sports facilities fund will be used to promote women's football in Scotland.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Football: Scotland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877604", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877603, "askingMemberId": 5137, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110172", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the \u00a38.14 million grassroots sports facilities fund on access to sport in deprived communities.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sports: Disadvantaged", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877603", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877600, "askingMemberId": 5137, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110171", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of further education colleges in Scotland on the skills requirement for the defence industrial strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Defence: Training", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877600", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877693, "askingMemberId": 5132, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110170", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average national unit cost to the NHS is for an MRI scan used in prostate cancer detection using (a) multiparametric and (b) biparametric MRI.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prosate Cancer: Screening", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877693", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877470, "askingMemberId": 5122, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110166", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will formally re-establish the Advisory Committee on Packaging as a forum for (a) industry, (b) government and (c) regulators to oversee the operation of the Packaging Recovery ", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877470", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877513, "askingMemberId": 5103, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110163", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of bereavement payments not being payable to cohabiting partners.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Bereavement Benefits: Cohabitation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877513", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877624, "askingMemberId": 5093, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110162", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she has taken to help ensure airports have the capital investment to transition to net zero carbon emissions (a) on their estate and (b) in airport operations.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Airports: Carbon Emissions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877624", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877679, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110161", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what requirements changes have the Army made to the Early Capability Demonstrator platform as part of the Mobile Fires Platform programme.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Artillery: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877679", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877678, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110160", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to page 10 of the Police reform white paper From Local to National: A New Model for Policing (CP1489), by what date will the independent review of police force structures report its fin", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Police: Reorganisation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877678", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877677, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110159", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment has she made of the potential benefit of establishing a joint Public order, firearms and tactics training centre in Cambridgeshire.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Police: Training", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877677", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877675, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110158", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress has she made in procuring a new firearm to replace the Heckler and Koch G36 for Cambridgeshire Constabulary.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cambridgeshire Constabulary: Firearms", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877675", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877674, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110157", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what progress has she made in building the new British Embassy in Beijing.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "British Embassy Beijing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877674", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877673, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110156", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to page 9 of the Police reform white paper From Local to National: A New Model for Policing (CP1489), what Artificial Intelligence powered a) tools and b) software to automate manual pr", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Police: Artificial Intelligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877673", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877671, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110155", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to page 9 of her Department's White Paper entitled From Local to National: A New Model for Policing, published on 26 January 2026, CP1489, if she will publish a list of the legislation ", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Police: Reorganisation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877671", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877670, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110154", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to page 9 of her Department's White Paper, entitled From Local to National: A New Model for Policing, published on 26 January 2026, CP1489, what is her planned timetable to take legisla", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Order Act 1986", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877670", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877668, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110153", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to page 9 of her Department's White Paper, entitled From Local to National: A New Model for Policing, published on 26 January 2026, CP1489, what steps she is planning to take to remove ", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Police: Reorganisation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877668", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877666, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110152", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which occupations have been (a) added and (b) removed from the shortage occupation list since 5 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Migrant Workers: Skilled Workers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877666", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877663, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110150", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 30 January 2026 to Question 107813 on Army, what new capabilities )a) have and (b) are in the process of being fielded to the Army via Task Force Rapstone.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Army", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877663", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877662, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110149", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Atlantic series deployments on deterring Russia\u2019s Northern Fleet from deploying.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Russia: Navy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877662", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877683, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110145", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking with Cabinet colleagues to help health authorities deliver endometriosis services in (a) East Sussex and (b) areas where the prevalence endometriosis is higher than the nati", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Endometriosis: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877683", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877682, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110144", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department has taken to help ensure the guidance on endometriosis published by National Institute for Health and Care Excellence is effectively implemented.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Endometriosis: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877682", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877681, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110143", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department has taken to help ensure that people from (a) ethnic minority and (b) low socio-economic backgrounds have adequate access to endometriosis diagnosis services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Endometriosis: Diagnosis", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877681", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877680, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110142", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will publish national data on endometriosis diagnostic waiting times.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Endometriosis: Diagnosis", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877680", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877650, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110141", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has made an estimate of the number of people facing financial difficulties due to the time taken to issue Teachers' Superannuation Scheme statements for teachers pensions.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Teachers: Workplace Pensions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877650", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877649, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110140", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of people in receipt of a teachers pension impacted by the length of time taken to issue Teachers' Superannuation Scheme statements.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Teachers: Workplace Pensions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877649", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877648, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110139", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to help reduce the time taken for issuing Teachers' Superannuation Scheme statements affecting teachers pensions.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Teachers: Workplace Pensions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877648", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877573, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110138", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, pursuant to the Answer of 12 December 2025 to Question 96957, when his Department plans to roll out the Connections Accelerator Service.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Clean Energy: National Grid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877573", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877565, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110137", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of setting minimum gigawatt targets for (i) local energy and (ii) community energy projects.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Renewable Energy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877565", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877465, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110129", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on what grounds Border Force might allow (a) sodium nitrate and (b) other toxic materials onward passage to a postal address.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chemicals: Import Controls", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877465", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877464, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110128", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what Border Force's policy is on the interception of (a) sodium nitrate and (b) other toxic materials at the border.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chemicals: Import Controls", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877464", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877463, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110127", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps Ofcom is taking to help tackle websites that provide instructions on committing suicide.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Internet: Suicide", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877463", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877453, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110125", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what data her Department holds on outcomes of asylum appeals since March 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Appeals", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877453", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877452, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110124", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what quality assurance data her Department holds on the outcomes of initial asylum decisions since 2023-24.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877452", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877451, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110123", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what impact assessments, internal modelling or economic analyses were produced to inform the policies set out in the White Paper \u201cRestoring Control over the Immigration System\u201d.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Immigration", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877451", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877450, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110122", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to publish an impact assessment of the policies contained in the White Paper, Restoring Control over the Immigration System; and if she will set out a timetable for publication.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Immigration", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877450", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877458, "askingMemberId": 5052, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110121", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of excluding the state pension as a form of taxable income.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "State Retirement Pensions: Taxation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877458", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877676, "askingMemberId": 5040, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110120", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department is taking to work with the travel industry to help ensure that package holidays sold to UK consumers meet appropriate health and safety standards, and what action is being con", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Package Holidays", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877676", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877462, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110116", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to support British food producers facing competition from increased imports following the UK-US Economic Prosperity Deal.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Imports", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877462", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877461, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110115", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of changing US to UK import levels of (a) wheat, (b) maize and (c) ethanol on (i) food security and (b) agricultural businesses.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Imports", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877461", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877552, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110110", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many members of the civil service pension scheme had not received quotes as to their expected pension income a) 12 months before retirement, b) six months before retirement, c) 3 months before retirement , d", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Civil Servants: Workplace Pensions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877552", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877551, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110109", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many newly retired members of the civil service pension scheme did not receive payments a) one week, b) two weeks, 3) one month, 4) two months, 5) three months and 6) six months after their first payment was", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Civil Servants: Workplace Pensions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877551", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877550, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110108", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many newly retired members of the civil service pension scheme did not receive payments on their due dates in each of the last 3 years.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Civil Servants: Workplace Pensions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877550", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877613, "askingMemberId": 4828, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110107", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what work his Department is doing to help improve data collection on the number of women rough sleeping and to adopt a gender-informed methodology for measuring rough sleeping.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877613", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877609, "askingMemberId": 4828, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-09T00:00:00", "uin": "110106", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if his Department will take steps to review the national definition of rough sleeping to help ensure it reflects the different ways women experience homelessness.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877609", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877606, "askingMemberId": 4828, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110105", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he has had discussions with local authorities on levels of female homelessness.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Homelessness: Women", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877606", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877473, "askingMemberId": 4824, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110104", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of expanding the UK Emissions Trading Scheme to maritime on (a) the international competitiveness of the UK\u2019s cruise sector, (b) Liverpool Cruise ", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Shipping: UK Emissions Trading Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877473", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877472, "askingMemberId": 4824, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110103", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of using funds raised by the expansion of the UK Emissions Trading Scheme to include maritime to support maritime decarbonisati", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "UK Emissions Trading Scheme: Shipping", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877472", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877471, "askingMemberId": 4824, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110102", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps her Department is taking to engage with Crown Dependencies and Overseas Territories on the impact of proposals to expand the UK Emissions Trading Scheme to international maritime voyages.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Shipping: UK Emissions Trading Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877471", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877408, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110101", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 20 Janaury 2026 to Question 104987, what forms of legislative modification a Harbour Revision Order is capable of making.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ports", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877408", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877402, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110098", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, with reference to page 19 of the Final stage impact assessment entitled UK Emissions Trading Scheme (ETS) Scope Expansion - Domestic maritime, published on 25 November 2025, for what reason n", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "UK Emissions Trading Scheme: Shipping", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877402", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877395, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110097", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many new buses were registered in the UK broken down by country of manufacture in each of the last 10 years.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Buses", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877395", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877394, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110096", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether her Department has included the foregone Dartford Crossing toll revenues in the Lower Thames Crossing project\u2019s cost\u2013benefit analysis.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Lower Thames Crossing: Cost Benefit Analysis", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877394", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877392, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110094", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which driving test centres the DVSA have proposed for closure.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Driving Tests: Facilities", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877392", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877391, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110093", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what schemes and programmes her Department has in place to help support zero-emission in (a) shipping and (b) aviation.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Aviation and Shipping: Carbon Emissions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877391", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877381, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110092", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 20 January 2026 to Question 104866, what is the expected month and year of publication of the new Plan for Freight.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Freight", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877381", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877371, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110091", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Royal Train will be treated as a Great British Railways service for the purposes of network access, charging and operational control once Great British Railways is established.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Royal Family", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877371", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877370, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110090", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to rail fares in England, what the average percentage change was between July 2024 and the current fares period for a) Advance fares b) First Class fares c) Super Off-Peak fares, and what methodo", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Fares", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877370", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877369, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110089", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the Rail Delivery Groups' updated fare search limits on (a) passenger choice, (b) the cost of rail fares and (c) levels of passenger demand.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Fares", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877369", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877368, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110088", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, since 1 January 2024, how many additional civil servants have been recruited into DfTO on a headcount basis; and for each quarter in the period January 2024 to the most recent quarter for which figures are avai", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Transport: Civil Servants", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877368", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877367, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110087", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate she has made of the costs to port developers of the requirement in paragraph 4.7.23 of the draft National Policy Statement for Ports to provide infrastructure to support alternative fuels and zero", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ports: Costs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877367", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877366, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110086", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the potential costs to port developers of setting target modal shares for rail or coastal shipping, as referenced in the draft National Policy Statement for Ports; and what furth", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ports: Costs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877366", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877365, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110085", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment the Department has made of the potential impact of higher electric vehicle repair costs on insurance premiums, and by when it expects its proposed battery health measures to reduce those costs f", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electric Vehicles: Repairs and Maintenance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877365", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877364, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110084", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many practical car driving tests were conducted in (a) July 2024 and (b) each subsequent month up to the most recent month for which data is available.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Driving Tests", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877364", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877363, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110083", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 6 January 2026 to Question 101488, what information her Department holds on revenue lost due to fare evasion by individual train operating companies.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Fares", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877363", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877362, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110082", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 9 January 2026 to Question 100958, whether her Department (a) receives or (b) reviews data on the proportion of rail journeys using fully digital tickets for each train operating compa", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Tickets", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877362", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877571, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110081", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people she expects to settle their disguised remuneration liabilities as a result of the McCann Review into Loan Charge settlement terms.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tax Avoidance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877571", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877570, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110080", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government plans to extend the improved settlement terms announced following the McCann Review to individuals who have already settled their Loan Charge liabilities with HMRC.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tax Avoidance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877570", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877567, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110078", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether her Department holds data on the proportion of roles employed offshore by UK-headquartered companies, broken down by sector and salary band.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offshore Industry: Staff", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877567", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877420, "askingMemberId": 4787, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110073", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact on the Police Funding Settlement (England and Wales) 2026-27 on the provisions for tackling fly tipping in rural areas.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fly-tipping: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877420", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877419, "askingMemberId": 4787, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110072", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made on the potential impact of the Police Funding Settlement (England and Wales) 2026-27 on the response times to rural crime incidents in North West Norfolk consti", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Crime: North West Norfolk", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877419", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877418, "askingMemberId": 4787, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110071", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many full time equivalent police officers there were in Norfolk Constabulary on (a) 1 September 2024 and (b) 1 September 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Norfolk Constabulary", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877418", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877417, "askingMemberId": 4787, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110070", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made on the potential impact of the Police Funding Settlement (England and Wales) 2026-27 on the number of police officers in North West Norfolk constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Police: North West Norfolk", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877417", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877583, "askingMemberId": 4785, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110069", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress her Department has made on the River Thames Scheme; what her planned timetable is for that scheme; and what the (a) current and (b) projected expenditure is for that sche", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "River Thames: Flood Control", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877583", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877502, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110065", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 28 December 2025 to Question 100476 on Brain: Tumours, what plans the National Institute for Health and Care Research has to undertake horizon scanning of the pharmaceutic", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Brain: Tumours", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877502", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877445, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110064", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of staffing levels in cancer care on waiting times for patients to receive treatment.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cancer: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877445", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877444, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110063", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to help reduce waiting times for cancer treatment in the East Midlands.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cancer: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877444", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877443, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110062", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase the number of clinical (a) radiologists and (b) oncologists in the East Midlands.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cancer and Radiology: Doctors", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877443", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877672, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110059", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, with reference to (a) SOPS 1.1. in the Department's 2024/5 Annual Report, a breakdown of the \u00a3209,590,000 spent in gross administration costs on capability and (b) Table 1, Annex A: Com", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology: Public Expenditure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877672", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877645, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110058", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to SOPS 1.1 in the Department's 2024-25 Annual Report, if she will publish a breakdown of the \u00a31,030,869,000 in gross spend on Programme Resource Outturn in H: Other Benefits in 2024-25; ", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Work and Pensions: Public Expenditure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877645", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877644, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110057", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to SOPS 1.1. in the Department's 2020-21 Annual Report, if she will publish a breakdown of the \u00a32,402,602 in gross spend on Programme Resource Outturn in A: Operational Delivery in 2020-2", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Work and Pensions: Public Expenditure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877644", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877643, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110056", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to SOPS 1.1. in the Department's 2024-25 Annual Report, if she will publish a breakdown of the \u00a36,156,284,000 spent on Programme Resource Outturn in A: Core Department in 2024-25.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Work and Pensions: Public Expenditure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877643", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877523, "askingMemberId": 4658, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110055", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps Student Loans Company is taking to ensure that borrowers repaying through PAYE are not issued incorrect repayment demands.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Students: Loans", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877523", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877484, "askingMemberId": 4647, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110052", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what progress his Department has made on achieving the Government\u2019s objectives for supporting Small and Medium-sized Enterprises participation in public procurement.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Government Departments: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877484", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877483, "askingMemberId": 4647, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110051", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of procurement contracts awarded by each Government Department were to Small and Medium-sized Enterprises in each of the last five financial years.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Government Departments: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877483", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877482, "askingMemberId": 4647, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110050", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government Commercial Agency is taking to help improve access to Government procurement processes for (a) Small and Medium-sized Enterprises and (b) other suppliers with expertise in artificial in", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Government Departments: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877482", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877481, "askingMemberId": 4647, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110049", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps her Department is taking to facilitate public sector access to Artificial Intelligence expertise through procurement; and how the Government Commercial Agency will (a) identify, (b) accredit and (c) e", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Sector: Artificial Intelligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877481", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877422, "askingMemberId": 4647, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110048", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information her Department holds on the extent to which enforcement authorities, when rejecting challenges to parking contravention notices during the discount period, re-offer the discount for a further 1", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Parking Offences: Fines", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877422", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877711, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110046", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment has she made of the adequacy of penalties for those who have committed crimes related to wildlife.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Nature Conservation: Crime", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877711", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877710, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110045", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent steps she has taken to prevent crime relating to wildlife.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Nature Conservation: Crime", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877710", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877695, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110042", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, in what month the first relocations to the UK took place (a) among the 217 principal applicants found newly eligible as a result of the data incident under Category 1 of the Afghan Relocations and Assistance Poli", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Afghanistan: Resettlement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877695", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877690, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110040", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she has held discussions with Transport for London on the potential impact of delays in issuing private hire licences on private hire drivers.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Taxis: Licensing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877690", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877706, "askingMemberId": 4613, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110037", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the answer of 8 January 2026 to Question 101383 on Government Actuary's Department: Freedom of Information, what is the evidential basis for the Minister for Defence Readiness and Industry's statement", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Government Actuary's Department: Freedom of Information", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877706", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877564, "askingMemberId": 4591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110035", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 30 January 2026 to Question 107739, if he will clarify what productivity and effectiveness service improvements are used with the assistance of AI.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Immigration: Artificial Intelligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877564", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877580, "askingMemberId": 4523, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110034", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how the National Cancer Plan will support people with secondary breast cancer.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Breast Cancer: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877580", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877592, "askingMemberId": 4464, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110029", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether HMRC plans to publish draft guidance for industry on the operation of the UK carbon border adjustment mechanism after spring 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Industry: Carbon Emissions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877592", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877714, "askingMemberId": 4434, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110028", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether she has had discussions with European counterparts on the potential merits of introducing sanctions against refineries that are buying Russian crude oil.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Russia: Oil", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877714", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877713, "askingMemberId": 4434, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110027", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether she will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing sanctions against refineries that are buying Russian crude oil.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Russia: Oil", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877713", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877669, "askingMemberId": 4434, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110026", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what criteria his Department uses in uprating retired Civil Servants Contracted Out Deduction with annual pension increases to their pre and post - 88 GMP; and what other methodologies his Departments uses for t", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Civil Servants: Workplace Pensions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877669", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877549, "askingMemberId": 4394, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110025", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, of the UC WCA decisions that resulted in an LCWRA outcome for 16\u201321 year-olds where at least one mental and behavioural disorder (F00\u2013F99) was recorded, how many also had at least one condition recorded", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Universal Credit: Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877549", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877548, "askingMemberId": 4394, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110024", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the estimated total Universal Credit expenditure is for 16 to 21 year olds who are receiving the UC health element, including the standard allowance and other elements, and for all ages receiving t", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Universal Credit: Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877548", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877547, "askingMemberId": 4394, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110023", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the estimated expenditure on the health element of Universal Credit is for 16 to 21 year olds, not including the standard allowance and other elements, and for all ages receiving the health element", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Universal Credit: Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877547", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877642, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110022", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department has assessed the salary outcomes, promotion rates and role progression of participants in the Beyond Boundaries programme compared to a control group of comparable civil servants who did n", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Civil Servants: Career Development", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877642", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877640, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110021", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what role the Crown Commercial Service (CCS) has in monitoring Bloom Procurement Services Ltd\u2019s compliance with the NEPRO3 framework; and whether CCS is required to audit the fees and margins applied by Procurem", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cabinet Office: Bloom Procurement Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877640", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877639, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110020", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the corrected Answer of 7 January 2026 to Question 98100 on Cabinet Office: Public Appointments and with reference to his Department's document entitled Guidance on Making Direct Ministerial Appointm", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cabinet Office: Public Appointments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877639", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877638, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110019", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Government's correspondence entitled Letter from the Prime Minister on government transparency and open data, published on 14 December 2017, whether the approach set out in the letter is Go", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Government Departments: Disclosure of Information", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877638", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877637, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110018", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish Department\u2019s fixed asset register.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cabinet Office: Assets", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877637", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877636, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110017", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the answer of 20 November 2025 to Question 90241 on 10 Downing Street: Official Hospitality, how much has been spent on hospitality by No10 since 4 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "10 Downing Street: Official Hospitality", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877636", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877634, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110016", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 5 January 2025 to Question 100331 on Ministers: Official Cars, how many civil servants have access to an official car from the Government Car Service.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Civil Servants: Official Cars", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877634", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877632, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110015", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, further to the Cabinet Office press release entitled Young people from all backgrounds to get opportunity to study abroad as UK-EU deal unlocks Erasmus+, published on 17 December 2025, on what basis was the \u00a357", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Erasmus+ Programme: Costs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877632", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877631, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110014", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 26 November 2025 to Question 92286 on Government Departments: Official Cars, which Government Departments have access to a official car that can be used by civil servants.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Government Departments: Official Cars", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877631", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877629, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110013", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 26 November 2025 to Question 92012 on Cabinet Office: training, if he will publish a breakdown of costs for the \u00a35,288.40 spent on the away days.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cabinet Office: Training", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877629", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877628, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110012", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will publish a list of programmes and schemes that require the UK to provide payments to the EU and are not included in the EU\u2013UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement of 2020.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "UK-EU Trade and Cooperation Agreement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877628", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877562, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110011", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if she will make it his policy to disclose forthwith whether an exit payment was made to Lord Mandelson by HM Government following Lord Mandelson's departure from the Civil S", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Lord Mandelson", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877562", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877557, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110010", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the answer of 13 November 2025, to Question 87332, on Lord Mandelson, whether Lord Mandelson during his (a) due diligence and (b) developed vetting processes, was asked about (i) payments made by Jef", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Lord Mandelson", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877557", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877555, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110009", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the answer of 13 November 2025, to Question 87332, on Lord Mandelson, on what specific date did the Cabinet Office complete its due diligence into Lord Mandelson in relation to his proposed appointme", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Lord Mandelson", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877555", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877554, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "110008", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether life peers who are on a Leave of Absence may be removed from the Roll of the Peerage.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Peers: Leave of Absence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877554", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877617, "askingMemberId": 4357, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110007", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment her Department has made of trends in the length of delays in the DVLA medical licensing process, particularly the time taken for applications to be reviewed by medical caseworkers after receipt;", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Driving Licences: Health", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877617", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877416, "askingMemberId": 4212, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "110006", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will publish (a) the the consultation timetable on the Eton Star Oldham free school and (b) the expected date for the publication of its findings.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877416", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877415, "askingMemberId": 4212, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-12T00:00:00", "uin": "110005", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will publish (a) the analysis identifying the need for additional 16 to 19 places in the Metropolitan Borough of Oldham and (b) the impact assessment on existing providers that was used to support the ap", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877415", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877400, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110003", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent steps she has taken to improve food supply security across the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food Supply", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877400", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877390, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110002", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people in England and Wales are on remand awaiting trial.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Remand in Custody", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877390", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877389, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110001", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of people who are victims of human trafficking.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Human Trafficking", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877389", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877388, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "110000", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people in the prison population are deemed to have a learning difficulty.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisoners: Learning Disability", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877388", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877387, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "109999", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to maximise the amount of time surgeons spend in theatre.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Surgery: Working Hours", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877387", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877386, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "109998", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to ensure that people with cystic fibrosis have access to Orkambi, Symkevi and Kaftrio on the NHS.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cystic Fibrosis: Drugs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877386", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877385, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "109997", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to help reduce regional inequalities in health outcomes.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health: Disadvantaged", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877385", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877383, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "109995", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking help improve addiction and mental health treatment.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Addictions and Mental Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877383", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877699, "askingMemberId": 4074, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "109994", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to extend the permitted development right for floating solar installations to disused quarries and docks in England and Wales.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Solar Power: Ports and Quarrying", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877699", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877698, "askingMemberId": 4074, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "109993", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to extend permitted development rights for floating solar installations to on-farm reservoirs in England and Wales.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Solar Power: Reservoirs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877698", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877696, "askingMemberId": 4074, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "109992", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to expand the permitted development right for floating solar installations on reservoirs in England and Wales to allow the electricity generated by the floating ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Solar Power: Reservoirs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877696", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877569, "askingMemberId": 4018, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "109991", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she intends to publish statutory guidance or a code of practice setting out the duty of care owed by higher education providers to their students.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Higher Education: Liability", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877569", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877626, "askingMemberId": 4008, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "109990", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she has taken to help ensure that the enrichment entitlement is received by young people in Gosport.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: Gosport", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877626", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877459, "askingMemberId": 3997, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "109989", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her policies of reports of Palestinian civilian deaths since the announcement of a ceasefire in Gaza.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gaza: Ceasefires", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877459", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877688, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "109988", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is planning to take to ensure the exchange of best practice among Healthcare Trusts from their deployment of Mental Health Support Teams.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mental Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877688", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877687, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "109987", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to conduct a post-implementation review of the potential impact of the early waves of deployment of Mental Health Support Teams on schools.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mental Health Services: Schools", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877687", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877579, "askingMemberId": 3952, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "109986", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what the five biggest allocations of funding for nature from International climate finance were in each year between 2021-22 and 2025-26.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Development Aid: Climate Change", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877579", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877469, "askingMemberId": 3952, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "109985", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average length of time was between charge and trial in a) rape, b) murder and c) GBH cases in each year between 2009 and 2025 for each court in England.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Crimes of Violence and Rape: Criminal Proceedings", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877469", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877468, "askingMemberId": 3952, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "109984", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many magistrates served in a) magistrate courts and b) family courts in each year between 2009 and 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Magistrates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877468", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877467, "askingMemberId": 3952, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "109983", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many court days were lost in 2025 due to the unavailability of courtrooms as a result of building failures by a) crown court, b) magistrates court and c) family court.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Courts: Buildings", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877467", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877466, "askingMemberId": 3952, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "109982", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many court days were lost in 2025 due to non-delivery of remanded prisoners to court by courier firms by a) prison held in, b) contracted courier company, c) Crown Court and d) Magistrates court.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisoner Escorts: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877466", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877596, "askingMemberId": 1576, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "109980", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to ensure illegal migrants accommodated in (a) hotels and (b) other government supported accommodation who leave that accommodation and do not report back within 72 hours are re", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants: Temporary Accommodation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877596", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877594, "askingMemberId": 1576, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "109979", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to ensure illegal migrants accommodated in (a) hotels and (b) other government supported accommodation are (i) kept securely within that accommodation and (ii) limited in the nu", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants: Temporary Accommodation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877594", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877522, "askingMemberId": 1576, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "109977", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will introduce pre-confirmation hearings before relevant select committees for permanent secretary appointments for government departments.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Senior Civil Servants: Recruitment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877522", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877519, "askingMemberId": 1576, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "109976", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will take legislative steps to amend the Public Interest Disclosure Act 1998 to protect whistleblowers from (a) illegal and (b) unethical work placed practices.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Disclosure of Information", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877519", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877515, "askingMemberId": 1576, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "109975", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to counter engagement with extreme online political content by members of the armed forces.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Radicalism: Internet", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877515", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877514, "askingMemberId": 1576, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "109974", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to counter espionage within the civil service.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Espionage: Civil Servants", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877514", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877659, "askingMemberId": 429, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "109968", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to respond to Question 106942 tabled by the hon. Member for Widnes and Halewood on 20 January 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cabinet Office: Written Questions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877659", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877657, "askingMemberId": 429, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-05T00:00:00", "uin": "109967", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to respond to Question 106941 tabled by the hon. Member for Widnes and Halewood on 20 January 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cabinet Office: Written Questions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877657", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877684, "askingMemberId": 415, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-10T00:00:00", "uin": "109965", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps she is taking to support civilians in the West Bank, in the context of recent reports of an increase in violent attacks by settlers.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877684", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877539, "askingMemberId": 373, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "109964", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the ability of the Solicitors Regulation Authority to access material over which privilege is claimed on the effectiveness of that organisation.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Solicitors Regulation Authority: Disclosure of Information", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877539", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877538, "askingMemberId": 373, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "109963", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he has had with the Solicitors Regulation Authority on their approach to complaints involving alleged Strategic Lawsuits Against Public Participation activity, including concerns that such compla", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Strategic Lawsuits against Public Participation: Complaints", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877538", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877537, "askingMemberId": 373, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "109962", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to strengthen protections against non-economic crime Strategic Lawsuits Against Public Participation.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Strategic Lawsuits against Public Participation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877537", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877536, "askingMemberId": 373, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "109961", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress his Department has made on ensuring the adequacy of legal protections for journalists, academics, campaigners and other public-interest actors facing Strategic Lawsuits Against Public Participation ", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Strategic Lawsuits against Public Participation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877536", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877521, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "109960", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what guidance her Department provides on the potential impact of Article 298 of the United Nations Convention on the Law of the Sea on British maritime logistics taking place", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "UN Convention on the Law of the Sea: British Overseas Territories", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877521", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877520, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "109959", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the transfer of Diego Garcia to Mauritius on the risk of nuclear proliferation across the African continent, in the co", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Africa: Nuclear Non-Proliferation Treaty", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877520", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1877446, "askingMemberId": 178, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2026-02-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2026-02-04T00:00:00", "uin": "109958", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department takes before issuing visas to former Pakistani military officers.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Visas: Pakistan", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1877446", "method": "GET"}]}]